<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>Dreamcast</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Stone 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Power Stone 2</name>
		<desc>The world's most revolutionary fighting game does it again! Power Stone 2 takes go-anywhere, grab-anything combat, and introduces awesome new innovations to the hit arcade fighting series. Now, up to four players wage insane battles in fully interactive, multi-level stages. Master over 120 different items used in battle - weapons, vehicles traps, power-upsand more! As if chaotic swashbuckling battles weren't enough, combine forces with other players to battle monstrous bosses to win the game!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Power Stone 2 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Power Stone 2 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Power Stone 2 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rainbow Cotton (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Rainbow Cotton</name>
		<desc>Another shooter in the Cotton saga. Trouble brews in the homeland of Cotton's long time friend Silk, as the evil demon Suede steals the legendary Willow candy from the queen's castle. Seeing as how no one can face Suede and his forces Silk drafts Cotton in order to restore peace to her land, but she may have forgotten that Cotton is a big fan of Willow candies herself...

Gameplay-wise Rainbow Cotton actually follows in the steps of Panorama Cotton as the gameplay switches from a 2D perspective to a 3rd person one. The gameplay itself however is reminiscent of games like Panzer Dragoon, in which you don't control Cotton as she flies, but instead where she aims with her magic spells. You can shoot down enemies as well as open chests, doors and other bonus locations for power-ups and spells, which advance Cotton's abilities in an rpg-lite fashion and increase your arsenal with different magical powers.

Taking advantage of the technological advances, the game uses for the first time polygonal graphics and to complement the action the game features 2D animated cutscenes between levels.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rainbow Cotton (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rainbow Cotton (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rainbow Cotton (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Success Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./fotns.zip</path>
		<name>'â˜†FIST OF THE NORTH STAR</name>
		<desc>This was an arcade game released in 2000 by Konami (also known as Punch Mania: Hokuto no Ken)</desc>
		<image>./mixart/fotns.png</image>
		<video>./snap/fotns.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/fotns.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20050101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Fighter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="13493" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Half-Life.cdi</path>
		<name>Half-life</name>
		<desc>Deep in the bowels of the Black Mesa Federal Research Facility, a decommissioned missile base, a top-secret experiment goes terribly wrong. As aliens come through the walls and a military death squad shoots everything in sight, young research associate Gordon Freeman must scramble to stay alive. Find your way through the monster-ridden areas of Black Mesa using your wits, limited security clearance, and a variety of weapons, ranging from a crowbar and pistols to a rocket launcher and grenades. With split-screen deathmatch and its exclusive "Decay" single-player and multiplayer cooperative modes, Half-Life is an action experience like no other.    Cancelled.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Valve</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Shooter / 3rd person-Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Half-Life.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Half-Life.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Half-Life.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Halo Revamped.cdi</path>
		<name>Halo Revamped</name>
		<desc />
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game id="13645" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./KISS Psycho Circus - The Nightmare Child (USA).cdi</path>
		<name>Kiss Psycho Circus - The Nightmare Child</name>
		<desc>Wicked Jester, a band of four, are headed for a Friday night gig at The Coventry, a rundown dive outside of town. They arrive only to find the parking lot deserted, the club seemingly dead. The band's members: Pablo Ramirez, Andy Chang, Gabriel Gordo and Patrick Scott, stepping from their van, are startled by a voice from the shadows. She offers them four tickets to a circus -- tonight's the grand finale! Having nothing better to do, the four accept and the nightmare begins.    Based on characters from comic book author Todd McFarlane, KISS Psycho Circus: The Nightmare Child brings the horror and carnage of the Psycho Circus to the PC in a shooter format. There are two-dozen creatures to battle with and three classes of weapons to use, each with four specific types: melee (beast claws, thornblade, twister and punisher), common (zero cannon, magma cannon, windblade and scourge) and ultimate (stargaze, galaxion, spirit lance and draco). In addition to the weaponry, temporary power-ups and instant items such as health, attack and defense powers are available.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20001029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tremor Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter</genre>
		<image>./mixart/KISS Psycho Circus - The Nightmare Child (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/KISS Psycho Circus - The Nightmare Child (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/KISS Psycho Circus - The Nightmare Child (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="13664" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Max Steel - Covert Missions (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Max Steel - Covert Missions</name>
		<desc>Mattel Interactive continues their Dreamcast assault with Max Steel, an action/adventure title based on the hit-rendered TV program of the same name. You control Max, a superhero with the ability to turn invisible and punch through walls, as he valiantly halts the plans of the diabolical John Dread. Gameplay is similar to Fighting Force 2, as you lead Max through expansive levels pummeling your foes with bare fists. The game also features voice-overs by the cast of the television show, adding dramatic flair to the proceedings. </desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20010530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treyarch</developer>
		<publisher>Mattel Electronics</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./mixart/Max Steel - Covert Missions (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Max Steel - Covert Missions (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Max Steel - Covert Missions (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="13593" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Soul Fighter (USA).cdi</path>
		<name>Soul Fighter</name>
		<desc>Pick the warrior, thief, or wizard, and fight through five huge levels, each with  its own boss. Your main weapons are your fists, but you can pull out weapons for quick kills. You only get so many shots with your weapon before it breaks, though.  Gameplay is basic 3D brawling. You will be attacked by one or more enemies, and will need to defend yourself, and attack back. The game features arcade and adventure modes. In the arcade mode, the levels are timed, and you only get 5 lives but you are revived where you died. In adventure mode, you get unlimited retries of each level, but must complete each level on a single life.  Note that your objective in each level is to kill every enemy; since the levels have multiple paths, you will need to backtrack often.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toka</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up-Role playing games-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Soul Fighter (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Soul Fighter (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Soul Fighter (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="13536" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Street Fighter III - Double Impact (USA).cdi</path>
		<name>Street Fighter III: Double Impact</name>
		<desc>After years of waiting, the true third sequel to Street Fighter is upon us.   3 Familiar faces in Ryu, Ken and Akuma appear in the roster, with 12 new faces including Sean, Yun, Yang, Alex, Ibuki, Elena, Dudley, Oro, Necro, Hugo, Urien and Gill. But even though they are new, the moves will seem familiar for those who have played other versions in the SF series. </desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Street Fighter III - Double Impact (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Street Fighter III - Double Impact (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Street Fighter III - Double Impact (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="13711" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wild Metal (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Wild Metal</name>
		<desc>Wild Metal Country is an action game in which one of five little tanks can be selected to control. Tank-like machines have gone wild on the three different planets of the Tehric system and the player's job is to defeat them.  The battles take place in desolate mountain environments. The big differences in altitude play an important role in the game. In the single player mode, complete levels by collecting 8 colored power cores, which are defended by the machines, and returning them to one of several hovering stores. The player has an infinite amount of lives. The weaponry consists of 8 types of missiles and 4 types of mines. Help is received from a pair of helicopters that drop ammo and provide healing.  The two tracks of the tank are operated independently. For example, make a quick spin by going forward with one track and backwards with the other. Moreover the turret can be turned in any direction. The camera always moves with the turret sometimes diverting the view towards the camera. The angle of the turret and the distance the rockets travel can be changed. The tank can only be controlled using the keyboard.  Noteworthy aspects of the game are: the physics modelling, the 3D engine and the amount of freedom the player has (no time constraints etc.). </desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20000201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Wild Metal (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wild Metal (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wild Metal (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Episode I Racer (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Star Wars - Episode I - Racer</name>
		<desc>Based upon the Pod Racing scenes of Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace, your mission as young Anakin Skywalker or as one of a collection of strange characters from around the Galaxy is to compete, survive and win in the high speed challenge of Pod Racing.

Each character has a unique Pod that can be upgraded with the credits you win after each race. Finish first to gain the most prestige and compete in greater and more challenging tracks, including the now famous race along the sand dunes of Tatooine that determined the destiny of many lives.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - Episode I Racer (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - Episode I Racer (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - Episode I Racer (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000404T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Magnetic Neo (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Super Magnetic Neo</name>
		<desc>In Super Magnetic Neo, a gang lead by evil, foul-mouthed baby Pinki has taken over Pao Pao Park.  The professor must stop her, so her sends Super Magnetic Neo, a little boy robot with a powerful electromagnet on his head.

The game has some resemblance to the Crash Bandicoot series in that some levels have you running toward the camera, have a side-view, or have you riding an animal.  It contains some running, jumping and switch-flipping much like any 3D platformer.  However, it does have a unique magnetism aspect.  Positive and Negative charges are represented by red and blue.  Neo's head can act as a positive or negative pole.  This is called his magnogimmick.  Using the principle of opposites charges attract and similar charges repel, Neo can pull himself toward platforms, then launch off them, or navigate many related environmental puzzles such as pulling himself into teleporters or swinging on magnetic pendulums.  Enemies also come in red and blue and can pulled pulled in to be captured or pushed away to be avoided accordingly.

You must use all these skills to make it through all four sections of Pao Pao Park and defeat Pinki.

There is also a challenge mode, with a series of short stages to pass all based around proper use of the magnogimmick.  It's something like the VR missions in the Metal Gear series.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super Magnetic Neo (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Super Magnetic Neo (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Magnetic Neo (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crave Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris 4D (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Tetris 4D</name>
		<desc>Tetris 4D is a fairly standard Tetris game that was released in Japan shortly after the Dreamcast launched.

The game features two modes, Classic and Battle. Classic mode offers a normal solitaire Tetris game: rotate and fit falling blocks to complete lines. Five difficulty settings are available, which change the speed and piece preview settings.

The sound and graphics generally follow a modern urban/industrial theme, with five techno music choices, including a variation of the classic Tetris "Karinka". The 3D backgrounds are basic but shift viewpoint as you advance in levels.

The Battle mode offers two to four player multiplayer. One player starts off flagged, and blocks push up from the bottom as other players make lines. Once he makes enough lines himself the flag moves to another player. Difficulty is set independently allowing for handicaps.

Unfortunately, you can't play the battle mode against the computer. There's also no VMU support for saving high scores, a rather critical omission for this type of game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tetris 4D (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tetris 4D (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tetris 4D (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19981223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zero Gunner 2 (JAP).chd</path>
		<name>Zero Gunner 2</name>
		<desc>Zero Gunner 2 would on first inspection appear to be a bog-standard 2D shooter. However this import game actually has a bit of a unique "spin" on the shooter genre.  Most noticable, all backdrops and vehicles in this game are modelled in 3D. The textures are quite highly detailed and this adds more depth than standard 2D shooters. Secondly, since your craft is a helicopter, a unique "target and spin" feature has been added whereby you can both rotate your craft to better attack an enemy or alternatively to lock on a particular point in space and rotate around it while still firing. This is all controlled by the player however and is not automatic; to succeed mastering this feature is imperative.  The usual power-ups and bosses are included, along with a selection of helicopters to select from.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Zero Gunner 2 (JAP).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Zero Gunner 2 (JAP).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Zero Gunner 2 (JAP).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010906T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psikyo</developer>
		<publisher>Psikyo</publisher>
		<genre>Various-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia - Arabian Nights (USA).cdi</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia - Arabian Nights</name>
		<desc>The Sultan of Persia and his son-in-law are visiting the Sultan's brother, Assan. The friendly family meeting soon turns into a nightmare: Assan kills the young Prince's bodyguards, locks him up in a prison, and captures the Sultan. The reason is a little disagreement between the brothers regarding matrimonial arrangements: it appears that the Sultan had promised his daughter to Assan's son, Rugnor, and later broke his promise by letting her marry the Prince. In the resulting turmoil, the Sultan is killed, and the Princess is kidnapped by Rugnor, a ruthless half-tiger creature. The Prince must figure out a way to find Rugnor, defeat him, and rescue his wife.    Prince of Persia 3D is just what its title implies: an action platformer with puzzle-solving elements in the style of the previous Prince of Persia games, but set in a three-dimensional environment. The Prince still has to time his jumps, avoid deadly traps, interact with the environment, and fight Rugnor's minions who will try to stop him.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20061206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Prince of Persia - Arabian Nights (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Prince of Persia - Arabian Nights (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Prince of Persia - Arabian Nights (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zombie Revenge (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Zombie Revenge</name>
		<desc>A top secret government plan to use undead soldiers has gone horribly wrong. Just before it was ready to be put into operation, someone unknown interfered. Now a year later the city is the home for the undead. Three agents, Stick Breitling, Linda Rotta and Rikiya Busujima, who have come together from various paths of fate, now join together to do battle against the army of the undead and rid the streets of the zombie scum!  The game features multiple weapons and 1 or 2-player arcade action. Each of the characters have different attributes, agility, strength, better with weapons as opposed to unarmed combat.   There are a multitude of weapons that can be found through the game such as shotguns and machine guns to battle the undead. There are a range of attacks that can be performed, charging your shot by holding down the button longer, variable shots by locking on the zombie longer, rolling attacks, backward and dash attacks and more.  There are a number of game modes accessible from the main menu. The Arcade mode from the coin-op version, an Original Dreamcast version, which gives you options of playing the game with more focus on either weapons only or bare knuckle fighting. There is also a vs Boss and Fighting mode, as well as a Training Room.  Zombie Revenge also features downloadable mini games for your VM unit. There is a Zombie Revenge Raising Game where you feed and raise your own zombie. Playing the above mentioned Original mode provides food items for your zombie. The zombie you have raised can also be uploaded to the Internet, or emailed to someone, and other peoples zombies can be downloaded.  There are two other mini-games: Zombie Fishing (fish for zombies) and Zombie Doubt (memory test with symbols).</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Zombie Revenge (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Zombie Revenge (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Zombie Revenge (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM1</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Psychic Force 2012 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Psychic Force 2012</name>
		<desc>Psychic Force 2012,  the sequel to Psychic Force,  is a one-on-one fighting game with a twist. The matches take place inside a giant floating cube. You are able to fly, using your psychic abilities, around a 3D arena with six walls. Each of the ten available characters, Might, Regina, Wendy, Emilio, Setsuna, Patty, Gudeath, Genshin, Carlo, and Gates, are controlled with three buttons: guard, weak attack and strong attack. The effect varies with the distance. Next to the regular life meter, there is also a power meter. By using special moves, the meter is drained and your moves are limited. It is possible to recharge, and the capacity of the power meter expands when you lose a lot of health.  Additionally, each fighter has its own unique moves, energy attacks and a weapon, which they use, mid-flight, to pummel their opponent. There are three main game modes: training, versus and a story mode using static anime-inspired images and in-engine cut scenes to tell the story. The story centers around two groups of psychics with differing ideals about co-existence with humans. In the middle of this are several neutral psychics with ties to members in either group.  The later PlayStation port, renamed to Psychic Force 2, adds the 3 missing characters from the first game (Genma, Brad and Sonia), the psy-expand mode where the player can play a series of special battles to learn other character attacks, and an anime intro video replacing the original in-game intro. It also lowers the overall difficulty of the CPU fighters and makes some control adjustments (for instance the shield can now optionally be enabled with a single button). Of course, the graphics were notably degraded.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Psychic Force 2012 (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Psychic Force 2012 (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Psychic Force 2012 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow Man (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Shadow Man</name>
		<desc>You're the Shadow Man, a person who can switch between the world of the dead and of the living. In Shadow Man your mission is to prevent 5 serial killers from bringing the total armageddon. In the world of the living, you're mortal and have conventional weapons. When you die, you are transported to the world of the dead and you become Shadow Man once again. Which means you're not really mortal. In the world of the dead you can't use normal weapons, your gun shoots ghosts which kill the zombies and the other ugly creatures which live there. You also have different voodoo powers and weapons. And you're carrying a large inventory around.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Shadow Man (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Shadow Man (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Shadow Man (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Triggerheart Exelica (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Trigger Heart Exelica</name>
		<desc>In the distant future humanity will develop intelligent weapons called Trigger Hearts. Despite their awesome offensive strengths, Trigger Hearts aesthetically closely resemble humans, and overtime even develop unique personalities. Of three existing Trigger Hearts one, named Faintear, has mysteriously vanished two years ago. The story begins as the two remaining Trigger Hearts - Exelica and Crueltear (who took on the personality of Exelica's big sister) are summoned to quell a mysterious rebellion of military machines against their human creators.  Trigger Heart Exelica is an arcade-style top-down shooter and is composed of 5 stages of shooting mayhem. Most levels take place in futuristic environments such as sky cities and space stations. The player is given a choice of one of the two Trigger Hearts at the beginning of the game - Exelica, who emits a wide fan of weak shots, and Crueltear, who fires a narrowly concentrated barrage of projectiles. However, the firing pattern of guns matters little during the game, as Trigger Heart's most awesome weapon is common to both models, and is called the Anchor Shot. By using the Anchor Shot Trigger Hearts are able to grab, swing, use as a shield, and hurl back any flying enemy vehicle in the game, including even the most giant of enemy battle cruisers. When thrown, the enemy cuts a path of destruction across the entire screen, causing explosive chain reactions between adjacent ships and occasionally even obliterating bosses in one hit. The Anchor Shot is a tricky weapon to use, as it requires the player to circle the joystick in order to give enemy ships more inertia while continuing to dodge enemy fire. The trajectory of the released enemy is also somewhat difficult to predict. Another innovative feature of Trigger Heart Exelica is AI-adjusted boss difficulty level, which will cut more slack to the inexperienced player, while attempting to punish the pros.  In addition to the original Arcade mode the home version of the game includes a Story mode, which adds fully voiced cutscenes, additional endings and bosses throughout the game, and Arranged Mode, which is just like the arcade mode, but is limited to Normal difficulty, no continues, and only two lives, and serves as a challenge to the most experienced players.  The PS2 port includes a new opening movie, story mode and CG sequences. TH44 Faintear is now a player selectable fighter and The Triggerheart Backupper C'r_na, originally only a story concept, now appears in the game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Triggerheart Exelica (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Triggerheart Exelica (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Triggerheart Exelica (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Warashi</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="13760" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mars Matrix (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mars Matrix</name>
		<desc>Mars Matrix is a top-down vertical scrolling shoot-em-up (shmup) game, originally for the Capcom CPS-2 arcade board. It is the second in a series of three Capcom/Takumi shmups, between Giga Wing and Giga Wing 2.  Mars Matrix features unique gameplay based on the "mosquito" system. By holding down the fire button, your ship can absorb shots and then "spit' them back at the enemies. Additionally, each destroyed enemy (and reflected shot) releases experience cubes of various values, which can multiplied by chaining. This experience is used to power-up your ship, and also acts as a multiplier for your score.  The Dreamcast port also includes some extra features that can be unlocked by accumulating points in the game. These features include replay videos, an image gallery, a score attack mode for perfecting individual levels, and even a complete extra game mode with a new enemy sequence. </desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Takumi</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<image>./mixart/Mars Matrix (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mars Matrix (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mars Matrix (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="13653" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Samba De Amigo (USA)[DCRES].chd</path>
		<name>Samba De Amigo</name>
		<desc>Samba De Amigo is a highly unique game:  a maracas simulation.  Game play is based around a special maracas controller that you use to interact with the music.  The controller senses which region in space out of a possible 6 that the maracas are in.  It also senses when the player shakes the maracas.  As the music plays, the player must shake the maracas in the appropriate region with proper timing to progress.  A standard controller can also be used if you do not have the maracas controller, which is sold separately.  The music in the game comes from a wide variety of sources.  Some of the songs are traditional samba music, while others are recognizable pop tunes, like "Macarena" and "Tequila."</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20001016T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Samba De Amigo (USA)[DCRES].png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Samba De Amigo (USA)[DCRES].png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Samba De Amigo (USA)[DCRES].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ready 2 Rumble Boxing (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Ready 2 Rumble Boxing</name>
		<desc>Ready 2 Rumble Boxing is a boxing video game developed by Midway and published in 1999 for the Dreamcast, PlayStation, Game Boy Color, and Nintendo 64. The success of the Dreamcast version led to it becoming one of the few Sega All Stars titles.    Like Nintendo's Punch-Out!! series, it features many characters with colorful personalities (i.e. Afro Thunder, Boris "The Bear" Knokimov, etc.); however, unlike the Punch-Out!! series, Ready 2 Rumble Boxing is in 3D, thus allowing for more control over one's character in the ring. Also unlike Punch-Out!!, players can choose whichever boxer they want from a rather large selection of characters.    One unique graphic feature of the game is the gradual bruises gained by players as the fight progresses (like hematomas and swellings), present in all fifth-generation versions. While this is not necessarily a new feature to games (it had been implemented before in SNK's 1992 game Art of Fighting), it garnered much appraisal from reviewers, because of the added fun factor this element supply to the game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ready 2 Rumble Boxing (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ready 2 Rumble Boxing (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ready 2 Rumble Boxing (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blue Stinger (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Blue Stinger</name>
		<desc>After an object from outerspace hits Dinosaur Island and surrounds it in a protective cocoon, you are left stranded to uncover the secret that could end life on Earth as we know it.   You play sea rescue expert Eliot Ballade, or weapons specialist Dogs Bower. Explore the island, solve puzzles and avoid hazards in seven areas and 230 locations. You can swim, drive, climb and fight, hand-to-hand or with the arsenal at hand.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Blue Stinger (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Blue Stinger (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Blue Stinger (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Climax</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Carrier (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Carrier</name>
		<desc>Carrier is a Survival Horror game published by Jaleco Entertainment released on January 31st, 2000 for the SEGA Dreamcast.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Carrier (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Carrier (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Carrier (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20001031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Survival Horror</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Confidential Mission (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Confidential Mission</name>
		<desc>Confidential Mission is a light-gun compatible shooting game most easily likened to Sega's Virtua Cop series.  You play as either Howard Gibson or Jean Clifford, both super-agents a la James Bond, and you are taken through scenarios shooting enemies and attempting to avoid civilian casualties.

The game is a home version of the coin operated arcade machine, and is playable by one or two players.  The game includes the popular features of the Virtua Cop series "Justice Shot" (in which you shoot an enemy's gun or gun arm instead of killing them) and the "Combo Shot" in which you can hit an enemy with up to three shots before they expire.  The home version does include some mini-games and training modes that were not in the arcade version of the game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Confidential Mission (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Confidential Mission (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Confidential Mission (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010514T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cosmic Smash (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Cosmic Smash</name>
		<desc>Cosmic Smash for Dreamcast is a port of the Sega Rosso arcade game. It is a futuristic sports game, a mix of squash and Breakout.

The player controls a semi-transparent human male in third-person view. The goal is to clear each level from a set of different blocks at the far end of the room within a given time limit. Additional time is given at the start of the next level depending on how well the player did. To clear the room, the player has to hit a ball with a racket at the correct angle. The ball bounces back from the blocks and walls. The blocks have different properties, for example, some have to be hit multiple times before they disappear, while others move around thus making them harder to hit.

Besides the regular shot, the player can also perform a trick shot, which in combination with other moves gives extra points when successfully executed. At the end of each level, a map with branching paths is displayed, enabling the player to take different routes towards the end of the game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Cosmic Smash (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Cosmic Smash (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cosmic Smash (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crazy Taxi (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Crazy Taxi</name>
		<desc>Crazy Taxi is an arcade-like racer where the player takes the role of a taxi driver who weaves his way through crowded streets, across sidewalks and even under water, in a wild and frantic race to deliver passengers on time. The courses are largely set inside cities crowded with general traffic and pedestrians (which can't be run over, they dive away). The main goal is to bring as many customers as possible to their destination in time. Available customers are marked through circles and the colour represents the distance and the fare they offer. Green means long rides with plenty of money, and red ones are very short.   In the main Arcade mode there is a timer that quickly runs down. It can be replenished by picking up customers. While driving reckless maneuvers are encouraged. Players can disregard all traffic rules and customers give extra tips for speedy and dangerous driving, but these can only be cashed when the customer arrives at his destination in time. By the same token the reward at the end of a ride is based on the amount of time left, as each customer also has a personal timer. The city is filled with slopes and jumps, and the game uses a very loose driving model. No damage can be done to the car, so driving as fast as possible is encouraged. While driving players can toy with the gears to perform two special tricks: a crazy drift and a crazy boost to speed up more quickly.  Next to the Arcade mode there is an Original mode, and Crazy Box where specific goals need to be met on closed down courses. In the regular modes it is possible to disregard the usual timer and play for a fixed amount of minutes. At the end of the race the player is rewarded with a license, either D, C, B or A, with S for an outstanding performance. Next to the interactive courses from the arcade version there is a new course for home consoles. There are four cabs and drivers to choose from. The cars have different statistics and the drivers different attitudes while racing. The game has a soundtrack featuring The Offspring and Bad Religion (not for the Xbox 360 version).</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Crazy Taxi (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Crazy Taxi (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Crazy Taxi (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Death Crimson OX (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Death Crimson OX</name>
		<desc>On July 29, 2010, the city of Saronica comes under attack by an army of monsters called the SMO as they lay siege to the city, capturing it and ruling the populace under an iron fist.  During this, The Resistance is formed in an attempt to stop the SMO, lead by a woman by the name of Lily who is kidnapped when she attempts to help a man by the name of Kou.  After she is captured, it is learned the man has come into possession of two ancient pistols by the name of "Crimson" that can destroy the monsters and their vicious leader.  Kou sets out with Lily's daughter, Yuri, to bring her back and stop the evil forces within the city.

Death Crimson is a light-gun game similar in style to House of the Dead where the player shoots at enemies that pop up on screen and save innocents from the monsters.  The player can also power-up the "Crimson" pistols by shooting death flowers that will turn their firepower into machine guns to decimate hordes of enemies.  There is also a health meter that will increase in size by successfully shooting enemies, gaining experience points.   Once enough points are obtained, the health bar will increase, however missing enemies or shooting civilians will take away points.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Death Crimson OX (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Death Crimson OX (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Death Crimson OX (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ecole</developer>
		<publisher>Ecole</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dux.cdi</path>
		<name>Dux</name>
		<desc>DUX is a scrolling shooter in the vein of R-Type. When scientists searched for new materials to enhance their space ships, they discovered a new and powerful material they dubbed DUX. Since this type of material proved unstable, nobody except the player seemed brave enough to fly the space ship constructed from it. The player's job is to lead the ship through a series of horizontal levels against the Spiritual Spacers "to reach the obvious."

The player's ship has a standard laser shot that can be upgraded or changed for x-ray and bounce shots, which are very similar to the weapons in R-Type. The player also has a pod that protects them from enemy bullets and that can be launched as an offensive weapon in a move called "dash." Keeping the fire button pressed will launch a more powerful hyper shot.

To score points, the player can destroy chains of enemies in quick succession or soak up chains of bullets. Hyper Soaking makes the player invulnerable to bullets, but drains the Obvious Energy gauge if not enough bullets are soaked in or new energy orbs are picked up. The player wins the game if they manage to beat all the bosses at the end of each level. If they are hit by a bullet or collide with their surroundings, a life is lost. After all lives and continues are depleted, the game is over.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dux.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dux.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dux.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hucast</developer>
		<publisher>Hucast</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Evil Twin - Cyprien's Chronicles (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Evil Twin - Cyprien's Chronicles</name>
		<desc>Evil Twin: Cyprien's Chronicles is a surrealistic 3D platformer from France. The player guides the orphan boy Cyprien through a darkly comical environment  spanning 8 distinct islands and about 70 stages, in a mission to save his 4 friends, find his talking teddy bear, and confront his inner self.   Cyprien is helped and hindered through his quest by an assortment of strange beings, from an elephant named Wilbur, who makes his entrances and exits on a swing, a tribe of demis - creatures cut in half, a giant termite queen, a dark root, and many many more.  He is not helpless in his battle against the odds however. He has brought along to this strange dimension Super-Cyp, his heroic alter ego, into whom he may change temporarily using the power-ups scattered around the levels. </desc>
		<image>./mixart/Evil Twin - Cyprien's Chronicles (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Evil Twin - Cyprien's Chronicles (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Evil Twin - Cyprien's Chronicles (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020412T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bigben Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>In Utero</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Expendable (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Expendable</name>
		<desc>In 2463 a race of vicious aliens has invaded human planets, wiping out the population of Novocastria first. Only the Millennium Soldier can lead the human fightback. 

In this sci-fi action game, reflex shooting dominates over planning or tactical play. Expect non-stop action from fighting and relentlessly killing off tons of bad guys across more than 20 levels of 3rd person 3D action, taking place inside and outside. Powering up your weaponry is crucial - there are 18 different ones to collect, from pulse cannons to particle accelerators and rockets to missiles. Two player cooperative and deathmatch modes are provided.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Expendable (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Expendable (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Expendable (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rage Software</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fighting Vipers 2 (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Fighting Vipers 2</name>
		<desc>This game is a sequel to Fighting Vipers, a 3D fighting game that allows you to face adolescents and adults that comes from different "urban tribes", but also, in that second version you can choose or beat another time the most charismatic characters of FV1 and some unedited characters never seen again (either in FV2 arcade, version appeared in 1998 on Model 3 arcade board).

FV2, as in FV, has the incentive to destroy the fight arena walls with the last combat impact, also, you can destroy again the armor of your opponent, that as a newness in 1998's FV2, includes the "Super KO System", in which, if you break the armor of your opponent and immediately, you make a Super Combo that leaves him "confused", you will win without dispute a second round.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fighting Vipers 2 (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fighting Vipers 2 (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fighting Vipers 2 (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Floigan Bros. Episode 1 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Floigan Bros. - Episode 1</name>
		<desc>Floigan Bros. Episode 1 is a Action/Platformer 3D game published by SEGA, Visual Concepts released on July 30th, 2001 for the SEGA Dreamcast.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Floigan Bros. Episode 1 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Floigan Bros. Episode 1 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Floigan Bros. Episode 1 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Visual Concepts</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform 3D</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fur Fighters (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Fur Fighters</name>
		<desc>A group of baby stuffed animals are kidnapped from their families by the Stupid Bears (an evil gang of stuffed teddy bears, of all things!), and it is up to the Fur Fighters to save the young ones.   The group that you control ranges from Kangaroos and Penguins to Cats and Dogs, all with their unique abilities and styles of fighting, which you must use to not only defeat the Stupid Bears, but complete puzzles and specific objectives along the way. You can control only one character at a time, but there are teleport areas so that you can change your character to one that can complete the tasks at hand.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fur Fighters (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fur Fighters (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fur Fighters (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000714T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bizarre Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hydro Thunder (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Hydro Thunder</name>
		<desc>Port of Midway's arcade boat-racer. The premise is non-existent, you simply rev up the engines and go on 13 water courses set in Antarctica, the far east, the Greek isles, etc. on different types of futuristic boats. Races use the usual arcade checkpoint system and scattered across the courses you'll find an assortment of power-ups and upgrades like nitro boosters.   Graphics are entirely 3D with reflective water effects and realistic bouncing and bucking in the boats. Multiplayer competitions are supported for 2 players on the PlayStation version.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Hydro Thunder (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Hydro Thunder (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hydro Thunder (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Eurocom</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver</name>
		<desc>1500 years after Blood Omen: Legacy of Kain, the vampire Kain's decision at the end of that game has finally defeated the human kingdoms and brought the world of Nosgoth under his control. Ruling from a castle built on the Pillars of Nosgoth, Kain has established an empire of six vampire clans, each ruled by a lieutenant, the sons of Kain. Raziel was one such lieutenant, but lost his position through the "insolence" of receiving a new evolutionary "dark gift", the growth of feathery wings, before his master had acquired it. Fearing that Raziel might one day surpass him, Kain tears off Raziel's wings in a fit of range and banishes him into the Abyss.  There, Raziel is lost in time, died and his body consumed. The Elder God recovers Raziel's soul and rebuilds the broken body, not as a living vampire, but as a strange new creature of the underworld. Swearing revenge on Kain, Raziel now phases seamlessly between Nosgoth and it's underworld, using his new powers to become a terrible reaver of souls...  Soul Reaver is a 3rd person action-adventure title that follows Raziel on his quest to purge the land of vampires and take revenge on Kain and his brothers, leaders of the six clans. The player controls the game from behind Raziel's shoulder, moving him in any direction, climbing, attacking, jumping and using specific abilities. Raziel's can grip onto the edge of ledges and his torn wings allow him to glide gently downwards. Raziel can shift through the "material" world into the "spectral" realm at will... but must find specific locations in order to shift back. The two realms mirror one another, with distortions which give access to new areas and platforms. Existing in the material world drains Raziel's life energy at a constant rate.  Throughout the game, energy is recovered by consuming the souls of defeated enemies. If Raziel is able to defeat one of his brothers, he will additionally gain a new ability ("dark gift") upon drinking it's soul. Examples include: the ability to swim, file telekinetic projectiles or the ability to phase through locked gates. Raziel can arm himself with a variety of weapons including spears, daggers, swords, axes, as well as attacking enemies barehanded. Eventually, Raziel will also come across Kain's personal sword (named the Soul Reaver), and will use it to create a powerful energy blade weapon.  The world is left open to Raziel, he can return to areas previously completed and explore the world of Nosgoth at will. Access to certain areas however sometimes  requires the use of gained specific abilities. Many of the puzzles the player will need to solve in this quest are "block puzzles", requiring the placement of certain large structures (usually square blocks), either to activate switches or to build access to out-of-reach areas. </desc>
		<image>./mixart/Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Crystal Dynamics</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Maken X (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Maken X</name>
		<desc>Maken X is a sword - a "Soul Sword" that possesses a unique ability called brainjacking. It can take over the mind and the body of another creature and adapt all its strength and weaknesses. Maken X is also the hero of the game - a wandering mutant spirit of the sword. The ability to manipulate a person's "psi", or soul, was discovered in a research lab. The chief scientist is kidnapped by terrorists and his daughter Kay awakens Maken X who now must assist her on her dangerous mission.  Maken X is a first-person action-adventure game with emphasis on melee combat, that offers the player the possibility of controlling minds and bodies of thirteen characters the player may meet while journeying. Each character has their own attacks, advantages, and disadvantages. Throughout the game the player has to make decisions that will influence the plot and bring the game to one of its seven endings.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Maken X (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Maken X (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Maken X (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metropolis Street Racer (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Metropolis Street Racer</name>
		<desc>Enter a new age of driving, a new form of thinking and feeling, and totally immerse yourself in the most advanced driving game ever created. Your 'Kudos' is the only path to success, since this is a unique test of skill, style and precision, which spans the streets of London, Tokyo and San Francisco. Be astounded by the realism, push your limits round 250+ different circuits, in hundreds of challenging events. Indulge up to 8 people in a unique multiplayer experience, and prepare yourself for the ultimate internet Kudos Challenge. From established racing game developers, Bizarre Creations, and featuring music from the renowned Richard Jacques, this game will change the way you think about driving forever.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Metropolis Street Racer (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Metropolis Street Racer (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Metropolis Street Racer (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bizarre Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving-Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NHL 2K2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>NHL 2K2</name>
		<desc>NHL 2K is a series of hockey games by 2K Sports for the Dreamcast, PlayStation 2, Nintendo GameCube, Xbox, iPhone, Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, and the Wii. Initially discontinued after the release of NHL 2K11 in 2010, the brand was revived on mobile devices in 2014. The games are officially licensed from the National Hockey League and NHL Players Association. While its games were released on consoles, its main competition was EA Sports' NHL video games.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/NHL 2K2 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/NHL 2K2 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/NHL 2K2 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treyarch</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Hockey-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Stone (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Power Stone</name>
		<desc>The creators of Street Fighter add a new dimension to 3D fighting. In Power Stone, 2 fighters take to multi-level arenas with Power Stones and other weapons lying around for use.

Each game contains Power Stones. When you have enough stones (between three to five), your character transforms into an almost unbeatable warrior, with an all-new range of moves (although this does not last for long).</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Power Stone (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Power Stone (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Power Stone (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Psyvariar 2-The Will to Fabricate (JP).chd</path>
		<name>Psyvariar 2 - The Will To Fabricate</name>
		<desc>Psyvariar 2 is another specimen of the recent breed of "newschool" arcade shoot'em'ups (other examples being Ikaruga and Border Down). As many other recently released shoot'em'ups, it combines basic arcade shooter gameplay with modern 3D graphics to liven up the genre. The level backgrounds as well as all enemies are modeled in full 3D, with the action taking place in a vertically scrolling two-dimensional plane which moves through the level.  As most of the other new-style SHMUPs, Psyvariar 2 has a gimmick: getting close to enemies or shots without actually being hit is called "buzzing" and yields massive extra score. In addition, the player ship's rate of fire is rather slow by default and can be raised by shaking the ship left and right a few times and then keeping moving horizontally - as soon as the horizontal movement stops, the fire rate drops down to normal again.   As in most other of the new Japanese style of shoot'em'ups, there are usually an  extremely high number of enemy shots on the screen. All these factors combine to make learning precise control a central part of the game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Psyvariar 2-The Will to Fabricate (JP).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Psyvariar 2-The Will to Fabricate (JP).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Psyvariar 2-The Will to Fabricate (JP).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20040226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Skonec</developer>
		<publisher>Success</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quake III Arena (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Quake III Arena</name>
		<desc>Quake III Arena is a First Person Shooter game published by Raster, SEGA released on October 22nd, 2000 for the SEGA Dreamcast.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Quake III Arena (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Quake III Arena (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Quake III Arena (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20001206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raster</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>First Person Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Re-Volt (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Re-Volt</name>
		<desc>For years, the Toy-Volt company has been producing toys and games for children all over the world. Within months of introducing their first products, Toy-Volt shot to the top! No one could put their finger on exactly what it was that made the toys so popular. Sure, they employed the best designers and marketers in the world, but there was something else about Toy-Volt toys, something almost.... magic. Now, their newest R/C cars really start to live!   Re-Volt is a racing game where you take control over one of more than 28 R/C cars and drive on one of the 13 tracks. The tracks are varied, and include a toy shop, a supermarket, a luxury liner and more. It is possible to play a "reversed" (backwards) or "mirror" (reversed left and right) variety of each track. There are also 4 levels of realism to choose from.   There are a couple of single- and multiplayer game modes to choose from. There's a Single Race, where you complete a single track while competing with several computer-controlled opponents; a Championship, where you try to complete a series of races in hopes of finishing on the top; and Multiplayer, where you play with live opponents. There's also a Time Trial, where you're alone on the track, and simply try to get as best a time as possible; a Practice mode, where you're free to drive around a track to learn its structure and shortcuts; and the Stunt Arena, where you drive around a special arena and try to collect stars situated in hard-to-reach places.   In Single Race, Championship and Multiplayer there are power-ups scattered throughout the track; picking them up gives you a one-use random power, such as missiles to launch at pesky opponents, a star to temporarily freeze competitors in place or a lightning bolt, which makes your car shock opponents nearby to make them stop.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Re-Volt (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Re-Volt (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Re-Volt (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rez (PAL).chd</path>
		<name>Rez</name>
		<desc>Rez is a fast-action shooter that takes you deep into the worldâ€™s computer network. The â€œProject Kâ€ Network has recently been upgraded to handle the rapid expansion of the information age and the core, known as â€œEden,â€ holds the most advanced artificial intelligence the world has ever seen. Unfortunately, Eden cannot handle the ability to create her own thoughts and buckles under the pressure in an existential breakdown. She is lost deep inside the system, and youâ€™re the only one that can bring her back online, saving the world from utter chaos.  You must blast complex viruses, unlock passwords, and destroy firewall bosses as you search for Eden. Each stage is in a constant state of flux dependent on your shooting techniques, which ultimately control the music and colors of your environment. The deeper you get into the dreamlike cyber world of Rez, your form will evolve or devolve depending on your progress.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rez (PAL).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rez (PAL).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rez (PAL).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>United Game Artists</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega GT (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sega GT</name>
		<desc>With a nod towards GT2, Sega tosses in their entry in the race-career-category, meaning that this game is all about racing. Racing to win competitions, cars, money and other prizes (such as licenses for bigger cars), buying new cars to race in, upgrading cars to race in and gaining licenses to race with.

It features realistic controls, graphic and physics, and spans over career, multiplayer or arcade modes, and hundreds of cars to boot.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sega GT (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sega GT (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sega GT (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20000829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Slave Zero (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Slave Zero</name>
		<desc>500 years in the future, man and machine are virtually one and the greatest megacity in the world is locked in brutal war. You are the ultimate saboteur and part of an elite fighting force. Your mission: steal the largest, most sophisticated biomechanical attack weapon ever designed.. and kick some serious ass.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Slave Zero (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Slave Zero (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Slave Zero (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soldier of Fortune v1.001 (2001)(Crave)(NTSC)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Soldier Of Fortune</name>
		<desc>A terrorist organization has stolen nuclear weapons from a facility in Russia, intending to sell them to various third-world nations, initiating a global conflict. The player takes the role of John Mullins, a US mercenary working for an organization known as "The Shop". The goal is simple: hunt the villains across the globe, thwart their evil plans, and save the world!  Like most 3D shooters, Soldier of Fortune consists mainly of exploring the environments and killing the enemies that try to impede the player's progress. It is one of the first shooters to isolate over 20 different body regions and show/inflict damage to those regions. For example, if the player character shoots an enemy in the foot, the enemy will limp. The game was also notable for including realistic gore animations resulting from the injuries sustained by the enemies.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Soldier of Fortune v1.001 (2001)(Crave)(NTSC)(US)[!].png</image>
		<video>./snap/Soldier of Fortune v1.001 (2001)(Crave)(NTSC)(US)[!].mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Soldier of Fortune v1.001 (2001)(Crave)(NTSC)(US)[!].png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010724T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crave Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Raven Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Adventure (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sonic Adventure</name>
		<desc>Yet again Sonic and friends find themselves wrapped up in the schemes of Dr. Robotnik. This time he plans to exploit the power of Chaos, a malevolent being that feeds upon the power of the Chaos Emeralds. In their own ways five heroes will do what they can to save Station Square and, perhaps, the entire world.  The player can select from which character to play after meeting them with Sonic, and each has their own unique version of each level. Sonic's levels involve racing through a level as quickly as possible, destroying any robots along the way. Tails can hover over distances, and his levels are similar to Sonic's except that he must beat an opponent to the finish line. Amy can't charge up ramps or run as quickly as Sonic and Tails, but she does have a giant hammer she can break obstacles with. The goal of her levels is to avoid being captured by a robot sent after her by Dr. Robotnik. E102 Gamma is a slow, difficult to maneuver robot, but it has guns and missiles that can lock on to several targets at once, chaining together attacks and earning a higher score and more time on the clock. The goal of its levels is to reach a boss enemy and destroy it before time runs out. The final character is Big the Cat, a fisherman searching for his lost frog. Big's levels are almost entirely devoid of action or fighting; he just fishes. Each character can find items that increase their abilities as the story progresses, such as a ring for Sonic that lets him home along lines of rings, or improved lures for Big. A final chapter wrapping up the story is unlocked after all other characters have been completed.  Additionally each of the characters can visit the Chao garden where they can raise baby Chaos. By petting, feeding, and showing animals found in levels to the Chaos they can grow stronger, and optionally be put into races against other Chaos. As well each level in the game has additional objectives that can be completed to acquire extra emblems, although the emblems don't do anything in this version of the game. Finally at one time it was possible to go online and download additional levels and bonuses in the game, such a Christmas theme for Station Square and a level sponsored by AT&amp;T, but since SegaNet shut down this is no longer possible.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sonic Adventure (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sonic Adventure (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sonic Adventure (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sonic Team</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Adventure 2 (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
		<name>Sonic Adventure 2</name>
		<desc>Sonic has returned! This time, his nemesis Dr. Eggman has teamed up with Shadow, a dark hedgehog with a mysterious past, and is aiming once again (like he doesn't) to rule the entire world with the power of the Chaos Emeralds! It's up to Sonic and his friends to stop Eggman and put him out of business for good!  With new features such as a story line told from the view of both the good guys and the villains, greater speed, and an improved A-Life system, Sonic Adventure 2 is poised to be Sonic's greatest and most dangerous mission yet!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sonic Adventure 2 (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sonic Adventure 2 (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sonic Adventure 2 (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Channel 5 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Space Channel 5</name>
		<desc>Hey there, Space Cats! Some pesky little aliens called Morolians are trying to take over Earth, and they're forcing the population to dance endlessly! Space Channel 5, the planet's news channel, has sent the grooviest reporter they have, Ulala, out to cover the latest happenings, but those little Morolians also have to be taught a lesson! So it's now up to Ulala to dance and groove with the aliens to beat them at their own game and free the population of Earth! Get dancin', Space Cats, 'cuz we're gonna give those aliens a little taste of their own groove!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Space Channel 5 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Space Channel 5 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Space Channel 5 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000604T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spawn - In The Demon's Hand (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Spawn - In the Demon's Hand</name>
		<desc>Todd McFarlane's dark comic book anti-hero, Spawn, is ready to give your Dreamcast hell. Play as Spawn (a.k.a. Al Simmons), or any of the anti-heroes or villains from the comics, such as Clown, Twitch, Overtkill, Angel, Redeemer and more in a battle royale blastfest. Not up to killing just anyone? Play Team Battle and join with a friend to blast those other guys! Just do your best to get to the big guy downstairs: Maelebogia, to reclaim your soul and return to life.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Spawn - In The Demon's Hand (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Spawn - In The Demon's Hand (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Spawn - In The Demon's Hand (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20001001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Time Stalkers (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Time Stalkers</name>
		<desc>You are walking down a lonely country road, thinking about a girl when suddenly you are attacked. You fend him off with your sword, he runs.  You are Sword the mighty warrior, so you give chase and find yourself, eventually, in a land that is a quiltwork of different cultures and styles. 

You have been selected to save this world.  As you complete each challenge,  another land is added to the core world.  As you progress,  you gain allies and eventually have up to 6 characters to use for your quests.  You can capture and build up monsters to assist you.  You can purchase and create weapons to defeat your foes.  You can even use credits gained in the VMU games to help in the development of your characters and dungeons.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Time Stalkers (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Time Stalkers (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Time Stalkers (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Climax</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2</name>
		<desc>Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2, known as ShutokÃ…  Battle 2 (Ã©Â¦â€“Ã©Æ’Â½Ã©Â«ËœÃ£Æ’ Ã£Æ’Ë†Ã£Æ’Â« 2) in Japan and Tokyo Highway Challenge 2 in Europe, is the sequel to Tokyo Xtreme Racer, which is also on the Sega Dreamcast. Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2 has been enhanced with better sound quality and graphics over its predecessor. The game managed to produce two more sequels. It is the last game in the series that was produced for Sega Dreamcast. Some of the game's mechanics were implemented into Daytona USA 2001.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crave Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Genki</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2</name>
		<desc>The sequel to the award winning PSX and N64 title, Tony Hawk 2 adds heaps of new tricks, as well as those from the original, and a complete roster of all the greatest skaters worldwide. Fly through some of the greatest skate parks in the world, or create your own, and share them with your mates. You can also create your own skater, with a choice of clothing and official skateboards. Improved graphics and a choice of alternative or hip-hop music add to the endless options and full on action.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Neversoft</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Unreal Tournament (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Unreal Tournament</name>
		<desc>Unreal Tournament is completely different to Unreal - it's now mainly based on multiplayer, like Quake 3.   At the beginning, you have to play classic deathmatch rounds. After you have successfully won some of them, a new game mode becomes available, domination. In domination there are about 3 or 4 different areas scattered around the map to be controlled by your team. For a certain amount of seconds you control one area, a point is added to your score. The more areas you control, the faster your team's score rises. When you or the other team reaches a certain score, the game is over. The 3rd mode is called capture the flag, every team has a flag to defend and tries to capture the other team's flag to score a point.   The 4th game mode is probably the most innovative one, it's called assault. These are real missions, like you have to attack an enemy base and destroy something in it. Again, there are two teams, the defenders and the attackers. You have to complete the mission in a certain time, like 5 or 10 minutes. If you were successful, your team has to defend this time and the other team attacks. But the attacking team now only has as much time as you needed to attack.  All these modes are either playable in single or multiplayer mode. If playing alone, you have a large menu with orders you can give your bots.  Also, all weapons were redesigned, and some new ones are added.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Unreal Tournament (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Unreal Tournament (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Unreal Tournament (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20010629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Secret Level</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toy Commander.chd</path>
		<name>Toy Commander</name>
		<desc>Some of the greatest adventures that kids have growing up occur in their imaginations as they play with their toys.  Toy Commander is a game that attempts to capture these adventures in an interactive, three dimensional world. The player's perspective is that of the toy vehicles that inhabit a house. The various gameplay areas are all based on rooms in this giant house.   Gameplay in Toy Commander is mission based.  In each mission, you control one or more toy vehicles to accomplish certain objectives. The objectives in each mission vary widely.  In some missions, you must drive an army truck and shoot things, in some you fly helicopters to pick up and drop off objects, and in some you must race against computer controlled vehicles.   There is a story line that ties together the missions in single player mode. A coalition of old toys has started a rebellion against the new toys in the house. An evil Teddy Bear, the Toy Commander, is leading this rebellion.  It's your job to stop him. In each mission, your basic goal is to complete the task in as short a time as possible.  If you meet a certain time goal, the mission is completed.  By completing 4 missions, you get to challenge the Boss character in the room.  If you successfully destroy the boss, he will assist you in the final fight against the Toy Commander.  In addition to the single player mode, there is a 4-player simultaneous deathmatch mode.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Toy Commander.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Toy Commander.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Toy Commander.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>No ClichÃ©</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TrickStyle (USA).chd</path>
		<name>TrickStyle</name>
		<desc>The game is set in the future and based around the sport of Hoverboarding. The player can race or do stunts through metropolis versions of London, Tokyo, and Manhattan Island, or in a massive practice arena called the Velodrome.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/TrickStyle (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/TrickStyle (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/TrickStyle (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Resident Evil Code: Veronica</name>
		<desc>Three months after the events of Resident Evil 2, Claire Redfield is still looking for her brother Chris. She infiltrates Umbrella Corporation's headquarters in Paris, where she is captured and knocked out. When she comes to, she finds herself in a prison on a remote island. Freed by a friendly guard, Claire faces several problems. Not only is the island under attack by an unknown assailant, but there has been another outbreak of the T-Virus and the island is crawling with zombies and other mutated creatures. Claire not only has to face the undead, but also the commander of the base, a mad aristocrat with family ties to the origins of Umbrella Corporation and the T-Virus. And escaping from the island is only the beginning of Claire's ordeals.  Code: Veronica continues the survival horror gameplay of its predecessors: the protagonist explores the surroundings, fighting monsters and solving puzzles. However, Code: Veronica is the first game in the series to do away with pre-rendered backgrounds, using a fully polygonal 3D engine instead, which allows for features such as real-time lighting and camera movement. Still, such movements are only used sparingly, and the use of perspective is mostly unchanged from earlier installments: the camera automatically switches to different static angles, showing protagonist, monsters and rooms from different spooky viewpoints.  Most of the weapons from the earlier games make return appearances: knife, handguns, shotgun, grenade launcher and crossbow are all featured. There are also new weapons including a sniper rifle, an AK-47 and several guns only found in pairs, which can be used to target two enemies at the same time. Several weapons upgrades can also be found.  Similar to the earlier games, the player will not only control Claire, but also two other characters: Claire's fellow prisoner Steve, and her brother Chris. </desc>
		<image>./mixart/Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Resident Evil - Code - Veronica (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./+Start Reicast.sh</path>
		<name>+Start Reicast</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<hidden>true</hidden>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./102 Dalmatians (USA).chd</path>
		<name>102 Dalmatians - Puppies to the Rescue</name>
		<desc>The game itself follows the films' storyline loosely. The player can choose the role of one of two dalmatians, Oddball or Domino, who are out in the backyard looking for treasure. It is not long before the player realizes that a toy found buried in a park was made at one of Cruella de Vil's toy factories; this alludes to the fact that Cruella's toy sales are down, which ultimately leads to the problem in the storyline. Facing financial ruin from lack of sales, Cruella sets an evil plan in motion - to reprogram her toys to capture any pets in sight. Oddball and Domino are the only puppies in their family who have not been captured when they return from the park. Their parents, Dottie and Dipstick, set out to rescue their puppies, commanding Oddball and Domino to stay home and 'be good.' The puppies do not listen, and are soon out on their biggest adventure yet - to save their brothers and sisters, and their parents who are captured along the way.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/102 Dalmatians (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/102 Dalmatians (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/102 Dalmatians (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Crystal Dynamics</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shikigami no Shiro II (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Shikigami no Shiro II</name>
		<desc>The Shikigami No Shiro II Deluxe Edition includes the following items:  1. Castle Shikigami 2 2. A soundtrack CD 3. Trading cards 4. A telephone card (Sega Direct release only) </desc>
		<image>./mixart/Shikigami no Shiro II (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Shikigami no Shiro II (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Shikigami no Shiro II (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20040325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alfa System</developer>
		<publisher>Alfa System</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Marvel vs. Capcom 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Marvel Vs. Capcom 2 - New Age Of Heroes</name>
		<desc>Marvel vs. Capcom 2: New Age of Heroes is the sequel to the 2D fighting game Marvel vs. Capcom: Clash of Super Heroes. 

The game allows you to tag in all three players (instead of two, while the third is only used for special attacks, in the predecessor).

There are now up to 56 characters to use (most you have to unlock), including new characters like Jill Valentine from Resident Evil and Tron Bonn from Mega Man Legends.

Another new gameplay feature allows your team mates to come in during battle and give you a little health boost. This helps in lasting the distance in Survival mode, but they can also be hit by on coming attacks from the enemy.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Marvel vs. Capcom 2 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Marvel vs. Capcom 2 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Marvel vs. Capcom 2 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Fighter 3tb (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Virtua Fighter 3tb</name>
		<desc>Virtua Fighter 3tb (Team Battle) is a port of the arcade game Virtua Fighter 3 to the Dreamcast. The "tb" adds a team battle mode which was not present in the coin-op. For those that do not know, the Virtua Fighter series is your classic beat-em-up, with a bunch of characters all trying to kick, punch, throw and body slam the bejesus out of each other. Each of the characters has over a hundred possible moves and the game plays very faithfully to the original. The game features interesting arena to fight in which are more like real locations in they are not flat and some parts can be broken away during the match. </desc>
		<image>./mixart/Virtua Fighter 3tb (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Virtua Fighter 3tb (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Virtua Fighter 3tb (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genki</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WWF Royal Rumble (USA).chd</path>
		<name>WWF Royal Rumble</name>
		<image>./mixart/WWF Royal Rumble (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/WWF Royal Rumble (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/WWF Royal Rumble (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Plasma Sword - Nightmare of Bilstein (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Plasma Sword: Nightmare of Bilstein</name>
		<desc>Plasma Sword - Nightmare of Bilstein is the successor of Star Gladiator released for Playstation. Like it's predecessor it was first released on Arcade before ported to the Dreamcast.  The game features 22 anime-like Characters in a 3-dimensional futuristic world - except for the backgrounds and the menus, which are plain 2D-bitmaps without a lot of movement. The stages are unlimited in all directions, so it's not possible to fall of the edge. The speciality of this game are the so called "plasma moves", visually very appealing special moves filling the complete screen which can be executed when you have collected enough "plasma power". Despite of the 22 characters there are only 11 different move layouts, as one layout is shared by two characters. </desc>
		<image>./mixart/Plasma Sword - Nightmare of Bilstein (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Plasma Sword - Nightmare of Bilstein (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Plasma Sword - Nightmare of Bilstein (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20000331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Striker 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Virtua Striker 2</name>
		<desc>It's here, Virtua Striker 2 V2000.1 has come to Dreamcast in all its arcade-perfect glory. Play any of the new modes - including 'Ranking' and 'Leagues' - or just sit back and enjoy the original arcade mode from the comfort of your armchair. You can save the best goal on your VM unit and use it when your competing in two-player mode.   Football has never looked so good and felt so right... you can almost taste the pie and Bovril at half time. </desc>
		<image>./mixart/Virtua Striker 2 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Virtua Striker 2 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Virtua Striker 2 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aqua GT (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Aqua Gt</name>
		<desc>Aqua GT is powerboat racing game. It features three modes: Championship, Arcade and Two-player.

Championship mode is the main single player game, where you advance through the Bronze, Silver and Gold Championships. In the Arcade gameplay mode you have to beat the clock. In two-player split screen mode you go head to head against another player.

There are 5 boats to choose from, and you can unlock another 15 while progressing through the game. All boat vary in speed, acceleration and handling.

The tracks are set in canals of major cities, like London, Amsterdam and New York. Each track has a high or low tide, and you can race at day time or during the night time.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Aqua GT (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Aqua GT (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Aqua GT (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20001202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>East Point Software</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat Gold (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat Gold</name>
		<desc>The first and only Mortal Kombat title to make onto the Dreamcast console, Mortal Kombat Gold offered players a carbon-copy of the arcade edition of Mortal Kombat 4, along with additional features and characters never before included in the arcade game.

Using the exact same engine found in Mortal Kombat 4, the game performs flawlessly on the Dreamcast platform, while also running at a higher resolution than its arcade counterpart.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mortal Kombat Gold (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mortal Kombat Gold (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mortal Kombat Gold (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skies of Arcadia (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Skies of Arcadia</name>
		<desc>Port of Midway's arcade boat-racer. The premise is non-existent, you simply rev up the engines and go on 13 water courses set in Antarctica, the far east, the Greek isles, etc. on different types of futuristic boats. Races use the usual arcade checkpoint system and scattered across the courses you'll find an assortment of power-ups and upgrades like nitro boosters.   Graphics are entirely 3D with reflective water effects and realistic bouncing and bucking in the boats. Multiplayer competitions are supported for 2 players on the PlayStation version.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Skies of Arcadia (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Skies of Arcadia (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Skies of Arcadia (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.80</rating>
		<releasedate>20000908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Overworks</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>RPG</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jet Grind Radio (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Jet Grind Radio</name>
		<desc>Jet Set Radio is a video game developed by Smilebit and published by Sega on June 29, 2000. Jet Set Radio was developed for the Dreamcast, although a 2D version of the game was later released for Game Boy Advance and was developed by Vicarious Visions, and published by THQ. Its sequel, Jet Set Radio Future was released 2 years later for the Xbox after SEGA became a software-based company. The game is known for spearheading the use of cel-shaded graphics in video games.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Jet Grind Radio (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Jet Grind Radio (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jet Grind Radio (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Smilebit</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Demolition (USA)[DCRES].chd</path>
		<name>Star Wars - Demolition</name>
		<desc>A demoliton derby in the Star Wars universe.  Essentially, Vigilante 8 with Star Wars vehicles.  Use anything from a Swoop Bike to a mind controlled Rancor.  You can even play as Boba Fett.  Boards include all of the worlds visited in the Star Wars movies  (Tatooine, Hoth, Death Star, Endor, Dagobah, etc...).  Single player, multi player, and tournament modes are available. </desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - Demolition (USA)[DCRES].png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - Demolition (USA)[DCRES].mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - Demolition (USA)[DCRES].png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Tennis 2.chd</path>
		<name>Tennis 2K2</name>
		<desc>Sequel to the original game which was released two years prior.    The games graphics have been improved, and there is a greater roster of players to choose from. The most noteworthy addition is that of female players, such as Monica Seles and Venus and Serena Williams. You cannot however play as a male against a female.    The gameplay is a lot faster than the original. The players you control move a lot faster, as do the AI computer players. Less diving, but more getting at shots that go behind you and over the shoulder shots.    The game modes from the original are the same, featuring tournament mode, where you play against the pros; exhibition mode for a one-on-one, best-out-of-three game; and world tour mode which now features the option of creating and customizing your own player. Build you player up, buy equipment and hire pros to play in doubles matches with you.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Virtua Tennis 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Virtua Tennis 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Virtua Tennis 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20011123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./San Francisco RUSH 2049 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>San Francisco RUSH 2049</name>
		<desc>Unlike the previous San Francisco Rush titles, this racing game is set in the future. The same rules apply though, get to the finish before everyone else while avoiding massive crashes and taking as many shortcuts as possible.  Along with the usual race style, you now have the ability to fly, allowing you even more speed, stunts and shortcuts to the finish line. While the tracks themselves include moving ramps and switches to other shortcuts.  Modes include time trials, stunt mode including unique track designs to get the most out of your stunts, and a four player 'Battlematch' mode that adds weapons to the action.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/San Francisco RUSH 2049 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/San Francisco RUSH 2049 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/San Francisco RUSH 2049 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000906T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soul Calibur (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Soul Calibur</name>
		<desc>A fighting game to end all fighting games.  A sequel to Soul Blade, Soul Calibur takes place in a time inspired by a mixture of 16th-century ancient China and oriental medieval fantasies and legends.  

All characters have weapons and distinct fighting styles with over 100 individual moves per character.  In addition to high, mid, and low attacks, characters can hold/throw, block, and perform special attacks -- one or more of which is deemed "un-blockable" and must be avoided by ducking, jumping, or rotating around your attacker. 

In addition to several locales in which to fight and alternate models/costumes per character, the Dreamcast conversion of Soul Calibur contains many additional features over the arcade coin-op, including hidden characters and locales, a campaign mode, and tournament mode.  There is also a "museum" where you can view character profiles and view motion-captured martial arts demonstrations.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Soul Calibur (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Soul Calibur (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Soul Calibur (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ikaruga v1.002 (2002)(ESP)(NTSC)(JP)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Ikaruga</name>
		<desc>Vertical shoot-em-up ported from the Naomi Arcade version. Ikaruga is more or less a sequel to Radiant Silvergun by Treasure, on the Sega Saturn.  Based on a two-colors system, the player has to switch between the black &amp; white sides of his ship during gameplay. The black side is immune to black enemy bullets which it consider as bonus, and dies on impact with a white enemy bullets. Your own black bullets damages white enemies twice as more as white bullets. And vice-versa for the white side. Those properties makes a balance between protecting yourself well and killing enemies fast.   This aspect, combined with specific enemy patterns and a combo system makes Ikaruga an original shoot-em-up with a dose of strategy.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ikaruga v1.002 (2002)(ESP)(NTSC)(JP)[!].png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ikaruga v1.002 (2002)(ESP)(NTSC)(JP)[!].mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ikaruga v1.002 (2002)(ESP)(NTSC)(JP)[!].png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Entertainment Software Publishing</developer>
		<publisher>Treasure</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker.chd</path>
		<name>18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker</name>
		<desc>The main purpose of the game is to make it to the finish line with the truck's cargo. Players are given a set amount of time, but can ram into special vans that will add three seconds to the timer. There are several characters to choose from, each with a unique truck and attributes.    The game starts out in Key West and players travel across the United States, ending in San Francisco. After Stage 1, the game gives the player a choice of trailer. One trailer is harder to haul, but provides a bigger payoff while the other choice is easier to haul but provides a smaller payoff. Money is deducted from the total when the trailer is hit. Players can sound the truck's horn to make other cars on the road yield and slipstream behind large vehicles to gain a momentary speed boost.    In addition to the time limit, players also compete with the "Lizard Tail", a rival trucker. Crossing the finish line before the Lizard Tail yields additional money. In between levels, players can park the truck in a mini game to earn more cash.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker.png</image>
		<video>./snap/18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20010518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bangai-O (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Bangai-O</name>
		<desc>Ever wanted to just unleash the ultimate weapon? Blow up 500 enemies at once? Cause the ultimate amount of mayhem ever? In true Treasure fashion...you just got that power!  As the pilots of the Bangaioh mech, you've got to stop a mad group from taking over the world by giving them a little dose of insane destruction. Wanna just be crazy and let them kill you? Go ahead...just hit that trigger before it happens...  The Nintendo 64 version was only released in Japan. The Dreamcast version exists in the U.S. and Europe.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Bangai-O (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Bangai-O (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bangai-O (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010321T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>Conspiracy</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phantasy Star Online v2.chd</path>
		<name>Phantasy Star Online Ver. 2</name>
		<desc>The world's first online console RPG gets an update with PSO Ver. 2. New items and weapons, new online games and play modes, a Dressing Room, new areas to explore, and the Ultimate Difficulty mode have been added. You can also bring in your PSO characters, modify them in the Dressing Room, and attempt Ultimate Mode and strive to reach Level 200!  PSO Ver. 2 functions as a stand-alone game, as well as an add-on. You don't need to have owned PSO in order to play. </desc>
		<image>./mixart/Phantasy Star Online v2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Phantasy Star Online v2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Phantasy Star Online v2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tee Off (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tee Off</name>
		<desc>One of the few golf games for the DC, with a cartoony style. Contains arcade mode, tournaments, five different courses and 15 characters (11 unlockable). Lots of different equipment (balls and clubs mostly) and even a futuristic cyber mini golf game are thrown in.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tee Off (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tee Off (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tee Off (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grandia II (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Grandia II</name>
		<desc>Ryudo has been hired to protect a young priestess who must participate in a ceremony to halt the encroaching rebirth of Valmar, the God of Darkness. Embroiled between the forces of good and evil, Ryudo must follow his destiny and save the people he detests so much.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grandia II (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Grandia II (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grandia II (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Record of Lodoss War (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Record of Lodoss War</name>
		<desc>In this game the player takes the role of an ancient warrior who has been brought to life by the benevolent wizard Wart. It seems that the evil goddess Kardis is about to be resurrected by her faithful servants. The only way to stop them is to gather famous heroes from Lodoss War universe and to defeat the evil ones in a battle.  Record of Lodoss War is quite similar to  Diablo gameplay-wise. It is an action RPG which is heavily combat-oriented. You can directly control only the main hero, while the legendary heroes who join him on the quest are controlled by the AI. As you go through the game you level up, tweak your items with the great Ancients system, and gain new spells. It is also possible to froge weapons and to imbue them with runes. As your adventures into the surrounding land go on, you can return to your HQ, the Goblin Fortress, and get much needed healing and healing potions (free of charge).</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Record of Lodoss War (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Record of Lodoss War (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Record of Lodoss War (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin</developer>
		<publisher>Swing! Entertainement</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dead Or Alive 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dead or Alive 2 Shokai Gentei Ban</name>
		<desc>The arcade conversion adds an improved tag feature, with new stadiums to fight in, new character moves to play with, and plenty of windows, walls and ledges to fall over and crash through. Unlike Tekken Tag Tournament, however, DOA2 also includes a single player mode, a dodge button (allowing you to move left and right away from attacks), and multi-level arenas.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dead Or Alive 2 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dead Or Alive 2 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dead Or Alive 2 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dynamite Cop! (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dynamite Cop</name>
		<desc>Pirates have kidnapped the President's daughter and are holding her on a hijacked cruise ship. Now it's up to an elite police force to get them back, using whatever means necessary. The action takes place on both the cruise ship and the pirate's island hideaway.  You play as one of three cops, in this beat-em up fighting game from Sega.  Dynamite Cop features similar gameplay to Die Hard Arcade. As your character enters an area, you have to beat up everyone there.  Once they are gone, you continue to the next area.  To help you there are many weapons, such as guns, knives, pepper spray, chairs, and bread.  Bread?  Yes, you can use pretty much anything as a weapon. </desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dynamite Cop! (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dynamite Cop! (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dynamite Cop! (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ecco The Dolphin (USA).chd</path>
		<name>ECCO the Dolphin - Defender of the Future</name>
		<desc>Hundreds of years in the future, mankind and dolphins live peacefully together and share the earth. Dolphins, who are much more intelligent than they seem, act as the earth's caretakers, while dolphins and humans explore the galaxy. An alien force, known as the Foe, seeks to end this happy existence. The Foe damages the Earth's defense system, and alters history for the worse. One extraordinary dolphin, Ecco, must travel through time to set things right.  Ecco is a 3d underwater adventure game. There are more than 25 aquatic environments to explore. Ecco must communicate with other ocean creatures and learn to manipulate his environment if he is to succeed in defeating the Foe. </desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ecco The Dolphin (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ecco The Dolphin (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ecco The Dolphin (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000816T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Appaloosa</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4 Wheel Thunder (USA).chd</path>
		<name>4 Wheel Thunder</name>
		<desc>4 Wheel Thunder is a Racing game published by Midway released on May 4th, 2002 for the SEGA Dreamcast.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/4 Wheel Thunder (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/4 Wheel Thunder (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/4 Wheel Thunder (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flashback HD.cdi</path>
		<name>'â˜†Flashback HD - The Quest for Identity</name>
		<desc>FlashBack HD: Quest for Identity developed by Delphine Software is back and looking better on the Sega Dreamcast! Quest for identity is the 1st game in the series with the sequels "Another World" and "Fade to Black" out this month on the Dreamcast! Pulling together the work from the 1995 PC release, a new animated opening even includes the never released Sega Megadrive Japanese version with English support!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Flashback - The Quest for Identity HD.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Flashback - The Quest for Identity HD.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Flashback - The Quest for Identity HD.png</marquee>
		<rating>9.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Josh</developer>
		<publisher>Josh</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daytona USA (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Daytona USA</name>
		<desc>Just like the arcade version, pick one of three tracks (beginner, advanced, or expert) and either automatic or standard transmission. A pounding music soundtrack kicks in as you are slapped into your car to await the green light. The game offers both a traditional arcade mode with checkpoint time splits and a special PC mode that pits you against the other cars over different race distances. The PC mode also offers more car choices, with a variety of speed, acceleration, and grip characteristics. It even rewards successful players (meaning those finishing first, second, or third in the difficult setting) by offering up to ten more upgraded cars to drive. Once underway, the goal is to work from last to first as smoothly and quickly as possible </desc>
		<image>./mixart/Daytona USA (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Daytona USA (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Daytona USA (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F355 Challenge - Passione Rossa (PAL).chd</path>
		<name>F355 Challenge</name>
		<desc>Get behind the wheel of one of the most worlds most prestigious cars, the F355 Ferrari, in this conversion of Sega's arcade game.  F355 features a number of game modes: the Arcade mode which is the same as the checkpoint arcade version; Championship mode where you race a total of 6 races for the combined highest score; Single play which is the same as Arcade mode but with no time limit; Versus play with a two player split screen; and Network Race where you can connect to the Internet and race a time attack against other players ghost cars.  The courses that are available to race on are Motegi, short and long versions of Suzuka, Monza, Sugo, Long Beach, Atlanta Motor Speedway, Nurburgring (GP track), Laguna Seca, Sepang, and Fiorano (Ferrari's test track).   The game features 3 levels of difficulty. There are also four Assist functions - Stability Control for cornering, Traction Control from the engine to the tires, Anti Lock Brake System to keep the tires from locking during braking and Intelligent Brake System for braking before corners so beginners can concentrate on steering.  You can also connect to the Internet and register your driver data. </desc>
		<image>./mixart/F355 Challenge - Passione Rossa (PAL).png</image>
		<video>./snap/F355 Challenge - Passione Rossa (PAL).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/F355 Challenge - Passione Rossa (PAL).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Headhunter (Europe).m3u</path>
		<name>Headhunter</name>
		<desc>After awakening from a coma in a sterile hospital room, Jack Wade realizes that his memories, his identity, and even his mind have all been stolen. In order to regain what he has mysteriously lost, Jack must embark on a shadowy quest that puts his headhunting skills to the test. As Jack or his accomplice Angela Stern, you must use stealth tactics or your arsenal of weapons to fight through seedy biker hangouts, gas-filled shopping malls, and futuristic laboratories.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Headhunter (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Headhunter (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Headhunter (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Amuze</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC (USA).chd</path>
		<name>NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC</name>
		<desc>NBA Showtime: NBA on NBC is a descendant of the original NBA Jam, and is created by some of the key team members. The game follows in the footsteps of NFL Blitz, featuring the option to save personal records and a cheat code system operated by pressing a sequence of buttons. It also features unlock-able characters, including NBA team mascots, and the "On-Fire" option that defines Midway's sports games. Players are able to perform special moves such as the alley-oop, the spin move, and the double dunk.  The game also features a Create-a-Player mode that allows custom players to have tweaked abilities by winning matches. </desc>
		<image>./mixart/NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NFL Blitz 2000 v2.000 (1999)(Midway)(NTSC)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>NFL Blitz 2000</name>
		<desc>New edition of Midway's "NFL Jam" action/sports game where the emphasis is on bone-crushing action rather than sport simulation.  Additions this year come in the form of a season mode, a simpler passing system based on preset buttons (gone is the "aiming" mechanism) as well as a limited yet functional play-book editor.  Also included are new audible calls and voice-overs, smoother animations and new stadiums to play in.  Supports multiplayer gameplay of up to 4 players in one single machine! (two on keyboard, two on gamepads).</desc>
		<image>./mixart/NFL Blitz 2000 v2.000 (1999)(Midway)(NTSC)(US)[!].png</image>
		<video>./snap/NFL Blitz 2000 v2.000 (1999)(Midway)(NTSC)(US)[!].mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/NFL Blitz 2000 v2.000 (1999)(Midway)(NTSC)(US)[!].png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AvalancheÂ Software</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Tennis (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Power Smash</name>
		<desc>Imagine how a tennis player feels when he enters the arena, the crowd is cheering, the atmosphere electric, the adrenalin rushes...  Well now you can with Virtua tennis, the most lifelike and playable tennis game ever! Play as one of eight licensed players and uncover the secret stars. As well as the traditional arcade mode you can play in the exhibition mode, with 4 player action via doubles play.  Once you've mastered those modes take on the world in the world circuit mode, with unique training games, diffrent challenges and shops to buy clothing, equipment, stages and playing partners.   Virtua Tennis, so realistic you can almost taste the strawberries and cream.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Virtua Tennis (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Virtua Tennis (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Virtua Tennis (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shenmue (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Shenmue</name>
		<desc>Shenmue is a Action/Adventure game published by SEGA released on November 7th, 2000 for the SEGA Dreamcast</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Shenmue (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Shenmue (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Shenmue (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20001206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silver (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Silver</name>
		<desc>An RPG set in a medieval land where all the women have been kidnapped and it is up to you to get them back. What starts as a mission to save the women soon turns into a battle against good and evil to the death.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Silver (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Silver (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Silver (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure-Role playing games</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sturmwind.cdi</path>
		<name>Sturmwind</name>
		<desc>You found the way in now find the way out! Survive 16 levels and even more big grumpy boss enemies</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sturmwind.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sturmwind.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sturmwind.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20130424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Redspotgames</developer>
		<publisher>Redspotgames</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fast Striker (2010)(NGDEV.TEAM).cdi</path>
		<name>Fast Striker</name>
		<desc>Fast Striker is an arcade-style vertical shooter with a science fiction setting. While the game is essentially 2D, the backgrounds consists of pre-rendered 3D graphics. This game features six stages with over 40 enemy types.    You can choose between 3 game modes (Novice, Original and Maniac) with different scoring systems. The modes differ, for example, in the set of available techniques. In comparison to the Novice mode, the Original mode features a shield to protect the ship, which can be activated for a short time, and holding the down the spread fire button will also shoot rockets after a few moments. Furthermore, the enemies are colored differently in Novice mode to make them more visible, and you collect golden stars as part of the scoring system. The Maniac mode adds some new ways to get higher scores. For example, the distance between your ship and an enemy influences the score: you get a larger bonus the nearer you are to the enemy ship when you destroy it. Destroying many enemies in short time will also increase the number of awarded points. Last, you can activate a "Grind Mode" by focusing your ship's laser beam on a huge enemy. The beam will turn green after a while and then all destroyed enemies will give a higher score.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fast Striker (2010)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fast Striker (2010)(NGDEV.TEAM).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fast Striker (2010)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>NG:Dev.Team</developer>
		<publisher>NG:Dev.Team</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GunLord (2012)(NGDEV.TEAM).cdi</path>
		<name>Gunlord</name>
		<desc>Gunlord is a Eurostyle Platformer with emphasis on exploring huge worlds and blasting off enemies. This game features 8 stages of exciting 2D game play with over 45 unique enemy types. Blast yourself through giant landscapes, explore caverns and reveal all secrets!!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/GunLord (2012)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</image>
		<video>./snap/GunLord (2012)(NGDEV.TEAM).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/GunLord (2012)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20120621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NG:Dev.Team</developer>
		<publisher>NG:Dev.Team</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Fighter Scrolling-Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Last Hope - Pink Bullets (2011)(NGDEV.TEAM).cdi</path>
		<name>Last Hope - Pink Bullets</name>
		<desc>The evil empire is rushing at light-speed across the galaxies, heading towards Mother Earth. Barely 24 hours ago, they penetrated the last defence line of our galaxy, the Arsion Laser Belt. Millions of innocent people perished in outer space colonies. 70% of our fleet was destroyed during first contact. Our intelligence has now extrapolated their arrival within six days. Conventional weapons cannot stop them. Our last hope is in your hands: The Z-42 Warpstar. Warp into their territories and destroy their leader before they reach Earth.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Last Hope - Pink Bullets (2011)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Last Hope - Pink Bullets (2011)(NGDEV.TEAM).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Last Hope - Pink Bullets (2011)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20090904T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NG:Dev.Team</developer>
		<publisher>NG:Dev.Team</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal-Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Neo XYX (2014)(NGDEV.TEAM).cdi</path>
		<name>Neo Xyx</name>
		<desc>NEO XYX is early 90is style maniac shooting game. Fast and intense.nnnnGame Features:nnnn    6 stages with varied and colorful settingsnn    6 endbossesnn    5 midbossesnn    16-bit hand-drawn graphics (dot graphics)nn    Switchable between vertical (TATE) and horizontal controls (YOKO)nn    The HUD/score/lives/bombs etc. switch between TATE and YOKO too.nn    Maniac shooting gamnn    Professional printed CD</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Neo XYX (2014)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Neo XYX (2014)(NGDEV.TEAM).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Neo XYX (2014)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20140217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NG:Dev.Team</developer>
		<publisher>NG:Dev.Team</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Volgarr the Viking.cdi</path>
		<name>Volgarr the Viking</name>
		<desc>Do you have what it takes to be the greatest Viking Barbarian Lord in the world? Return to the Golden Age of arcade gaming with all-new hardcore action experience that pulls no punches. Playing as Volgarr the Viking, use your sword and spear to slaughter your foes in bloody combat. Battle Gigantic bosses in every world and find secrets that lead to unknown paths. Holding onto Volgarr's gear is key; his very life depends on it.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Volgarr the Viking.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Volgarr the Viking.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Volgarr the Viking.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20150424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
</gameList>
