<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>MSX2</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game id="97685" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Aleste (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Aleste</name>
		<desc>The sequel to Aleste 2.It was released as a free game in Compile's now defunct WOOMB magazine. It is also known as Aleste Special, because it was released in the Disc Station 4 Aku Gau disc in Autumn.

Unlike Aleste 1, you are not controlling a spaceship, but instead you're controlling a robot. However, like Aleste, you can shoot enemies, enemies can shoot you, collect power ups, and defeat bosses at the end of a level. However, new to this game is the ability to jump over holes in the ground. This adds a new challenge to the game. In some levels, there are even obstacles like cars that you have to avoid. Power ups range from one that clones yourself and can fire lasers with you, one that replaces your default laser with shurikens. One replaces your default weapon and instead shoots red targets that go in a zig-zag. This laser has a possiblity of shooting enemies. The kinds of power-ups are marked by the color of their box-containers and the Japanese letter on them.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Compile</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C29EDD84</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Aleste (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Aleste (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Aleste (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94511" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Alpha Roid (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Alpha Roid</name>
		<desc>Alpha Roid is a simple but great combination of a shump and a fighting game. 

After flying through space you must perform hand-to-hand combat with an equally determined enemy in order to get your weapon upgrades.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pony</developer>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon Inc.</publisher>
		<hash>4EF7C4E7</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Alpha Roid (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Alpha Roid (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Alpha Roid (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97727" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./AshGuine - Densetsu no Seisenshi (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>AshGuine</name>
		<desc>The evil Banutracus had destroyed the great civilization of the planet Nepenthus and brought it down to a primitive state. War broke out between the planet's humble Eletrian people and Banutracus's barbarous Cooligan invaders. After a long struggle, the Eletrians got united under the powerful leadership of one they called the father and managed to obtain a momentary peace. Howerver, when Banutracus returned to his planet he killed the father and re-established his hold. One Cooligan Gea saw the evil nature of Banutracus and escaped with the father's only daughter Neshah to one of the great ruined Eletrian cities. There, they had a son. When the boy grew to be a strong young man, one of the Cooligan soldiers discovered their hideout and killed his escaped parents. From that day, the boy swore vengeance on Banutracus and to eventually restore peace to the planet.?</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bit²</developer>
		<publisher>Panasoft</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3CB34EFB</hash>
		<image>./mixart/AshGuine - Densetsu no Seisenshi (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/AshGuine - Densetsu no Seisenshi (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/AshGuine - Densetsu no Seisenshi (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95466" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Grog's Revenge (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>B.C.'s Quest for Tires II - Grog's Revenge</name>
		<desc>B.C. II: Grog's Revenge is a 1984 video game by Sierra On-Line for the Commodore 64, ColecoVision, and MSX. It is the sequel to B.C.'s Quest For Tires and is based on B.C., the newspaper comic strip by Johnny Hart.

The player controls Thor, a caveman, who rides a stone unicycle. Thor is searching for the "Meaning of Life" within several mountains.
The player must navigate through the mountains, collecting clams. Like the comic strip, they are used as money, in this case to pay the toll to another caveman, Peter, to access the next mountain.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Comptiq</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>5F74AE0E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Grog's Revenge (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grog's Revenge (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Grog's Revenge (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94596" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./B.C.'s Quest (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>B.C.'s Quest for Tires</name>
		<desc>B.C.'s Quest for Tires is a 1983 video game designed by Rick Banks and Michael Bate and published by Sierra On-Line. It was released for the Commodore 64, Atari 8-bit family, ColecoVision, ZX Spectrum, MSX, and Apple II. The game is based on the comic strip B.C. by Johnny Hart, with the title being a play on the title of the contemporaneous film Quest for Fire.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Toshiba-EMI</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9C9420D0</hash>
		<image>./mixart/B.C.'s Quest (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/B.C.'s Quest (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/B.C.'s Quest (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94601" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Back to the Future (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Back to the Future</name>
		<desc>In Back to the Future, 80s teen Marty McFly is mistakenly send 30 years into the past where he disrupts his own parents from meeting. Faced with extinction at the hands of a temporal paradox, Marty must find a way to reunite his future parents and make it back to his own time.

LJN's game differs completely from the computer versions, and plays as a literal race against time broken up by brief arcade minigames. In the main game, the player controls Marty in an overhead view as he runs down the streets of 1950s Hill Valley.  A collection of period-appropriate bad guys block his path, including bullies, hula hoop girls, bumblebees, and park benches.  The camera scrolls forward at a fixed speed, so the player must keep Marty on the move and away from obstacles. Hitting one causes Marty to fall and lose a life. The player must also collect clocks scattered on the street to stop Marty's photograph from fading away.  If it fades completely, Marty is erased from existence.

Street running sections lead to three minigames. In these, Marty must sling milkshakes at oncoming bullies, deflect kisses (shown as hearts) from his mother, and collect notes to rock out on stage at the high school dance. The final stage resembles the street sections, as the player must control the DeLorean time machine and collect enough energy to travel through time (shown as lightning bolts instead of clocks).</desc>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software Pty., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>LJN Toys, Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>DBDB64AC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Back to the Future (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Back to the Future (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Back to the Future (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94653" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Beam Rider (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Beamrider</name>
		<desc>Beamrider takes place above Earth's atmosphere, where a large alien shield called the Restrictor Shield surrounds the Earth. The player's objective is to clear the Shield's 99 sectors of alien craft while piloting the Beamrider ship. The Beamrider is equipped with a short-range laser lariat and a limited supply of torpedoes. The player is given three at the start of each sector.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>PONY CANNON</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1553E408</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Beam Rider (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Beam Rider (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Beam Rider (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94708" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomber King (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Bomber King</name>
		<desc>RoboWarrior takes place on an alien planet called Altile. The player operates a cyborg named ZED (Z-type Earth Defence). In the game, ZED raids Altile to fight the Xantho empire and destroy its leader, Xur. ZED deploys bombs to clear a path through rocks, walls, and forests, while killing enemies and collecting items. Some gameplay elements resemble those of Bomberman (1983).

RoboWarrior comprises five level formats. In one, the player must obtain a key before the time limit expires. In another, the key is unavailable until the player acquires a crystal or chalice. Some levels are cast in darkness, rendering obstructions invisible unless the player has a lit lamp. Still other levels are mazes in which a player must find and blast-through weak points in walls to proceed. Periodically, a player engages a boss level.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<hash>8CF0E6C0</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Bomber King (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bomber King (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bomber King (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94711" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomber Man Special (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Bomber Man Special</name>
		<desc>Bomberman was a robot in a bomb making factory who longed for his freedom. Rumors circulated that escaping to the surface would allow the robot to become human. Getting out would be the trick. Each room is inhabited by monsters that must be neutralized and the exit itself hidden underneath bricks.

The first of the Bomberman series, Bomberman is a single-player game with a top down view and simplistic controls. In fact, in addition to movement, the player only has a single ability: placing bombs. Each bomb explodes into a cross-shaped blast (four directions) which can destroy either enemies or blocks. Power-ups may be found to increase the size of the blast, place additional bombs, increase the speed of the Bomberman or to walk through walls. The goal on each level is to destroy all enemies and escape through the exit before the time limit is up. Hitting the exit with a bomb blast releases more enemies which must also be destroyed.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<hash>042AD44D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Bomber Man Special (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bomber Man Special (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bomber Man Special (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94709" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomber Man (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Bomber Man</name>
		<desc>Bomber Man (çå¼¾ç· Bakudan Otoko) is a maze-based video game developed by Hudson Soft and released only for home computers. While it is often overlooked, it is a distinct title and the first entry in the Bomberman series. The MSX and ZX Spectrum versions were localized in Europe as Eric and the Floaters.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<hash>9A5AEF05</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Bomber Man (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bomber Man (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bomber Man (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94760" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bruce Lee (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Bruce Lee</name>
		<desc>The late martial arts hero features in this platform game, with the aim of reaching a wizard in an underground lair, defeat of whom can offer him untold wealth. 

In each area you must collect the many strategically-placed lanterns before exiting through the newly-revealed passageway. Some rooms also have escalator-type sections to run along, and the standard (although slightly illogical in this context) ladders.  There are 20 areas to be completed.

On the way, you'll fight two enemies - a ninja and a green sumo warrior named Yamo. You can defeat them by punching, kicking, dropping on their heads or luring them into hazardous terrain, or even by making them accidentally hit each other. Even after they are killed, however, they keep coming back for more after a few seconds. The game also allows a second player to take control of Yamo.

There are lots of hazards to avoid by either walking round or jumping - walls of electrical charge and exploding bushes for example.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Datasoft, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Comptiq</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>A20B196D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Bruce Lee (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bruce Lee (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bruce Lee (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94791" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cabbage Patch Kids (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Cabbage Patch Kids</name>
		<desc>Cabbage Patch Kids is a 1984 action/platform game based on the Cabbage Patch Kids franchise. It is the first and only game in the Cabbage Patch Kids Adventures series.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>057D2790</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Cabbage Patch Kids (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cabbage Patch Kids (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Cabbage Patch Kids (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94800" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Candoo Ninja (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Candoo Ninja</name>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mass Tael</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B6AB6786</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Candoo Ninja (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Candoo Ninja (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Candoo Ninja (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94830" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Castle Excellent (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Castle Excellent</name>
		<desc>The puzzle and platform game Castle Excellent is a sequel to The Castle. In Castle Excellent you control a prince that has to save the princess again. 

To find your princess you have to explore the castle, which has 100 different rooms. Each room is a puzzle on its own as you have to avoid enemy knights, fat Tiroler men, hazardous objects and have to use objects to get to the next door.
In each room you have to collect keys and items like rings and gold bars. The keys may have different colors and only opens doors with the corresponding key color.

The main difference with the original The Castle game is that the castle rooms are completely redesigned and contain many new challenges. The game play has not changed.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ASCII Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>90F38029</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Castle Excellent (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Castle Excellent (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Castle Excellent (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94735" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Boulder Dash (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Champion Boulder Dash</name>
		<desc>You are Rockford, and you have to dig through monster infested caves in search of diamonds. In each level you must collect a certain number of these diamonds, in order to open a portal to the next stage. Enemies can be squashed by falling boulders, which are released when the ground below them is removed or they are pushed onto empty ground, but be careful because these can also squash you. In later levels, difficulty is increased by many puzzle elements and shorter time limits.

There are 16 levels to be completed and five different skill levels available, which affect the number of jewels which must be collected and the time limit.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>First Star Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Orpheus Ltd</publisher>
		<hash>A3A56524</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Boulder Dash (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Boulder Dash (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Boulder Dash (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97795" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Contra (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Contra</name>
		<desc>In the year 2631, a small meteorite has fallen into the Galuga archipelago, located 20km northeast off the coast of New Zealand. Two years later, a terrorist group known as Red Falcon has seized the island in preparation for an alien invasion. The earth's marines sent two members of their elite Contra unit, Bill Rizer and Lance Bean, to neutralize the terrorists.

As either Bill (player 1) or Lance (player 2), the player must get to the end of each stage, shooting everything in sight, while avoiding enemy fire themselves. The player can upgrade their standard-issue rifle into one of four different weapons, including the powerful spread shot.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>4E82660D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Contra (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Contra (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Contra (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95067" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Devil's Heaven (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Devil's Heaven</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Paxon</publisher>
		<hash>CE08F27D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Devil's Heaven (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Devil's Heaven (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Devil's Heaven (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95111" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragon Attack (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Attack</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<hash>A0FF8771</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dragon Attack (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dragon Attack (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dragon Attack (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97856" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragon Buster (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Buster</name>
		<desc>Originating in the arcades, Dragon Buster is an action platform game composed out of several large levels, each one containing various stages: a cave, a tower, a castle, etc. The player's goal in every level is to reach the final stage where the protagonist faces the level boss. There are often several ways to reach the final stages, and not all stages are necessary to visit. Equipped with a sword, the player character moves through platform stages, clearing them of diverse monsters, collecting power-ups and trying to stay in good health until the level boss, since it is impossible to heal between the stages. The hero's life meter (called "vitality" in the game) is the first introduction of such a feature to action games.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Namco Limited</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>49252882</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dragon Buster (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dragon Buster (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dragon Buster (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="185991" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragon Slayer II - Xanadu (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Slayer 2 - Xanadu</name>
		<desc>Xanadu was the name of the summer capital of the Mongolian-ruled Yuan Dynasty in 13th century China. The game, however, is set in a fantasy world, its Xanadu being mysterious ruins beneath a prosperous kingdom, where only the bravest adventurers dare to venture. The player takes the role of one of such explorers, who is sent by the king to discover the secrets hidden deep within the ruins.

Xanadu: Dragon Slayer II bears many similarities to the first Dragon Slayer, being a dungeon-crawling role-playing game with action combat, primarily revolving around exploration of vast underground mazes. Unlike the previous game, the exploration in Xanadu is conducted from a side-scrolling perspective. There are no platforming elements in the game, and action-based gameplay is confined to combat only. Like in its predecessor, attacking enemies involves simply "bumping" into them, gaining advantage by positioning the hero so that he faces the enemy.

Experience points are awarded for defeating enemies. There are two types of experience: fighter and magician, gained from attacking physically and casting spells, respectively. Weapons and armor also gain experience and level up, depending on the amount of time the protagonist equips them for. The main character must visit a temple in order to increase his level.

Money can be found in the dungeon or dropped by enemies, and later spent to purchase equipment and items in shops. The player must also regularly feed the hero, as he will get weak and eventually die without food. The game features a "karma" system, which keeps track of the alignment of the enemies killed by the protagonist. If he kills too many "good" enemies, temples might refuse to level him up.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Falcom</publisher>
		<hash>D640DEAF</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dragon Slayer II - Xanadu (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dragon Slayer II - Xanadu (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dragon Slayer II - Xanadu (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97872" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragon Slayer IV - Drasle Family (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Slayer 4 - Drasle Family</name>
		<desc>Long ago, an evil dragon named Keela was imprisoned inside a magical dungeon. However time has passed and the magic that sealed the dragon away is weakening. The Drasle family decides that it's time to destroy the dragon once and for all. However only one weapon is capable of doing this, the Dragon Slayer, which is itself sealed away by four magical crowns. The Drasle family decides to take on this quest, and will use every member of the family in order to accomplish it.
The player chooses a character from among five different members of the Drasle family. The choices are: Xemm the father and woodcutter, Mayna the magic-using mother, Roas the brave warrior son, Lyll the athletic daughter and Pochi the domesticated monster-pet. Each character has unique abilities (including attack and jumping abilities) and can only use certain items from those collected. Players can travel back to the Drasle household at any point to change characters.

The object of the game is to enter the large dungeon, itself divided into 5 areas, collecting a variety of items (which as mentioned, can only be used by particular characters) and use them to progress through the dungeon, defeating monsters. Power-ups dropped by monsters include gold, keys, health-restoring bread, magic-restoring potions and health-damaging poison. Gold can be spent on items and other power-ups that are available at various shops hidden inside the dungeon. The player must eventually defeat the four bosses guarding the crowns that seal the Dragon Slayer and then use that weapon to defeat the Kress.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Falcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>98095852</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dragon Slayer IV - Drasle Family (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dragon Slayer IV - Drasle Family (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dragon Slayer IV - Drasle Family (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97873" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragon Slayer Jr. - Romancia (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Slayer III - Romancia</name>
		<desc>This game exists in two editions, one for the MSX1 and one for the MSX2 with better graphics.

In Romancia: Dragon Slayer Jr., you are a young warrior whom the king sends on a mission to rescue a lost princess. You must leave the town and enter the dreadful monster-infested catacombs in order to complete your quest.

The game is a departure from Dragon Slayer RPG-oriented gameplay style. It tends more towards medieval-themed platformer action. The hero has hit points, can buy items and weapons, use magic, and stay in inns to recover health. However, instead of receiving experience points and becoming stronger, you simply must attack quicker (by bumping into your opponent on platform levels) and jump higher.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Nihon Falcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>17F9EE7F</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dragon Slayer Jr. - Romancia (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dragon Slayer Jr. - Romancia (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dragon Slayer Jr. - Romancia (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95122" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dragon Slayer (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Slayer</name>
		<desc>Dragon Slayer is commonly considered one of the progenitors of the action RPG genre. The premise is similar to Roguelikes: the player takes control of a knight who must fight his way through large overhead maze-like dungeons. Unlike roguelikes, the combat in the game is fully action-oriented: the player must approach the monster and "bump" into it in order to inflict damage, at the same time trying to avoid its blows. Combat takes place on the same screen as the exploration; monsters will also sometimes pursue the knight if he attempts to escape. Also contrary to roguelikes, none of the locations or items in the game is randomized.

The player can collect power stones and coins during the journey; the power stones increase the hero's strength, while the coins increase his hit points (health). Defeating enemies also yields experience points, which determine the amount of maximum HP the hero is able to receive. The knight is able to cast magic spells, though they are mostly used outside of combat, for example breaking walls, teleporting, or creating a map of the area.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Square Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6A515349</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dragon Slayer (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dragon Slayer (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95176" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Eggerland Mystery (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Eggerland Mystery</name>
		<desc>The Eggerland series consists of several puzzle games. You play Lolo, a blue ball-like character with eyes, arms, and legs. The story mainly deals with King Egger, the villain, who has captured princess Lala, who is similar to Lolo, only colored red. It is up to Lolo to rescue Lala by travelling through Egger's domain and solving the puzzle rooms laid out before him.
You must guide Lolo through a room of tiles and collect all of the Heart Framers in the room. Doing this opens up a Jewel Box, which contains an item. Successfully acquiring the contents of the Jewel Box will clear the room of all monsters and open the way to the next room(s). Luckily for you Lolo has a weapon: the Magic Shot. Two shots can be obtained by collecting certain Heart Framers.
There are other types of obstacles in the levels, as well, such as water and Emerald Framers (green blocks that Lolo may push around freely).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
		<hash>232B1050</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Eggerland Mystery (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Eggerland Mystery (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Eggerland Mystery (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95233" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./F-1 Spirit - The Way to Formula-1 (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>F-1 Spirit - The Way to Formula 1</name>
		<desc>F-1 Spirit: The Way To Formula-1 is a top down Formula One Racing game, developed and published by Konami, which was released for the MSX in Japan and Europe in 1987. The game engine is very similar to Konami's Road Fighter. It also features Konami's custom sound chip called Konami SCC (a five-channel chip that compliments the three-channel PSG chip of the MSX computer system, or in other words, a sound custom chip that brings five voices more to the three voices of the PSG sound chip on the system), and great MSX1 graphics to go with it. It was one of the first ROM on MSX with this sound feature. Together with its "3D" spinoff (F-1 Spirit: 3D Special), F-1 Spirit: The Way To Formula-1 was the most extended racing game Konami released for the MSX.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>12BFD3A9</hash>
		<image>./mixart/F-1 Spirit - The Way to Formula-1 (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/F-1 Spirit - The Way to Formula-1 (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/F-1 Spirit - The Way to Formula-1 (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="186017" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fantasy Zone II - The Tears of Opa-Opa (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Fantasy Zone II - The Tears of Opa-Opa</name>
		<desc>In the past, the courageous hero Opa-Opa saved the Fantasy Zone from the invading Nenon forces, but his victory came at a price as he was forced to fight his own father who led the invasion. It is now Space Year 1432, 10 years after that battle, and the Nenon forces are once again spreading chaos through the Fantasy Zone. Opa-Opa must once again fly into the Fantasy Zone to rout the invasion. Similar to Defender, the player occupies a side-scrolling level that repeats indefinitely, and in which the player can freely travel left or right. Each zone contains several "bases" that serve as primary targets. New to the sequel are "warps" hidden behind certain bases that allow the player to travel between different zones. Each level has at least three zones, and when all of the bases have been cleared in all of the zones of a level, the player can travel through the warp to the boss. Boss fights do not allow for free travel as the main stages do, and force the player to face the boss or face a particular direction. Bosses are generally very large and change color to reflect damage taken. The final stage is a "boss rush" in which the player must fight a succession of previous bosses before fighting the final boss. There are two action buttons that correspond to two types of attacks, "fire" and "bomb". The fire attacks shoot horizontally, as in a typical shooter, and different variants can be purchased at shops. The bomb attacks are more powerful, and the basic bomb drops downward. Other variants have other behaviors and are limited in quantity. Shops, uncovered at key points, allow the player to purchase upgraded weapons, bombs, and speed, as well as extra lives.[8] Upgrades to Opa-Opa's speed (such as larger wings, or jet engines) are permanent as long as the player does not lose a life, but weapon upgrades are time-limited, and bombs limited in quantity. Items become increasingly expensive with subsequent purchases, encouraging the player to vary their purchases.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon</publisher>
		<hash>1BDFAEEB</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Fantasy Zone II - The Tears of Opa-Opa (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fantasy Zone II - The Tears of Opa-Opa (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Fantasy Zone II - The Tears of Opa-Opa (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95250" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fantasy Zone (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Fantasy Zone</name>
		<desc>The Fantasy Zone is a solar system consisting of eight brightly colored, fantastic planets. The evil Menons are trying to take over all of the planets in the Fantasy Zone by using misappropriated foreign currency to build their forces. It is the player's job to recover all of the coins and save the solar system! 

Fantasy Zone is an arcade style shooter for one or two players. The goal is to destroy all of the creatures on each planet and collect as many of the lost coins as possible. At the end of each level is a large enemy that will have to be defeated before moving on to the next world.  At various points in the game, the player will be able to find a parts shop, which allows purchasing improvements for his spaceship, including better weapons and faster engines.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA Enterprises Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3E96D005</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Fantasy Zone (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fantasy Zone (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Fantasy Zone (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95270" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Justice (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Final Justice</name>
		<desc>Final Justice is a vertical shoot 'em up game developed by Compile. In Final Justice, you control a space craft that has to defend the earth against an invasion of aliens. You have to navigate your space ship around various obstacles and destroy all sorts of enemies at the same time. 

At the end of each round an end boss has to be defeated before you can continue to the next round.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>851BA4BB</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Final Justice (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Final Justice (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Final Justice (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95273" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Zone Wolf (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Final Zone Wolf</name>
		<desc>Final Zone Wolf is a overhead game where your in command of a small military commando team, and you move down the streets shooting. The goal of the game seems to be to stop some kind of missile attack. At the beginning of the game you need to select two members of your team, out of five options available. Statistics of these members are presented during the opening credits of the game.

The gameplay is sluggish, and your team members take a fixed formation which is actually a hindrance to get past obstacles as they will not get out of formation and prevent you from moving forward. The enemies seem to be being spawned at random, as such it is critical to keep moving forward as fast as possible avoiding them as much as you can.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wolf Team</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet Japan Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>14E2EFCC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Final Zone Wolf (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Final Zone Wolf (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Final Zone Wolf (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97925" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fire Ball (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Fire Ball</name>
		<desc>Generic Pinball Game</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hummingbird Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hummingbird Soft</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>CDCDC6C0</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Fire Ball (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fire Ball (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Fire Ball (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98008" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hinotori - Houou Hen (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Firebird</name>
		<desc>Based on the "Ho-o" (or "Karma" volume) of Osamu Tezuka's famous manga Hi no tori (or "Phoenix"), "Hi no tori Hououhen" is a vertically-scrolling shooting game where Gaou's goal is to locate the mystical phoenix across 6 stages of labyrinths, enemies and various other obstacles. As the game progresses, Gaou can power up by obtaining phoenix plumes to activate special weapons and other items to help him gain abilities such as invulnerability and special shots. In order to reach the final boss and pay a visit to the phoenix, Gaou must obtain a series of keys scattered across the stages - and must even backtrack to find others. The game is over when all three lives are gone - or when Gaou has reached the phoenix's lair.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3AB5AE57</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Hinotori - Houou Hen (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hinotori - Houou Hen (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hinotori - Houou Hen (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95334" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Front Line (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Frontline</name>
		<desc>Front Line is a vertically scrolling action game. Your mission is to infiltrate enemy territory and destroy their fortress. To reach the fortress, you will have to make your way through varied and dangerous terrain. Jungles, deserts, brush, and rocks all slow your progress, plus each area has numerous enemy fighters and tanks trying to stop you. To help get past these obstacles, you are armed with a machine gun and grenades; at some points in the game you may even come across an abandoned tank which you can control to increase your odds of survival. When you reach the end of the level and successfully destroy the fortress, the game will repeat at a higher level of difficulty. Gameplay is for one or two players, and four different skill levels are available.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Electric Software Limited</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B9D03F7B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Front Line (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Front Line (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Front Line (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95359" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gall Force - Defense of Chaos (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Gall Force - Defense of Chaos</name>
		<desc>Vertical scrolling, top-down, shoot 'em up. You can select between seven characters when to begin the game, depending on the character you will have a different ship, weapons and upgrades. During the game you can at select times switch to one of the other characters. The game plays both in space and flying over planets, where you have to destroy alien ships and installations and collect upgrades.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>99EF860E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Gall Force - Defense of Chaos (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gall Force - Defense of Chaos (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gall Force - Defense of Chaos (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97953" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Garyuu Ou (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Garyuoh</name>
		<desc>A spectacular battle scene that can not breathe in the background is backed by a magnificent story. You must break through a number of difficulties by using weapons that can shoot in 8 directions for high speed vertical scrolling.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xain</developer>
		<publisher>Xain</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2FB0ED30</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Garyuu Ou (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Garyuu Ou (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Garyuu Ou (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97958" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gekitotsu Pennant Race 2 (Japan) (English Menu).zip</path>
		<name>Gekitotsu Pennant Race 2</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<hash>E92FC432</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Gekitotsu Pennant Race 2 (Japan) (English Menu).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gekitotsu Pennant Race 2 (Japan) (English Menu).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gekitotsu Pennant Race 2 (Japan) (English Menu).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95402" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ghostbusters (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Ghostbusters</name>
		<desc>Based on the 1984 film of the same name, the Ghostbusters are the ones to call to "bust" any ghost hauntings. They do this through the use of nuclear-accelerated "proton packs" and "ghost traps", whereby the ghosts can be captured and transferred to a secure storage facility at their Headquarters. However New York City has suddenly become a very haunted place, and the number of ghosts has suddenly and dramatically increased. The Ghostbusters must reduce the paranormal psychokinetic energy, the "PK level" in the city, which represents ghost power, before the Temple of Zuul awakens and resurrects an evil goddess called Gozer.

Ghostbusters is an action game that features an overhead-view and a side-view. From Ghostbusters HQ, the player must monitor a map of midtown Manhattan for "ghost alarms", as well as for casual, roaming spirits, and plot a route to the alarmed area. Once the route is plotted, the player then controls the purchased Ghostmobile as it drives through traffic. Here, the player is able to capture casual ghosts on the way if they are en route. When the haunted location is reached, the game switches to a side-view. Two of the Ghostbusters will take position, activate their proton beams, and toss a trap to the ground. The player must then use the two Ghostbusters to attempt to lead the ghost(s) over the placed trap. Once activated, the trap springs to capture any ghosts directly above it. A successful capture will earn the player money, which can then be used to purchase new Ghostbusters vehicles and new modifications for it. An unsuccessful capture will see the ghost fly away (after nastily sliming one of the Ghostbusters).

As the game progresses, the PK energy in the city increases. The Ghostbusters must keep it under critical levels by being constantly successful at busting ghosts. Eventually the Temple of Zuul will activate, and if the PK levels are still manageable, the Ghostbusters can venture there for a final showdown with Gozer.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Activision (UK) Limited</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C9BCBE5A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Ghostbusters (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ghostbusters (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ghostbusters (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96202" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Nemesis 3 - The Eve of Destruction (Japan, Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Gofer no Yabou Episode II</name>
		<desc>Gofer no Yabou: Episode II (ã´ã¼ãã¡ã¼ã®éæã¨ãã½ã¼ãII lit. Gofer's Ambition Episode II) is a side-scrolling shooter developed and published by Konami for the MSX home computer in 1988. It was published in Europe as Nemesis 3: The Eve of Destruction later on the same year. The game is part of the long running Gradius series, and is a spin-off of the arcade game Gradius II: Gofer no Yabou. It is the second game of the series to be released exclusively for the MSX after Gradius 2. In terms of the story; the game is a sequel to Gradius II and Salamander. The game takes place almost 200 years after the crisis with Dr. Venom and James Burton has died in the year 6718. The Vic Viper is replaced by a new ship called the Vixen (4 classes); piloted by David Burton, a direct descendent of James who is assisted by his AI Gaudie.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>4B61AE91</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Nemesis 3 - The Eve of Destruction (Japan, Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nemesis 3 - The Eve of Destruction (Japan, Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Nemesis 3 - The Eve of Destruction (Japan, Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96201" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Nemesis 2 (Japan, Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Gradius 2</name>
		<desc>In the year 6664 Dr. Venom, the director of the Space Science Agency, was exiled to the planet Sard for his involvement in a failed rebellion and illegal scientific activities. One year later, he joined forces with the Bacterion invaders, escaped Sard, and took control of the space surrounding the planet Gradius. In 6666, the local government sends Colonel James Burton on the newest hyperspace fighter known as Metalion. The goal is clear: stop Dr. Venom and the Bacterion army before they conquer the planet.

Nemesis 2 (Gradius 2 in Japan) is a side-scrolling shoot-em-up. The gameplay is for the most part similar to that of Gradius. The player-controlled ship can alternate between three main weapons: Missile, Double, and Laser. Extra weapons such as various types of lasers, napalm missiles, reflex ring, and back beam can be collected as power-ups and equipped. In addition, special power-ups can be acquired, their effects ranging from slowing down enemies to turning the Metalion into an invincible drill-like machine for a brief amount of time. Boss battles are followed by optional mini-stages, which grant the player new weapons if completed successfully.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>DB847B2B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Nemesis 2 (Japan, Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nemesis 2 (Japan, Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Nemesis 2 (Japan, Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96200" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Nemesis (Japan, Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Gradius</name>
		<desc>Nemesis is the first entry in the long-running Gradius series on the Game Boy. Its side-scrolling shoot'em up gameplay follows the series template closely. Players control the Vic Viper through five levels, most based on levels in earlier entries, for a kind of 'greatest hits' of the series. There is a cave level (as in level 1 of the original Gradius), the mandatory Moai stage, a Gigeresque organic level, a graveyard (similar to bonus stages in the MSX and PC Engine version of the original Gradius) and a high-tech base. Besides the classic core ship in the first level, all boss enemies are entirely new.

The cycling Gradius power-up system is reused here: collected power ups advance the power meter which can be activated at any time to gain the highlighted item. The line-up includes the classic selection of speedups, missiles, dual shots, lasers, option satellites and forcefields.

The game allows players to start in any of the five levels and even to set the number of lives to a maximum of 99.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ultra Software Corporation</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>4D44255F</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Nemesis (Japan, Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nemesis (Japan, Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Nemesis (Japan, Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95459" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Green Beret (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Green Beret</name>
		<desc>This arcade game arms you with a knife and sends you on a kamikaze mission against hordes of enemy fighters.

There are four distinct sections of gameplay, taking in a Missile Base, a Harbour, a Bridge, and an enemy Prison Camp. Extra weapons with limited ammunition can be collected along the way, which will make the task a lot easier. The level is divided into 3 horizontal levels, which can be moved between either by jumping or using ladders, and this gives a chance to avoid the more threatening mobs of enemy fighters.</desc>
		<rating>0.1</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>61F41BCD</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Green Beret (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Green Beret (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Green Beret (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95470" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Guardic (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Guardic</name>
		<desc>Guardic is a top-down 2d shooter based on the classic premise of pitting a single starfighter against a horde of enemies with the fate of the galaxy at hand. A particularly interesting touch in Guardic is that instead of fighting through a scrolling field filled with enemies, the game places your ship in "rooms" with a fixed amount of opponents that take up the most part of the screen. After defeating every enemy on screen you advance to the next room and so on... Power ups are not activated until you reach the next room (with some exceptions) and even then you have to choose which ones to activate before you enter the fight, which gives the game an additional strategic touch.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Compile</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6AEBB9D3</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Guardic (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Guardic (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Guardic (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95474" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gun Fright (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Gunfright</name>
		<desc>The player takes the part of the "meanest and fastest Gun Totin'Bunch of Rootin' Tootin' Gun Slingers which ever did hit the Wild West", Sheriff Quickdraw. In the beginning of the game in a first person view the player has to be quick on the draw to shoot bags of money that fall down the screen, to collect a "bounty" that will be used to buy supplies and cover possible fines during the game.

The main game then takes place in an isometric scrolling play-field that is similar to previous Ultimate Filmation titles. The objective is to collect a bounty by finding and eliminating wanted criminals that are harassing the town. Innocent bystanders will point to the direction of the criminal, shooting them will result in a fine reducing your score. A horse can be obtained to speed up the chase. Once the wanted criminal is encountered, the game again switches to a first person cross hair view, where the first to draw will be the winner. Taking out the criminal will give you a reward that helps you with future expenditures as the cost of ammo and horses changes as the game goes along. Your final tally will become your score at the game's end.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Nippon Dexter</publisher>
		<hash>F877B3D6</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Gun Fright (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gun Fright (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gun Fright (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95489" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./H.E.R.O. (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>H.E.R.O.</name>
		<desc>There is trouble in the mines! Volcanic activity has trapped numerous miners, and it is your job to save them. As Roderick Hero, you need to make your way through the dangerous mineshaft avoiding the dangerous creatures and lava, and find out where the miners are located before you run out of energy. To help on your mission, Roderick Hero has several useful types of equipment. A prop pack will allow you to hover and fly around the mineshaft and (hopefully) avoid the many dangers within. Your helmet features a short range microlaser beam which can be used to destroy the bats, spiders, snakes, and other creatures you'll encounter in the mines. From time to time, your path through the mine may be blocked by stone or lava walls. You begin each mission with six sticks of dynamite which can be used to destroy these obstacles (be careful you don't blow yourself up, though!). If you run out of dynamite, your laser beam can also be used to destroy the walls, though this will take longer and use up more energy. As the levels progress, the mine shaft will become longer and more maze-like, creatures will more frequently block the path, and lava walls and pools will appear which are dangerous to the touch.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Activision (UK) Limited</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8FDAD3AF</hash>
		<image>./mixart/H.E.R.O. (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/H.E.R.O. (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/H.E.R.O. (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95588" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hydlide II - Shine of Darkness (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Hydlide II - Shine of Darkness</name>
		<desc>Hydlide II: Shine Of Darkness is an action RPG, and the second installment in the Hydlide series.

In a different space a wonderful world existed, called Fairy Land, which was dominated by swords and magic after the times of domination by monsters and evil had ended. The people of Fairy Land were intoxicated with peace. At that time an incident occurred. A Consciousness filled with evil awoke and it created new monsters, brought the dead back to life, and wanted to dominate Fairy Land again.

The monks were one of the first who noticed this and warned the people about it but they didn't listen and left the monks disappointed. The monks prayed to God and asked Him if there was a Savior. God, impressed by the monks prayers warped the space-time of Fairy Land with the human world and selected an innocent boy who lived there.

The player controls the innocent boy, who must roam the lands of Fairy Land and free it from evil. The player has to create a character before beginning the quest, customizing his parameters - life, strength, and magic. As in the previous game, the player slays enemies by "bumping" into them or using magical spells. It is possible to change between attacking and defensive stances on the fly. The hero can become stronger and gain additional powers. In the villages there are shops where the protagonist can buy and sell weapons, armor, and items.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>T&amp;E Soft</publisher>
		<hash>D8055F5F</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Hydlide II - Shine of Darkness (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hydlide II - Shine of Darkness (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hydlide II - Shine of Darkness (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95582" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hydlide (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Hydlide</name>
		<desc>An evil demon named Varalys casts a curse upon the princess Ann, turning her into three fairies. You control Sir Jim and set out to find the fairies, and then slay Varalys.  Only by vanquishing Varalys can the curse be lifted. Once the princess is restored the kingdom will be saved.

Hydlide is an action game with strong role-playing elements. The player has to explore vast wilderness areas, descending into dungeons and eliminating enemies on the way. Combat system is similar to the one implemented in Ys series: attacking enemies requires the player to "bump" into them, at the same time preventing them from attacking the playable character from the sides and the back. The player can change between defensive and offensive stances by pressing a single button. Magic spells can also be used to dispose of the enemies. The player character grows stronger and gains better parameters as he advances in the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>T&amp;E Soft, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>T&amp;E Soft, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>0F9D6F56</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Hydlide (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hydlide (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hydlide (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98022" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ikari (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Ikari Warriors</name>
		<desc>Better known as Ikari Warriors in the west, Ikari is a vertically scrolling action game where one or two players fight their way through a variety of terrain, such as jungles, rivers, and ruins. Along the way different weapons can be found, including machine guns, grenades, and rocket launchers.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<hash>A9A66075</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Ikari (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ikari (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ikari (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94537" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Antarctic Adventure (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Kekkyoku Nankyoku Daibouken</name>
		<desc>As a penguin, you must travel around Antarctica, making your way between bases before time runs out. This sounds easy, right? Wrong. Hindering your progress will be ice crevices and leopard seals. You can jump over the crevices, but jumping over the leopard seals may be difficult. You can speed up or slow down the penguin to avoid both of these hazards. The bases include Australia, France, New Zealand, USA, Argentina, UK, and Japan. You can collect flags and eat fish for points. Collecting a flashing flag will allow you to wear a propeller that enable you to fly over those hazards.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6B739C93</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Antarctic Adventure (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Antarctic Adventure (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Antarctic Adventure (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98068" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./King Kong 2 - Yomigaeru Densetsu (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>King Kong 2</name>
		<desc>Based on King Kong Lives movie King Kong 2: Yomigaeru Densetsu is an action game with puzzle-solving and role-play elements, a more complex experience compared to Famicom version of King Kong 2.

You play as Mitchel (Hank Mitchell from the movie) who travels to Golnebo Isle in search of Lady Kong, the only creature whose blood can save King Kong, seriously wounded in the end of the first movie. Exploring the island Mitchel will fight enemies with melee weapons and magic scrolls and gain experience points. With enough experience he levels up and gets increase in strength, speed, health and magic points. By entering certain buildings Mitchel can engage in conversations, buy weapons or healing items and rest. In conversations Mitchel will also get hints needed to solve some puzzles. The game has several endings depending on how long it took the player to beat it (game time is measured in days) and how many continues were used.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>23B78A2D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/King Kong 2 - Yomigaeru Densetsu (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/King Kong 2 - Yomigaeru Densetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/King Kong 2 - Yomigaeru Densetsu (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95744" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./King Knight (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>King's Knight</name>
		<desc>King's Knight is a fantasy-themed top-down shooter where four heroes have to unite to defeat a dragon and rescue a princess in despair. It was one of the first games published by Square Soft (now one-half of Square Enix). King's Knight is a variation on Konami's Knightmare which sold extremely well.

The first four stages involve you powering up your characters as far as they can go, picking up shields (to increase defense), boots (to increase speed), swords (to increase attack power), and spell icons (which will be required to be held by everyone for the final storm on the castle), defeating monsters along the way. The power-ups are hidden underneath mountains, rocks, and houses. Nearly everything can be shot at and destroyed. The heroes are, in order:

Ray Jack, the Knight, who possesses strong attacking power; Kaliva, the Wizard, who is good with magic and jumping; Barusa, the Monster, who has a strong defense; and Toby, the Thief, who can move swiftly.

It is necessary to keep all four heroes alive for the fifth and final stage, because there are certain points that the group cannot get past if one of the party members has died.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<hash>A0481321</hash>
		<image>./mixart/King Knight (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/King Knight (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/King Knight (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95751" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./King's Valley II (Japan, Europe).zip</path>
		<name>King's Valley II - The Seal of El Giza</name>
		<desc>Far, far into the future, inter-planetary archaeologist Vick XIII, makes a choking discovery. The pyramids on earth are malfunctioning devices of alien origin with enough energy to destroy earth. And it's up to Vick to switch off the core functions of El GizaThe game consists of six pyramids each with its own wall engravings and color pattern; every pyramid contains 10 levels. The idea of the game is to collect crystals called soul stones in each level by solving the different puzzles and evading or killing the enemies using the many tools and weapons available to unlock the exit door that will take you to the next level.King's Valley II: The Seal of El Giza is an Action game, published by Konami, which was released in Europe in 1988.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E82A8E8E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/King's Valley II (Japan, Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ouke no Tani - El Giza no Fuuin - Edit Contest Yuushuu Sakuhinshuu (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/King's Valley II (Japan, Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95766" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Knight Lore (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Knight Lore</name>
		<desc>Our hero must reach Melkhior, a somewhat eccentric wizard who is the only one who can save him. As with most Ultimate titles of the day, reaching him is a long and treacherous challenge, involving both puzzle-solving and action, meaning that each screen requires thorough planning and precise navigation. 

The game uses the isometric viewpoint in a manner similar to the later Head Over Heels, using monochrome but detailed graphics and techniques to avoid flickering sprites. The game lasts for 40 days and nights - at night your character turns into a werewolf. Ultimate's individual style of eschewing straightforward instructions in favor of feature lists and riddles is put to good use here, with the story detailed in a rhyming poem of sorts.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Aackosoft International B.V.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B575C44A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Knight Lore (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Knight Lore (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Knight Lore (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="185841" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Knightmare II - The Maze of Galious (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Knightmare II - The Maze of Galious</name>
		<desc>Knightmare 2:Maze of Galious/Majou Densetsu 2:Daimashikyou Galious is a 
Japanese game which was released back in 1987 for MSX. It is a sequel to Knightmare. I've never played Knightmare 1 before. All I know is that it is a shooter type of game in which you play as 
Popolon who tried to rescue his wife Aphrodite from a villain named Hudnos. The
sequel takes place right after you rescued Aphrodite.  Now you play as both 
Popolon and Aphrodite, who will try to to rescue their future baby kidnapped 
by a dark priest named Galious. The gameplay is a mix between action and RPG.
You have the side-scrolling actions throughout six worlds and yet at the same
time there are some RPG elements included such as having to find certain items
to complete certain tasks. Maze of Galious stays true to its name with its huge
and sometimes confusing maze-like worlds to be explored.Majou Densetsu II: Daimashikyou Galious is a Role-Playing game, developed and published by Konami, which was released in Japan in 1987.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>FE23D253</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Knightmare II - The Maze of Galious (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Knightmare II - The Maze of Galious (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Knightmare II - The Maze of Galious (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="185842" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Knightmare III - Shalom (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Knightmare III - Shalom</name>
		<desc>In this game, you play the role of a Japanese high-school student, the leader of computer club. Above all, you like playing games. One day, you and your girlfriend are playing a game and suddenly get teleported into the game world. This is a fantasy world that resembles ancient Greek civilization. Before long you realize that you are in fact a hero who must save this world from the evil Gog, an ancient demon awaiting resurrection, otherwise you won't ever be able to return home.

Shalom is the third entry in Konami's Knightmare series. Unlike the previous games, it is much less heavy on action and is structured primarily like an adventure game with emphasis on interaction with characters and exploration. You navigate your hero through a large top-down world, interacting with characters along the way. The interaction is done via a command menu with verbs such as "Look", "Talk", "Take", etc. From time to time you'll have to fight enemies. The battles take place on a separate screen, and you attack the enemy with your weapons in real time.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<hash>CF60FA7D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Knightmare III - Shalom (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Knightmare III - Shalom (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Knightmare III - Shalom (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95776" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Knightmare - Majou Densetsu (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Knightmare. Majyo Densetsu</name>
		<desc>Plunge into the saga of romance and bloodcurling adventure - in a castle full of surrealistic knightmare monsters right out of greek mythology! For experts only : this is a game adventure of super-high level difficulty!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>0DB84205</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Knightmare - Majou Densetsu (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Knightmare - Majou Densetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Knightmare - Majou Densetsu (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95932" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Magical Kid Wiz (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Magical Kid Wiz</name>
		<desc>Magical Kid Wiz is an Action game, developed by Seibu Kaihatsu and published by SCEI, which was released in Europe in 1986.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Seibu Kaihatsu</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8C2F2C59</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Magical Kid Wiz (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Magical Kid Wiz (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Magical Kid Wiz (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95935" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Magical Tree (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Magical Tree</name>
		<desc>Magical Tree is a platform game where the player's objective is to reach the tree's top, some 2,000 meters above the ground. You play the little indian and you have to avoid several enemies, like bees and owls while climbing towards the top of the tree. Collect fruits and special items as diamonds on your way to the top of the tree.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>827038A2</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Magical Tree (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Magical Tree (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Magical Tree (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95434" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Golvellius (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Maô Golvellius</name>
		<desc>Golvellius is an action adventure video game for the Japanese MSX home computer system that plays much like The Legend of Zelda.
The scenario is the same in all the three different versions of Golvellius. The ending promised a sequel, which was never developed/released.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Compile</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>5EAC55DF</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Golvellius (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Golvellius (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Golvellius (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95382" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gate of Labyrinth (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Meikyuu no Tobira. Gate of Labyrinth</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dempa Shinbunsha</developer>
		<publisher>Dempa Shinbunsha</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2C2020A0</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Gate of Labyrinth (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gate of Labyrinth (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gate of Labyrinth (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96080" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Monkey Academy (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Monta-kun no Ichi-Ni-Sans?</name>
		<desc>This platform game is about solving arithmetic problems. In the equation one number is missing, you 'll have to find the right number. This game is aimed at young children to help them learn arithmetic problem solving or playing with numbers.

Some monkeys are minding their own business when they see a number missing from their arithmetic problem. Who took it? Another monkey, a crab? And where could it be? The only way to find that out is to go looking for it.

Guide your monkey across the screen and up and down platform levels. Watch out for the crab! If its claws bite you, you lose a monkey. Jump up and pull down shades to find the missing number. When you find it, catch the number bar. Then send it up to your helper monkey. Find three missing numbers and earn bonus points!</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>98CD6912</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Monkey Academy (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Monkey Academy (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Monkey Academy (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96096" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mopiranger (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Mopi Ranger</name>
		<desc>The peaceful land of the Mopira have been invaded by the Razons. In this platform game you 'll play Mopiranger and you have to save the young Moplits, who have been kidnapped by the dastardly Razons. The levels are build in a maze-like pattern in which you have to find and rescue the young Moplits from the hostile Razons. Using the obstacles present in the game you can block the Razons, but also lock yourself in...</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9D73E4C5</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Mopiranger (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mopiranger (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mopiranger (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98225" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Out Run (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Out Run</name>
		<desc>OutRun is a racing game that allows the player to race across varied terrain in a readily available Ferrari, complete with a female passenger, over a series of short tracks.

Gameplay is viewed from just above and behind the car. The roads are full of sharp bends and hazards, contact with which can cause the car to roll and lose the player's time. On each section of track there is a fork in the road, allowing the player to choose which direction he or she wishes to go in. The player has to to complete five track sections in total, out of the fifteen in the game.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon</publisher>
		<hash>0A9F8D6C</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Out Run (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Out Run (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Out Run (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96302" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pac-Man (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Pac-Man</name>
		<desc>One of the most popular and influential games of the 1980's, Pac-Man stars a little, yellow dot-muncher who works his way around to clear a maze of the various dots and fruit which inhabit the board.

Pac-Man's goal is continually challenged by four ghosts: The shy blue ghost Bashful (Inky), the trailing red ghost Shadow (Blinky), the fast pink ghost Speedy (Pinky), and the forgetful orange ghost Pokey (Clyde).  One touch from any of these ghosts means a loss of life for Pac-Man.

Pac-Man can turn the tables on his pursuers by eating of the four Energizers located within the maze.  During this time, the ghosts turn blue, and Pac-Man can eat them for bonus points.  This only lasts for a limited amount of time, as the ghosts' eyes float back to their center box, and regenerate to chase after Pac-Man again.

Survive a few rounds of gameplay, and be treated to humorous intermissions between Pac-Man and the ghosts.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Bug-Byte Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>D74DFFA2</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Pac-Man (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pac-Man (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pac-Man (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98231" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pac-Mania (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Pac-Mania</name>
		<desc>Pac-Mania is a variation on the game Pac-Man. You need to guide Pac-Man around a maze and eat all of the dots on the board in order to proceed on to the next round. Numerous, multi-colored ghosts also roam the maze trying to stop you. If you eat one of the power pellets in the maze, the ghosts will temporarily turn blue and run from you. Pac-Man can earn bonus points by eating the ghosts when they are in this state. The maze is now shown in isometric perspective and is larger than screen which will scroll to follow the action. To help get out of tight spots, Pac-Man now has the ability to jump. But be careful, because some of the ghosts have learned this trick as well and you could end up in a mid air collision! </desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Namcot</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7DF16FC8</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Pac-Mania (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pac-Mania (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pac-Mania (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96536" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Road Fighter (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Road Fighter</name>
		<desc>A top view racing game. You have to reach the finish line before time runs out. Don't crash into the wall, cars or trucks. Because if you do you will lose gasoline. You can get additional gasoline by picking up fuel items. Especially avoid the purple cars, they do change lanes! And remember... oil makes road slippery...</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>01DDB68F</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Road Fighter (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Road Fighter (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Road Fighter (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96567" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./R-Type (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>R-Type</name>
		<desc>R-Type is a side scrolling shoot 'em up best known for its extremely tough and strategic gameplay.  You control the R-9 spaceship as it launches a last-ditch effort to repel the evil Bydo empire.

The R-9 comes equipped as standard with a small gun which can only take down the smallest of enemies without firing several shots. By holding down the fire button, it can be loaded up so as to release a large burst of energy, eliminating all but the strongest enemies in its path. From time to time, pods will come flying in your direction. Upon being shot, they release an upgrade. The first one will invariably be the one called "The Force", which is a weapons pod that clings either to the front or the back of your ship, absorbing any enemy bullets or acting as a bumper with which you can fly head-on into them. You can also use it as an offensive weapon by firing it and pulling it back in. Mastering the Force is vital to surviving in R-Type, since it must be used both as protection against bullet clusters, as a remote controlled cannon, and in order to clear the screen from obstacles. Other upgrades give you target-seeking missiles or a bigger main gun. Different gun types, differentiated by their colour, serve different purposes. The blue one sends laser beams bouncing across the screen (good for tunnels), the red one fires straight ahead, and the yellow one follows any walls it may encounter (good for artillery emplacements).

The stages of R-Type are made in an organic style, certainly inspired by H. R. Giger's artwork for the Alien movies. When it came out, it was considered trend-setting since it broke off from the stereotypical sci-fi mould of other shoot'em'ups. In part, the levels themselves are your enemy, which is exemplified by the fourth, where spider-like creatures weave webs that cover the screen and block your path, or levels with intricate tunnel systems. Still, the levels are best handled with a combination of strategy and reflexes, without the memorisation that is required of R-Type's contemporary rival, Gradius.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Irem Corp.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A884911C</hash>
		<image>./mixart/R-Type (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/R-Type (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/R-Type (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96584" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Salamander (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Salamander - Operation X</name>
		<desc>In a distant part of the universe, an alien creature called Zelos was born. As he grew so did his appetite, and soon he began devouring galaxies, planets, and stars by the hundreds. Now your planet has appeared in Zelos' path, and it is up to you and a partner to fly into battle to save your world. Life Force is an action packed shooter based on the arcade game. There are six levels which alternate between side and vertical scrolling, each of them ending with a powerful guardian. Throughout the game, destroying certain enemies will release power ups which can be used to equip your ship with more powerful weapons, extra speed, and shields.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
		<hash>C36F559D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Salamander (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Salamander (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Salamander (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96686" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Skooter (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Skooter</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Eaglesoft</publisher>
		<hash>53B87DEB</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Skooter (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Skooter (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Skooter (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96691" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sky Jaguar (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Sky Jaguar</name>
		<desc>Vertical shooter. When a weakened and vulnerable Earth is invaded by the vicious Zephyr army, the planet's only hope is a fleet of powerful ships, the Sky Jaguars. It'll take sharp reflexes and amazing skills to survive the Zephyrians' unrelenting assault... can you last long enough to discover and destroy the enemy's hidden headquarters?</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E4F725FD</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Sky Jaguar (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sky Jaguar (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sky Jaguar (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98386" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Space Manbow (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Space Manbow</name>
		<desc>Space Manbow is a side scrolling shoot 'em up. Shooting certain enemies will leave a power up pod behind which can be collected to add more power to your ship. Each level features a wide variety of enemies trying to stop you, with a large boss at the end. The levels are maze-like. Gameplay is for one player or two players alternating.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>27405EED</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Space Manbow (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Space Manbow (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Space Manbow (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98442" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tetris (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Tetris</name>
		<desc>The original commercially-licensed version of Alexey Pajitnov's classic Tetris puzzle game.  Geometric shapes fall from the top of a playfield to rest on the bottom; fit the pieces together, and the line they form disappears.  If the pieces don't form lines and eventually stack up to the top of the playfield, the game is over.  Difficulty increases by dropping the pieces faster and faster over time.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BPS</developer>
		<publisher>BPS</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>AA598DFD</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Tetris (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tetris (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Tetris (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96953" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Castle, The (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>The Castle</name>
		<desc>In the puzzle and platform game The Castle the player controls a prince that has to save the princess. To find his princess he must explore the castle, which has a hundred different rooms. Each room is a puzzle on its own as the prince must avoid enemy knights, fat Tiroler men, hazardous objects and has to use objects to get to the next door. In each room the prince has to collect keys and items, such as rings, gold bars and bottles. The bottles will give the prince an additional life. The keys may have different colors and only opens doors with the corresponding key color.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ASCII Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2149C32D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Castle, The (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Castle, The (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Castle, The (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98455" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cockpit, The (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>The Cockpit</name>
		<desc>The Cockpit is a Simulation game, developed and published by Nidecom, which was released in Japan in 1988.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nidecom</developer>
		<publisher>Nidecom</publisher>
		<hash>5F354E65</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Cockpit, The (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cockpit, The (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Cockpit, The (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96963" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Demon Crystal, The (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>The Demon Crystal</name>
		<desc>Once upon a time, a demon called Sharudo came to Fairy's land, creating havoc. He built a monster town on a mountain top and dwelled there, ruling over the land below. One day, Sharudo came and took princess Chris to his monster lair. Now it's up to Ares, a brave soldier in the service of the Fairies, to save Chris.

Demon Crystal is an action puzzle game. Scattered around the stage are numerous keys which help open locked areas. The goal is to find the big key which is needed to open the exit and advance to the next stage. Ares' only weapon is a limited number of bombs, which explode in a flame and can kill multiple enemies at once. The game consists of 30 stages (houses).</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Radio Wave Newspaper Publisher</publisher>
		<hash>11DE4DFD</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Demon Crystal, The (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Demon Crystal, The (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Demon Crystal, The (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96968" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fairy Land Story, The (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>The Fairyland Story</name>
		<desc>The Fairyland Story puts the player in control of Ptolemy the witch, who must make her way through 101 single-screen rounds and defeat the evil purple dragon Dracolisk to retrieve the holy diamond and return peace to the land. Ptolemy's main weapon is her magic attack, which turns enemies into cakes for a short while, then the enemies can be either destroyed by further magic attacks or by being dropped off a platform, possibly squashing other enemies below.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Hot-b</publisher>
		<hash>26E34F05</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Fairy Land Story, The (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fairy Land Story, The (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Fairy Land Story, The (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96977" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Goonies, The (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>The Goonies</name>
		<desc>While this MSX version of The Goonies borrows the basic concept from the Famicom (NES) version, it features completely different levels and enemies. Rather than play Mikey and save the remaining Goonies, you play as Sloth who must rescue all the Goonies, meaning you need to rescue seven Goonies per stage instead of just one so the stages are significantly longer and more complicated. To open doors you need to use keys instead of bombs, and you can only carry one key at a time. There's also an experience meter that increases every time you kill an enemy.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>DB327847</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Goonies, The (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Goonies, The (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Goonies, The (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98472" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Treasure of Usas, The (Japan, Europe).zip</path>
		<name>The Treasure of Usas</name>
		<desc>The Treasure Of Usas is a platform game. Centuries ago, the War God Induras banished Usas, the supreme Mother God, and threw the four pieces of her jewel in the winds. Wit and Cles are attempting to find the broken jewel to try and achieve one of the greatest discoveries of the academic world. Their adventures, controlled by you, will lead them to many strange places to fight many unusual enemies. There are five stages in the game.

There are emotion icons in the game and by touching these icons your player will change emotion. At the top of the screen you can see which emotion you have. This is important because you 'll have to have the same emotion of the demon of the level to fight him.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>30396650</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Treasure of Usas, The (Japan, Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Treasure of Usas, The (Japan, Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Treasure of Usas, The (Japan, Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97036" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Thexder (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Thexder</name>
		<desc>A platform shooter from Japan, Thexder offers many levels and diverse enemies that gradually increase in difficulty. You pilot a Battletech-style robot capable of switching from a mech into a jet at any time. Your weapon auto-aims, but uses up a fixed amount of rechargeable energy; if you run out of this energy, you'll have to wait a few seconds before you can fire again. Your mech also contains a shield that can be activated to protect you from harm, but this lasts for a few seconds and uses up some of your life energy.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Game Arts Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>599AA9AC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Thexder (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Thexder (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Thexder (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98484" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Topple Zip (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Topple Zip</name>
		<desc>Topple Zip is a vertically scrolling shooter that is marketed as a racing game. The basic premise is that you control an aircraft and fly in competition against several other, computer controlled crafts. In addition to shooting at your opponents, you may ram into them, and they into you. Doing so may dislodge a pill shaped power-up from them which you can then shoot and collect. 

Power-ups exist in various types, including defensive and offensive such as giving you better weapons. There are eight different levels, each of which contain a number of warps which link to other levels. How the levels connect is random each time you play the game. 

The goal of the game is to locate a key which is necessary to access the warp which leads to the eight and final level. Collect it from whichever level it is hidden inside of, and access the eighth level before any of your competitors.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bothtec</developer>
		<publisher>Bothtec</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>96B33497</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Topple Zip (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Topple Zip (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Topple Zip (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="95783" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Video Hustler (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Video Hustler</name>
		<desc>"Pocket bal", one of the most famous versions of billiards in the world is now on your computer screen.
You'll discover the excitement of balls colliding.
The silence and concentration of the billiard room, as well as the enthusiasm of the players will all be there for you.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
		<hash>64853262</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Video Hustler (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Video Hustler (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Video Hustler (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="94573" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Athletic Land (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Wanpaku Athletic</name>
		<desc>You play a child on a metro-cross-like dash across an obstacle course with a time limit.
Your physical prowess is tested to the limit as you leap, duck, turn and twist to avoid all hazards.
There are several screens with different combinations of obstacles.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>7B1ACDEA</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Athletic Land (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Athletic Land (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Athletic Land (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97274" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Yie Ar Kung-Fu II - The Emperor Yie-Gah (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Yie Ar Kung-Fu II - The Emperor Yie-Gah</name>
		<desc>Yie Ar Kung-Fu 2: The Emperor Yie-Gah is a sequel to the MSX / Famicom (NES) version of Yie Ar Kung-Fu, rather than the versions directly based on the arcade release. The game follows the quest of Lee Young, the main character from the previous game, to become a kung-fu master. This involves fighting with a wide range of opponents in a traditional one-on-one 2D environment. Lee Young has a wide range of attack moves he can use to lower his opponent's life bar, including traditional punching and kicking attacks as well as jumping ones. Opponents are well equipped with unique weapons and attacks.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>D66034A9</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Yie Ar Kung-Fu II - The Emperor Yie-Gah (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Yie Ar Kung-Fu II - The Emperor Yie-Gah (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Yie Ar Kung-Fu II - The Emperor Yie-Gah (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97270" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Yie Ar Kung-Fu (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Yie Ar Kung-Fu</name>
		<desc>Yie Ar Kung-Fu follows the quest of a martial artist named Oolong to become the Grand Master of Kung-Fu, honoring the memory of his illustrious father. To do that, Oolong will have to face some of the most skillful martial artists in one-on-one battles. The battles take place on side-view screens. The hero has two moves at his disposal: punching and kicking. These moves must be executed by pressing a corresponding button together with a directional button or arrow key. Oolong also has the advantage of being able to jump higher than most of his opponents. The latter utilize unique moves to stop the hero, including sumo-style leaping motions, shuriken-throwing, nunchaku-swinging, etc.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8A12EC4F</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Yie Ar Kung-Fu (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Yie Ar Kung-Fu (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Yie Ar Kung-Fu (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="96345" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Penguin Adventure (Japan, Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Yume-tairiku Adventure</name>
		<desc>Penguin Adventure: the main character - a male penguin - must save the penguin princess from a sickness that has spread across the penguin world. The cure to the sickness can be found in the Golden Apple of the Golden Apple Tree.

In this action packed game, you take control of the male penguin and travel across the lands and seas in search of the Golden Apple, fighting different types of enemies including bats, thunder-striking clouds, and environmental obstacles such as rocks, until finally reaching the princess. The stages feature different types of landscapes such as forests, mountains, caves, and water stages. As you fight your way through, you can also catch flying fish which you can trade at the different types of shops for new equipments and a weapon.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>0F6418D3</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Penguin Adventure (Japan, Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Penguin Adventure (Japan, Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Penguin Adventure (Japan, Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98560" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Yuurei-kun (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Yuurei Kun</name>
		<desc>Yuurei-kun is an Action game, developed and published by System Sacom, which was released in Japan in 1988.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>System Sacom</developer>
		<publisher>System Sacom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>712AE3C6</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Yuurei-kun (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Yuurei-kun (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Yuurei-kun (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98561" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Zanac Ex (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Zanac Ex</name>
		<desc>Zanax EX is an enhanced version of the vertically scrolling shooter Zanac A.I.. While preserving the locations and the gameplay system of the original version, this release builds upon the graphical enhancements of the Famicom/NES version of Zanac A.I..

The backgrounds are noticeably more detailed than in the original version; also, some locations have different graphical design. The scrolling is also smoother than in the previous releases, effectively altering the feeling of control and gameplay speed. The status bar, which has occupied the right side of the screen in the original release, has been moved to the top of the screen, occupying significantly less space.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D153B2F2</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Zanac Ex (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Zanac Ex (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Zanac Ex (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Metal Gear</name>
		<desc>Near the end of the 20th century, a small fortified nation named Outer Heaven (founded by a mysterious war hero whose name and identity are shrouded in secrecy) is threatening the nations of the "West" with the development of a new prototype weapon named Metal Gear, a walking tank which is capable of launching nuclear warheads from anywhere on the globe. As FOX-HOUND's (an elite black ops unit) newest recruit, going by the codename of Solid Snake, your mission is to infiltrate Outer Heaven and rescue your missing comrade, Grey Fox (who was captured after a failed infiltration), while gathering intelligence on Metal Gear. 

In order to fulfill this objective, the player must collect various weapons and equipments (including keycards for further access into the fortress), while avoiding visual contact with the enemy. The player must also confront bosses in the form of Outer Heaven's elite mercenary force and rescue hostages hidden within the fortress in order to increase player rank, which gives Snake an extended life bar and increased storage capacity for replenishable items and ammo. The player can use a wireless transceiver to come in touch with their commanding officer, Big Boss, to learn more about their current mission objectives or contact one of the local resistance members operating covertly within the fortress to gain useful tips and insights.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Metal Gear (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Metal Gear (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Metal Gear (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aliens - Alien 2 (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Aliens. Alien 2</name>
		<desc>Whereas most platforms, including the MSX, received their own versions of Activision's Aliens, Square gave Japanese MSX users a unique spin-off.

Aliens: Alien 2 is an arcade platformer (or run'n'gun if you like) featuring Ripley on a planet infested with aliens. Armed with only a basic gun at first, she faces facehuggers that come out of alien eggs. After having dispatched a face hugger, the egg may be shot to reveal an item. Items may be hand grenades, stronger guns or wing items which make her jump longer. For some reason, the planet is infested not only with aliens and their offspring, but also with snakes. After clearing the surface level, Ripley enters a complex where the first boss, a giant, full-grown alien resides. The following level takes place within the complex.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Aliens - Alien 2 (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Aliens - Alien 2 (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Aliens - Alien 2 (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King's Valley (Japan, Europe).zip</path>
		<name>King's Valley</name>
		<desc>King's Valley is a puzzle game in which you need to collect all the treasures by drilling and cutting your way through the pyramids. But beware of the mummies that haunt the pyramids. If you use the limited available cutting and drilling equipment in the wrong order you'll eventually get stuck. You'll then have to play the whole level over again.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/King's Valley (Japan, Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/King's Valley (Japan, Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/King's Valley (Japan, Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Industry Co. Ltd.</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ganbare Goemon! - Karakuri Douchuu (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Ganbare Goemon</name>
		<desc>The second game in the Ganbare Goemon series (known in English as Mystical Ninja) and the first released on a video game console and home computer. It was initially released for the Family Computer July 30, 1986[1] and later released for the MSX one year later.
The game revolves around the main character, Goemon, and his exploits. As the name suggests, his character was based on Ishikawa Goemon, the noble thief of Japanese Folklore. Unlike its sequels, this game still doesn't feature the comic situation and strange characters that define the series, and Goemon is portrayed as a noble thief rather than a plain hero.[2]

The game plays a top view action/adventure game (similar to The Legend of Zelda) though it is separated by stages. In each level Goemon must find three passes in order to advance. Some of these passes are found in boxes, secret passages or can be bought. After finishing all the stages, the game will present you with a new Japanese province (eight total), but all the levels will remain the same. The ending, however, will be different.

Like the rest of the series, Goemon can be powered up if certain items are found and/or bought, which can be lost after a few hits.

The MSX version has the option to be played in turns by two players, with the second player playing as a ninja named Nezumi KozÅ, which is the basis of Goemon's sidekick Ebisumaru. In addition, unlike the Family Computer version, the game has six more provinces with completely new levels after finishing the game once.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ganbare Goemon! - Karakuri Douchuu (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ganbare Goemon! - Karakuri Douchuu (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ganbare Goemon! - Karakuri Douchuu (Japan).mp4</video>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hacker (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Hacker</name>
		<desc>Hacker is an adventure/trading game based on what was then a unique idea. You're starting into the adventure as a real hacker would do, lacking information of what is to come, only driven by your ambition. Consequently, the game opens with a plain text screen, prompting you for the login password. To break into the system is the first puzzle you've got to solve.

Once in, you'll soon find out that you've accidentally stumbled upon a conspiracy of global impact. From then on, you'll maneuver a robotic drone around the globe through a tunnel system deep in the earth. In major cities, you may surface and talk to contact persons, who'll trade items for cash. When delivered to the correct city, you can exchange these items for a piece of evidence. If all evidence is collected, you're to inform the FBI. As if figuring out the correct routes and trades wasn't hard enough, frequent system malfunctions and security checks test your skill as well...</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Hacker (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hacker (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hacker (Japan).mp4</video>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Activision, Inc.</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hyper Olympic 1 (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Hyper Olympic 1</name>
		<desc>Track &amp; Field is a sports game that allows the player to have an experience based around the Summer Olympic Games. Events include the 100 meter dash, the hammer throw, the javelin throw, the long jump, the high jump and the 110 meter hurdles.

The MSX version replaces the hurdles with a 400 meter dash.

The Famicom version loses the hammer throw and the high jump, but the NES version restores the high jump while adding skeet shooting, the triple jump and archery as events. The NES version also keeps the 110 meter hurdles and forgoes the 400 meter dash.

If the player wants to go to the next event or round then they will have to qualify, by beating increasingly difficult maximum times or minimum distances. This game contains a two player option, in which the players take it in turns.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Hyper Olympic 1 (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Hyper Olympic 1 (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hyper Olympic 1 (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hyper Olympic 2 (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Hyper Olympic 2</name>
		<image>./mixart/Hyper Olympic 2 (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Hyper Olympic 2 (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hyper Olympic 2 (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fathom (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Ningyo Densetsu. Fathom</name>
		<image>./mixart/Fathom (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fathom (Japan).mp4</video>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Toshiba-EMI</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear 2 - Solid Snake (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Metal Gear 2 - Solid Snake</name>
		<desc>In 1999, a great scientist named Kio Marv invented "oilix", a special petroleum-purifying substance that was supposed to help in the upcoming oil crisis. Shortly after the invention became known in the world, Dr. Marv was abducted. An investigation showed that he was held captive in Zanzibar Land, an isolated state in Central Asia which was ruled by a group of mercenaries from all around the world. Having oilix in addition to nuclear weapons are bound to Zanzibar an invincible state that would sooner or later attempt to conquer the entire world. Roy Campbell, ex-commander of special unit FOXHOUND, sends Solid Snake, the man who has single-handedly brought down the military nation of Outer Heaven four years ago, on a mission to infiltrate Zanzibar and to bring back the scientist and his invention.

Like its predecessor, Metal Gear 2: Solid Snake is a stealth game. The driving element of the gameplay is to stay unnoticed. If guards spot you, you don't have much chance in combat, unless you are armed with appropriate weapons, which aren't easily acquired. Snake can use a variety of weapons and gadgets to help him survive during his mission. He can also hide behind objects, punch guards, and crawl. From time to time he'll have to participate in boss battles, where stealth won't help any more.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Metal Gear 2 - Solid Snake (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Metal Gear 2 - Solid Snake (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Metal Gear 2 - Solid Snake (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19900720T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Boomerang (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Boomerang</name>
		<desc>You control a boy walking through a platform maze trying to collect items while being chased by enemies. They can be killed by using the  boomerang. The boomerang has a limited range and, if thrown, must always picked up. It will not return to you.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Boomerang (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Boomerang (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Boomerang (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AshGuine Story III - Fukushuu no Honoo (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>AshGuine 3</name>
		<desc>The time had come to put an end to the long and unproductive battle. This was brought about by the Azumural, the third race that came from the heavens.  While both countries were fighting, the Azumural steadily developed their scientific capabilities and in the end even acquired aviation technology. They got to know about the world beyond the Ring. Because of their brutal nature they made a temporary alliance with the Ghouls and invaded Eletria. The balance of fight largely deteriorated and the Eletrians barricaded themselves in the last remaining fortress Nesha Castle</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AshGuine Story III - Fukushuu no Honoo (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/AshGuine Story III - Fukushuu no Honoo (Japan).mp4</video>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>T&amp;E Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Panasoft</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dungeon Master (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dungeon Master</name>
		<desc>Dungeon Master is a role-playing game where the player selects four adventurers and descend into the depths of the dungeon.  The gameplay is reminiscent of the 3D dungeon crawl type of role-playing games popularized by Wizardry and The Bard's Tale.  However, unlike these games, Dungeon Master features real-time combat, which requires the player to click on the opponent in order to execute an attack. Another notable aspect of the game is its growth system: instead of gathering experience points and leveling up, characters improve by repeatedly using the same action. Spellcasting involves selecting and combining symbols, which can be arranged as rune sequences. The game also allows the player to directly interact with objects in the game world through a point-and-click interface.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dungeon Master (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dungeon Master (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dungeon Master (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FTL Games</developer>
		<publisher>FTL Games</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Athletic Ball (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Athletic Ball. Ghost Flipper</name>
		<image>./mixart/Athletic Ball (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Athletic Ball (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Athletic Ball (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ASCII</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AshGuine Story II - Kokuu no Gajou (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>AshGuine 2</name>
		<desc>The time had come to put an end to the long and unproductive battle. This was brought about by the Azumural, the third race that came from the heavens.  While both countries were fighting, the Azumural steadily developed their scientific capabilities and in the end even acquired aviation technology. They got to know about the world beyond the Ring. Because of their brutal nature they made a temporary alliance with the Ghouls and invaded Eletria. The balance of fight largely deteriorated and the Eletrians barricaded themselves in the last remaining fortress Nesha Castle</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AshGuine Story II - Kokuu no Gajou (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/AshGuine Story II - Kokuu no Gajou (Japan).mp4</video>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>T&amp;E Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Panasoft</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vampire Killer (Japan, Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Akumajyo Drakyula</name>
		<desc>You are young Simon, who has just entered Dracula's Satanic Castle.
The world of Dransylvania is in trouble, and you are the one to set it right. You have to fight your way through 18 stages of demons to where Dracula is hiding. Once you have destroyed Dracula, the evil force behind all the trouble will show up, attempting to destroy you! Destroy this menace, and Dransylvania will return to it's happy days after a wait of hundreds of years.

Vampire Killer follows the same plot as Castlevania, but with a different gameplay. At each stage, Simon has to find a white key to open the exit door which leads to the next stage. The keys are usually hidden in the castle's walls, in which he will also find useful items. Items can also be found by whipping candles and other sources of light inside the castle.

Among the items which can be found are:
Gold Cross: wipes out all enemies;
Silver Cross: prevent enemies from appearing for a short time;
Sapphire Ring: renders Simon invincible for a short time;
Blue Crystal: renders Simon invisible for a short time;
Yellow Key: is used to open chests containing items;
Candle: highlights destructible walls; 
Map: can be used up to three times and shows Simon location n the castle;
Red Book: increases item's prices;
White Book: decreases item's prices
Tan Shield: blocks enemy attacks;
Red Shield: reduces damage upon enemy contact;
Boots: make Simon walk faster;
Wings: make Simon jump higher;
Holy Water: a secondary weapon, which uses hearts as ammunition;
Hourglass: stops enemy movement for a short time, consuming hearts.
Hearts are both a kind of ammunition and currency in the game. They can be found by whipping candles or killing enemies. They are used for buying items from the Old Crone and as ammo for the Holy Water and the Hourglass.

Simon can also find several primary weapons in the game, such as whip upgrades, a throwing dagger, an axe and a cross. Differently from Castlevania, the dagger, axe and cross replace the whip and do not use hearts as ammo.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Vampire Killer (Japan, Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Vampire Killer (Japan, Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Vampire Killer (Japan, Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
	</game>
</gameList>
