<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>Famiri Konpyuta Disuku Shisutemu</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game id="98601" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bakutoushi Patton-kun (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Bakutoushi Patton-kun</name>
		<desc>Bakutoushi Patton-Kun is an overhead tank combat game similar in style to Atari's Combat game. It was the first FDS title to allow for four players to play simultaneously. In the game, players attempt to destroy each others tanks. If a tank is destroyed, the driver of the tank will exit the vehicle, and must try to stay alive long enough for a replacement tank to parachute down from the sky. Game play continues until only one tank is the sole survivor. Then players advance to a new stage with different terrain. There are 56 stages in total. Tank stats can also be changed in an Editor mode. Despite referencing the name of American General George S. Patton in the title, there is no mention of him anywhere else throughout the game. Although the game was only release in Japan, the loading screen instructions contain English profanity.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880805T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Soft Pro International</developer>
		<publisher>Soft Pro International</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>7304E4C0</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Bakutoushi Patton-kun (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bakutoushi Patton-kun (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bakutoushi Patton-kun (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98602" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Baseball (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Baseball</name>
		<desc>A re-release for the Famicom Disk System in 1986 of Nintendo's Famicom Baseball. As in real baseball, the object of the game is to score the most runs. Up to two players are supported. Each player can select from one of six teams. Although there is no difference between them other than uniform color, they are meant to represent the six members of the Japanese Central League.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>D48AEA0C</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Baseball (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Baseball (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Baseball (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88124" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Big Challenge! Gun Fighter (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Big Challenge! Gun Fighter</name>
		<desc>A sheriff must take down the outlaws of the wild west, and uncover the greater mysterious that has terrorized the town for decades. You'll scroll across stages and must defeat a certain amount of outlaws to draw out their leader and finish him off in a 3rd person shootout. Ammo is very valuable and limited in this game and must be used wisely.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D9836FB3</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Big Challenge! Gun Fighter (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Big Challenge! Gun Fighter (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Big Challenge! Gun Fighter (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88126" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bio Miracle Bokutte Upa (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Bio Miracle Bokutte Upa</name>
		<desc>Upa is the prince of a magical kingdom and the most recent in a line of brave fighters. One day, though, he broke an urn containing the spirit of Zai, an incredibly evil goatish demon who takes the life force of the kingdom's adults and kidnaps all the babies - except for Upa, who is given a magical rattle by a fairy who was trapped in the urn along with Zai. And so, in order to save his kingdom, Upa crawls into action... He will navigating side scrolling stages with platforms and can inflate enemies by hitting them with his rattle for use as temporary platforms or to throw at adversaries.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9CBD8207</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Bio Miracle Bokutte Upa (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bio Miracle Bokutte Upa (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bio Miracle Bokutte Upa (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="71325" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Breeder (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Breeder</name>
		<desc>In the future there is a coliseum featuring automated fighting robots. It was created so a space civilization can research and develop its fighting machines.Players can create up to eight of these metal soldiers to fight against each other in the combat arena. For each fighting machine, players are given up to 999 points to disperse it between fifteen different categories such as the machine's speed, dexterity, armor, and jumping abilities. Each category costs a different amount of points to increase.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Soft Pro International</developer>
		<publisher>Soft Pro International</publisher>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<hash>DE8FE836</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Breeder (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Breeder (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Breeder (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98611" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Clu Clu Land - Welcome to New Clu Clu Land (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Clu Clu Land</name>
		<desc>In Clu Clu Land, the player is an female balloonfish named Bubbles who swims around in a maze trying to uncover all the golden Ingots.

Clu Clu Land's story starts with a type of sea urchin, the Unira, stealing all of the treasures in the underwater kingdom of Clu Clu Land. Bubbles, the heroine, sets out to retrieve the treasure. The object of the game is to uncover all the gold ingots in each stage while avoiding the Unira and Black Holes. Ingots usually form a shape such as a heart or a mushroom. The only way Bubbles can turn around to change directions is by means of Turning Posts located throughout the stages. Bubbles can stun the Unira by using a Sound Wave. When they are stunned, Bubbles can push them into a wall to get rid of them and receive points. If Bubbles is hurt by the Unira, she will lose a life. A life is also lost when Bubbles falls into a Black Hole, or when time runs out. The game ends if Bubbles has lost all her lives.

In later levels, the player must pass over the ingots an odd number of times to uncover them, as they will alternate between their uncovered side and a dull side.

The Famicom Disk version is based on Vs. Clu Clu Land which was released for the coin-op Nintendo Vs. System. It contained twice as many puzzles, a new enemy (Boss Unira), different level themes, and some other adjusted game features.

This is the last licensed game that was released for the Famicom Disk System. Because of this it is arguably the rarest Famicom Disk system game and sells for a large amount of money.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>E588C55E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Clu Clu Land - Welcome to New Clu Clu Land (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Clu Clu Land - Welcome to New Clu Clu Land (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Clu Clu Land - Welcome to New Clu Clu Land (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88140" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cocona World (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Cocona World</name>
		<desc>You control a young witch who wanders throughout various parts of the kingdom. There are many animal inhabitants to interact with, some of which are good and some of which are evil. There are also a number of activities to perform and mini-games to play. Over time, the witch will request that certain activities be performed. If they are not performed within a certain time period, the player receives a penalty. Over time, the character's mood and strength will drop. If both of these are never restored and drop to zero, the game is over. This game was only released in Japan, and has never been translated into English.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870410T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SOFEL Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>SOFEL Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F83A603D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Cocona World (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cocona World (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Cocona World (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98612" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dandy - Zeuon No Fukkatsu (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dandy : Zeuon no Fukkatsu</name>
		<desc>A conversion port of the Atari 8-Bit computer game Dandy. Though it has been changed quite a bit for it's Japanese audience and doesn't resemble the original game very much at all.The view is overhead and much like Zelda you walk around and explore while using your sword to defeat various enemies. There are various dungeons and villages you can visit and the game even has a day/night cycle.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19881021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atelier Double</developer>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F523A202</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dandy - Zeuon No Fukkatsu (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dandy - Zeuon No Fukkatsu (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dandy - Zeuon No Fukkatsu (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="99361" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dig Dug II (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dig Dug II</name>
		<desc>Unlike the first game, Dig Dug II takes place on an island with an overhead view. The goal is simple: to kill all the enemies on the round. There are two types of enemies; Pookas (the round red monsters with goggles) only have the power to kill a player by touching him, but Fygars (the dragons) have the power to kill a player either by touching him or horizontally breathing fire to burn him.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>819B7566</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dig Dug II (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dig Dug II (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dig Dug II (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="99360" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dig Dug (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dig Dug</name>
		<desc>The objective of Dig Dug is to eliminate underground-dwelling monsters by inflating them with an air pump until they explode, or by dropping rocks on them. There are two kinds of enemies in the game: "Pookas" (a race of cute round red monsters, said to be modeled after tomatoes, that wear yellow goggles) and "Fygars" (a race of green dragons that can breathe fire while their wings flash).</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900720T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>82B4A619</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dig Dug (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dig Dug (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dig Dug (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88149" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dirty Pair - Project Eden (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Dirty Pair : Project Eden</name>
		<desc>Kei and Yuri, two cute space investigators, are the heroines of this side-scrolling action game by Bandai and based on the popular animation series Dirty Pair. This was released along with the movie Project Eden though it doesn't follow the plot of the actual movie all that well. Also the game is known for it's incredible difficulty.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Daiei Seisakusho</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>F3DC053A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dirty Pair - Project Eden (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dirty Pair - Project Eden (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dirty Pair - Project Eden (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88156" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Donkey Kong Jr. (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Jr.</name>
		<desc>Mario has gone mad! He's turned the tables on Donkey Kong and locked him in a cage. It's up to you, as Donkey Kong Jr., to rescue your father by stealing Mario's set of keys. But it won't be easy. You'll have to fight off ape-eating Snapjaws, jump onto moving islands and break through a jungle of vines to get to the keys that will free Donkey Kong. Can you handle the action? Because this off-the-wall monkey business will have you going bananas!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>3046966A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Donkey Kong Jr. (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Donkey Kong Jr. (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Donkey Kong Jr. (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88155" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Donkey Kong (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>You are Mario, and that big old gorilla, Donkey Kong, has run off with your girlfriend. It's up to you to struggle up those ladders and balance on those beams to rescue your lady fair. She's held captive at the very top. But Donkey Kong is not ready to give her up so easily. He's tossing barrels and fireballs at you at every turn. It's up to you to outmaneuver that wily ape. Good luck, your lady awaits!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880408T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>6C0740E9</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Donkey Kong (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Donkey Kong (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Donkey Kong (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88159" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Druid - Kyoufu no Tobira (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Druid : Kyoufu no Tobira</name>
		<desc>Druid is an action game inspired by the arcade hit Gauntlet. As the eponymous hero, your job is to destroy four magic skulls hidden over eight levels.The game is presented in a top-down view. The druid walks around the terrain seeking out the staircase that leads to the next level. On the way, he is harassed by hordes of monsters that come out of every direction and attack him, decreasing his health. To defend himself, the druid can use the spells of water, fire or electricity to toss projectiles. However, these magical weapons have limited ammo.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880303T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E978A8AE</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Druid - Kyoufu no Tobira (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Druid - Kyoufu no Tobira (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Druid - Kyoufu no Tobira (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88160" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Eggerland (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Eggerland</name>
		<desc>The Eggerland series is better known outside of Japan as The Adventure of Lolo series.The game is often referred to as "Syodai", or the "first one". The game is a remake of "Meikyuu Shinwa" (Eggerland 2; lit. "Labyrinth Myth") for the MSX2 Home Computer System with updated graphics and different music. Furthermore, in this remake the location of some special rooms was swapped, and a final boss battle was introduced.In this Eggerland, Lolo must navigate his way through a non-linear series of rooms, the majority of which occupy a 10x10 arrangement along the main floor of a castle. Many rooms have more than one exit for Lolo to choose from, and a map can be collected along the way to provide the player with information about where he or she is, and what rooms have already been visited. Secret entrances to hidden chambers must be found so that keys can be collected, enabling the player to explore deeper into the castle.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D9C2CE76</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Eggerland (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Eggerland (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Eggerland (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88163" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Esper Dream (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Esper Dream</name>
		<desc>This is a story that occurred in the distant village from where you live.
This village was filled with a beautiful, quiet, and mysterious aroma.

However, the villagers suffered from an unexpected tragedy.
The Evil clan called Narcisse tribe, began searching for the magic hidden in our village.

Even worse, they kidnapped the daughter of our mayor, Alice.

Please, go forth and rescue Alice, and bring peace to our land!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash />
		<image>./mixart/Esper Dream (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Esper Dream (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Esper Dream (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88164" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Exciting Baseball (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Exciting Baseball</name>
		<desc>A baseball simulator, Exciting Baseball follows Exciting Billiards and Exciting Basket (better known as Double Dribble in the West) in Konami's series of sports games for the Famicom Disk System.

Like the others in the Exciting series it's a straightforward exemplar of its particular sport. It doesn't have the flair of the original two Exciting games, as it never had an Arcade antecedent.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
		<hash>FA860775</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Exciting Baseball (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Exciting Baseball (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Exciting Baseball (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88165" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Exciting Basket (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Exciting Basket</name>
		<desc>Exciting Basket (Known in the US as Double Dribble) was a basketball arcade game developed and released in 1987 by Konami. Much of the game's popularity came from its animation sequences showing basketball players performing slam dunks.Players can choose from one of four teams: Boston, Chicago, Los Angeles and New York. There is no difference in skill level or abilities between the teams. Since there is no NBA license, no team names or player names are used, however, the teams wear the same color of their NBA counterparts (Boston wears green, Chicago red, etc.).</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870724T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>AE5D2E58</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Exciting Basket (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Exciting Basket (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Exciting Basket (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88166" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Exciting Billiard (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Exciting Billiard</name>
		<desc>Exciting Billiard is a billiard simulation game developed and published by Konami for the Family Computer Disk System in 1987. It was the first of Konami's "Exciting Sports" series produced for the Nintendo Famicom, similar to Namco's own "Family Sports" label. Exciting Billiard offers players four modes of play. Break Shot is a single player only mode, where the player competes against other pool hustlers for money, attempting to earn enough money to graduate to higher and more impressive venues with increasing amounts of money on each bet. The remaining three modes can be played with one to four players at a time (human or computer controlled), with each players' progress capable of being saved to disk.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>9EEE752A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Exciting Billiard (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Exciting Billiard (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Exciting Billiard (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88167" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Exciting Soccer - Konami Cup (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Exciting Soccer : Konami Cup</name>
		<desc>Players select one of the various soccer teams, and aim to become the best team in the league. Each team possesses different levels of kick strength, endurance, dribbling technique, defensive skill, and luck. They are set at the beginning of the game, but can be enhanced through training. During play, the view of the field is a bird's eye view, with either goal located at the far top and bottom sections of the field. Although this game is considered a relatively minor release, it's ending BGM entitled "Seaside Memory" is highly revered.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>9DC7C28B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Exciting Soccer - Konami Cup (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Exciting Soccer - Konami Cup (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Exciting Soccer - Konami Cup (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98622" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fairytale (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Fairytale</name>
		<desc>A strategy game about a group of children going to battle against an army of pigs that has suddenly appeared near their village. The children and pigs take turns moving around a map before going into semi-real time turn based battles. A cute but surprisingly difficult game and the last of Soft Pro International's releases for the Famicom Disk System.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Soft Pro International</developer>
		<publisher>Soft Pro International</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>73CA4E71</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Fairytale (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fairytale (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Fairytale (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88169" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Falsion (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Falsion</name>
		<desc>Humanity has colonized most planets in our galaxy, the Milky Way, and they now look towards expanding their reach by using an experimental travel technology called "Hyperzone Drive". However, a race of aliens who have already mastered that technology are currently invading planets at a quick pace, closing in on our solar system. The invaders attack humanity's colony on Pluto and conquer it with little resistance, since human civilization doesn't have the technology to defend itself.

The human organization responsible for the space program, the "United Space Force", decides to use the yet-untested "Hyperzone Drive" in order to send ships that will directly attack the armies of the invading aliens. However, the new technology proves hard to control, and only one of the ships manages to survive the trip: Falsion.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>DE943D3E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Falsion (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Falsion (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Falsion (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="71371" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Famicom Grand Prix - F1 Race (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Famicom Grand Prix : F1 Race</name>
		<desc>Compete in championships or try to beat your best time in this top-down Formula 1 racing game.

Famicom Grand Prix: F1 Race gives you 10 tracks to race on with either dry or rainy conditions. On top of keeping all four wheels on the road, tire wear, damage, and fuel must be managed to secure victory. Stopping into the pit for maintenance at the right moment can mean the difference between victory and defeat. There are also 24 different cars to purchase with your winnings with varying attributes including speed, fuel efficiency, body strength, and tire endurance.

F1 Race was released as one of Nintendo's Disk Fax line of games. It came on a special blue disk and allowed players to submit their best times through special kiosks in various stores across Japan. Players with the best time were given a chance to win a Super Mario Bros. Game &amp; Watch LCD game.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>C2E8B252</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Famicom Grand Prix - F1 Race (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Famicom Grand Prix - F1 Race (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Famicom Grand Prix - F1 Race (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="71370" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Famicom Grand Prix II - 3D Hot Rally (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Famicom Grand Prix II : 3D Hot Rally</name>
		<desc>The second game in the Famicom Grand Prix series. In a departure from its predecessor, Famicom Grand Prix II features a behind-the-car view similar to Outrun and Rad Racer. Rather than consisting of a handful of short tracks, 3D Hot Rally provides three long tracks consisting of a variety of different terrain types giving the feel of an actual rally race. Each track has multiple routes to the finish line, requiring you to find the best path to victory. The game features three cars to choose from: the speedy Kattobi coupe, the balanced Yonque truck, or the rugged Monster buggy.



In order to complete a race, players must reach each checkpoint within a certain time limit. If the limit is crossed too late, time is subtracted from their bank. If the time bank is depleted, the race is over. Successfully reaching a checkpoint before the time limit is reached banks extra time. Players can also collect exclamation marks scattered throughout the tracks. Collecting enough exclamation marks to fill the dash meter allows temporary access to the hot dash, a fifth gear that greatly increases speed. Before each race, you're asked to place a repair point somewhere on the track, allowing you to repair any damage done to your car, so long as you pick a route that leads you past that checkpoint. Taking too much damage puts you out of the race.



As the name implies, 3D Hot Rally allows you to use the Famicom 3D System glasses to give the race a real feeling of depth. It also challenged players to submit their best times via Famicom Disk Fax kiosks located in various stores for a chance to win a Disk-kun stationary set.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880414T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>85CDD2E9</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Famicom Grand Prix II - 3D Hot Rally (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Famicom Grand Prix II - 3D Hot Rally (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Famicom Grand Prix II - 3D Hot Rally (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98625" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Family Composer (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Family Composer</name>
		<desc>Family Composer  was developed by the same team that created Ikinari Musician for the Famicom earlier in the same year. Like Ikinari Musician, it is not really a game, but rather a music simulator. Unlike Ikinari Musician, Family Composer gives players more control over the music played, and even allows them to compose new songs, and record the compositions to disk. In many ways, it can be seen as a precursor to the music composing feature of Mario Paint.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Musical Plan</developer>
		<publisher>Tokyo Shoseki</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>90F4D3ED</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Family Composer (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Family Composer (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Family Composer (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88176" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Final Commando - Akai Yousai (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Final Commando - Akai Yousai</name>
		<desc>Your brothers-in-arms are hostages behind enemy lines, and you're their only hope for freedom. But the firepower you'll face to rescue them is awesome. Cannons, tanks, submarines and snipers will blast you with horrific crossfire, while jet fighters zero in from above. To defend yourself, you control the army's advanced all-terrain attack jeep, with its arsenal of guided missiles and incendiary grenades. Of course these are merely tools, and to save your countrymen you'll need more than a handful of gunpowder. You'll need a pocketful of miracles, and the ferocity of a wild Jackal!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>B89D5131</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Final Commando - Akai Yousai (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Final Commando - Akai Yousai (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Final Commando - Akai Yousai (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98629" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Galaga (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Galaga</name>
		<desc>The objective of Galaga is to score as many points as possible by destroying insect-like enemies. The player controls a starfighter that can move left and right along the bottom of the playfield. Enemies swarm in groups in a formation near the top of the screen, and then begin flying down toward the player, firing bullets at and attempting to crash into them. In later stages, some enemies even break from an entering group in a frantic attempt to crash into the player. The game ends when the player's last fighter is lost by colliding with an enemy, being hit by an enemy bullet, or being captured.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>2AD9A7FD</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Galaga (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Galaga (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Galaga (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98630" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Galaxian (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Galaxian</name>
		<desc>The gameplay is relatively simple. Swarm after swarm of alien armies attack the player's ship that moves left and right at the bottom of the wraparound screen. The ship can only have one shot on screen at a time. The player defeats one swarm, only to have it replaced by another more aggressive and challenging swarm in the next stage. A plain and repetitive starfield scrolls in the background.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900720T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>30FF4A34</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Galaxian (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Galaxian (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Galaxian (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="71390" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gall Force - Eternal Story (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Gall Force : Eternal Story</name>
		<desc>Based upon the anime of the same name, Gall Force is a group of science fiction anime OAV series by the studio Artmic, with production by Youmex and AIC. The original character designs were by Kenichi Sonoda. In the original story line, an all-out, prehistoric galactic war rages between the all-female Solnoids and the amorphous Paranoids for too long. In the midst of battle, a plan which was secretly hatched by the leaders of both sides comes into fruition, and an unsuspecting crew of seven Solnoid soldiers aboard the Kulanis-class Cruiser named the Star Leaf is caught up in the middle.

The Famicom Disk System game is a top down shooter and follows a different story than that of the OAVs. It features Rabby flying across Terra, and catapulting into six different regions of space in order to rescue each of her crew members one at a time. With each crew member that you rescue, you gain access to a new configuration for your ship.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>4FE5C67B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Gall Force - Eternal Story (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gall Force - Eternal Story (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gall Force - Eternal Story (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88187" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ginga Denshou - Galaxy Odyssey (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Ginga Denshou : Galaxy Odyssey</name>
		<desc>Ginga Denshou - Galaxy Odyssey is a game developed for the Family Computer Disk System by Wave Jack, and published by Imagineer in 1986. Unlike most games for the FDS, Galaxy Odyssey did not come with just a disk and an instruction booklet. Among the contents found in the large box, were an audio cassette tape and a book recounting the game's story.The game itself is quite unusual as well. It features a blend of vertical shooting gameplay mixed with more Zelda-like exploration sequences. As the pilot of a ship, you could dock with certain dungeon entrances, and take a shuttle down to the ground to explore and search for items. Searching around isn't easy at first, since you run out of oxygen fairly quickly, and that starts to drain your life, of which you start out with three bars.To win the game, you must find the medicine needed to rescue the people who are suffering from a disease in your home area. To do so, you must collect warp codes, and translate alien codes, and blast off from one dungeon location to travel to another. The game's text is in Japanese, and has never been translated to another language.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagineer</developer>
		<publisher>Imagineer</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>FD0384BE</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Ginga Denshou - Galaxy Odyssey (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ginga Denshou - Galaxy Odyssey (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ginga Denshou - Galaxy Odyssey (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88171" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Family Computer Golf - Japan Course (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Golf : Japan Course</name>
		<desc>An update of sorts to Golf. Players get to take control of Nintendo's mascots Mario and Luigi (in the 2 player game) and play over 18 holes of golf on courses modeled after real courses in Japan.

Players can choose to either try their skills in match play or stroke play. Match play involves two golfers trying to win the most holes. They win holes by getting the better score than their competitor. Stroke play differs as it just involves the golfer trying to get the best score possible by completing each hole in as few strokes as possible.

When on the golf course, players can choose the club they want to use, adjust the speed and strength (from a 1 to 3 scale) of their swing, and aim in the direction they want to hit the ball. Hitting the ball involves the use of a meter with an icon that goes back and forth, which gauges the distance the ball is hit. Players can take a step back from the tee and take practice swings so they can get into a rhythm using this meter.

This game also contained a now defunct feature where players could record their personal information and their best scores and then bring the game disk to a Disk Fax machine. Inserting the disk into this machine would fax over the player's information to Nintendo's headquarters. This information was used for a contest. Being selected a contest winner would award the player with a golden colored disk version of this game. This golden disk version of the game contained an exclusive course that was not present on the original version of this game.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>8F25B303</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Family Computer Golf - Japan Course (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Family Computer Golf - Japan Course (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Family Computer Golf - Japan Course (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88188" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Golf (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Golf</name>
		<desc>A port of the Nintendo Famicom game to the Famicom Disk System.

Golf is a sports-simulation video game released in 1984. The golfer is a mustached man who resembles Mario.

The player one character wears a white shirt and shoes with blue pants and uses a white ball, while the player two character wears a red shirt and shoes with black pants and uses a red ball.

The user must first decide whether to play single stroke play or the two player selections of doubles stroke play or match play. The user is then placed at the tee of the first hole of eighteen.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>CE3404A8</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Golf (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Golf (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Golf (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="71377" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Family Computer Golf - U.S. Course (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Golf: U.S. Course</name>
		<desc>A slightly updated companion title to Golf - Japan Course released just a few months earlier. The graphics are more updated and the gameplay is a little more advanced as well. Players get to take control of Nintendo's mascots Mario and Luigi (in the 2 player game) and play over 18 holes of golf on courses modeled after real courses in the USA.

Players can choose to either try their skills in match play or stroke play. Match play involves two golfers trying to win the most holes. They win holes by getting the better score than their competitor. Stroke play differs as it just involves the golfer trying to get the best score possible by completing each hole in as few strokes as possible.

When on the golf course, players can choose the club they want to use, adjust the speed and strength (from a 1 to 3 scale) of their swing, and aim in the direction they want to hit the ball. Hitting the ball involves the use of a meter with an icon that goes back and forth, which gauges the distance the ball is hit. Players can take a step back from the tee and take practice swings so they can get into a rhythm using this meter.

This game also contained a now defunct feature where players could record their personal information and their best scores and then bring the game disk to a Disk Fax machine. Inserting the disk into this machine would fax over the player's information to Nintendo's headquarters. This information was used for a contest. Being selected a contest winner would award the player with a golden colored disk version of this game. This golden disk version of the game contained an exclusive course that was not present on the original version of this game.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870614T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>A02BB651</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Family Computer Golf - U.S. Course (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Family Computer Golf - U.S. Course (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Family Computer Golf - U.S. Course (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98635" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Green Beret (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Green Beret</name>
		<desc>Based on the arcade game of the same name, the player's objective in the FDS version was changed from rescuing prisoners to destroying a secret weapon being developed in the enemy's headquarters. Additionally, a 2-players co-operative mode was introduced as well, allowing two players to play simultaneously (with Player 1 in blue and Player 2 in red). The play mechanics are essentially identical to the arcade version, however the Flamethrower is removed (only the Rocket Launcher and Grenades remained) and two new power-up items are introduced: a Star mark which grants invincibility and a pistol with unlimited ammo, both which are only usable for a limited period. The FDS version also features two additional stages that were not in the arcade game: an airport set between the Missile Base and the Harbor, where the player faces a group of rocket soldiers at the end; and a new final stage set inside the enemy's base in which the player must disarm a nuclear missile at the end that is about to be launched; by using rocket launchers dropped by enemy soldiers. The flamethrower corps at the end of the Warehouse stage was replaced by a paratrooper unit.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870410T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>F226ABAA</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Green Beret (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Green Beret (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Green Beret (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98637" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gyruss (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Gyruss</name>
		<desc>Gyruss  is a shoot 'em up arcade game designed by Yoshiki Okamoto and released by Konami in 1983. The majority of enemies are spaceships, which must be destroyed to complete a level. They appear either from the centre of the screen or from one of the edges, and move in swirling patterns. They can shoot the player's ship or destroy it by contact. They hover near the centre of the screen after completing their deployment pattern, and occasionally fly outwards and shoot at the player. If not destroyed by the player, the enemy ships gradually fly away one by one.

The gameplay is similar to that of Galaga but presented in a forced 3D perspective, with the player's ship facing 'into' the screen and able to move around the perimeter of an implicit circle. The scrolling starfield of earlier space shooter games is arranged to fit the 3D perspective, with the stars coming into view at the centre of the screen and flying outward, giving the impression of the player's ship moving through space.

Gyruss was also remade for the Family Computer Disk System in Japan, and later the Nintendo Entertainment System in North America, released by Konami's subsidiary Ultra Games. In these versions of the game, the core gameplay is still largely the same, but there are several major revisions. The game was well received in North America. Revisions include:

Updated graphics

Additional control options

The music from the arcade version of the game was slightly remixed, and several additional tracks composed by Atsushi Fujio, Yuichi Sakakura, and Harumi Ueko were added.

The player starts off at "Three Warps To Neptune" instead of "Two Warps"

The player can use a super phaser attack in addition to the normal guns

There are additional enemies, including boss fights when the player reaches each planet

Bonus stages after each planet's boss is defeated, for a chance to gain additional powerups
    
There is a definite ending to the game. In the NES version, it's a brief text about the Universe being at peace. In the FDS version, there is a full ending sequence with credits.

In addition to the satellites providing the usual double guns and bonus points, they can also provide extra phasers, a smart bomb, and even an extra life

Instead of the arcade's looping 24 stages, there are 39 looping. In the arcade, the player starts from Neptune and proceeds to Earth. On the NES version, the player travels through the entire Solar System, including Neptune, Pluto, Uranus, Saturn, Jupiter, Mars, Earth, Venus, Mercury, and the Sun.

The player can enter the Konami code at the title screen for extra lives, but with a twist: the code must be entered in reverse (A-B-A-B-right-left-right-left-down-down-up-up) instead of in the original sequence.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19881118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D2A68BDF</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Gyruss (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gyruss (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gyruss (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="18699" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Halley Wars (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Halley Wars</name>
		<desc>Its the middle of the 21st century. The armies of Lord Halley are launching attacks on planet Earth. You are the last chance for Earth, piloting a craft specially developed to engage these hordes. You must fight your way through their defenses to the final goal, the alien base. The final battle is about to commence!

Halley Wars is a vertical scrolling shooter. The game has 6 stages set in locations in space such as, above planets or in asteroid fields. There are end of levels bosses at the end of each stage each with their own weaknesses. There are power-ups, which can be picked up along the way when you shoot particular asteroids or satellites. These upgrade your weapon strength, speed, add explosive pods and shields.

Where the game stood out was, there are comets that need to be destroyed on your journey. Each comet and ship that you dont shoot makes it to earth and does some damage there. Comets do more damage than the enemy ships do. If Earths damage level reaches 100% the game is over. For every 2000 points you score, 1% of Earths damage is repaired.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ITL Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>08F9E8FC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Halley Wars (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Halley Wars (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Halley Wars (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88190" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hao-kun no Fushigina Tabi (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Hao-kun no Fushigi na Tabi</name>
		<desc>As my apprentice, you have been studying a long time to master the secrets of magic. Now the time has come to prove yourself. You must journey to the four Mystery Castles in search of four magic talismans. You will face many perils along the way: the castles are riddled with underground passages and intricate mazes, where you may become lost forever! And strange creatures prowl the castles, ready to pounce upon you when you least expect it! But you will find magic powers hidden along the way, to help you in this Mysterious Journey. The magic talismans you seek are the greatest gifts known to man: wealth, wisdom, happiness, and peace. Go now, complete your quest, and prove that you are as great a wizard as I!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870511T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Carry Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Disk Original Group (DOG)</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>CB7A8570</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Hao-kun no Fushigina Tabi (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hao-kun no Fushigina Tabi (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hao-kun no Fushigina Tabi (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88192" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hikari Shinwa - Palthena no Kagami (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Hikari Shinwa : Palthena no Kagami</name>
		<desc>In a time where humans and gods coexisted in harmony, the kingdom of Angel Land was ruled by two goddesses, Palutena the Goddess of Light and Medusa the Goddess of Darkness. While Palutena administered the light and helped the mortals cultivate their crops, Medusa despised the mortals and used the darkness to destroy their crops and turn the mortals into stone. Enraged, Palutena transformed Medusa into a hideous monster and banished her into the dark Underworld.

But Medusa would not go quietly. She assembled an army of monsters and evil spirits of the underworld to conquer Palutena's home, the Palace in the Sky. War erupted and Medusa's minions overwhelmed Palutena's army, eventually imprisoning the Goddess of Light. Medusa then seized the Three Sacred Treasuresâthe Mirror Shield, the Arrow of Light, and the Wings of Pegasusâand gave them to her most powerful minions.

Defeated and imprisoned, Palutena's only hope was to seek the help of Pit, a young angel trapped in the Underworld. Using the last of her strength, she sent Pit a magical bow. Thus, Pit set out on a quest to escape the Underworld, retrieve the Sacred Treasures that would help him defeat Medusa, and rescue Palutena and restore peace to Angel Land.

The original Famicom Disk System versions feature save slots, unlike the North American version which uses a password system (known in-game as "Sacred Words"). As with Metroid, the FDS version of Kid Icarus also features higher-quality music and sound effects that take advantage of the system's additional sound channels.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>AA05F769</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Hikari Shinwa - Palthena no Kagami (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hikari Shinwa - Palthena no Kagami (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hikari Shinwa - Palthena no Kagami (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98644" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ice Climber (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Ice Climber</name>
		<desc>The plot is simple: the Condor has stolen the food supply from the neighboring village and takes it to his nest on the mountain nearby. So it's up to Nana and Popo to climb up the ice-covered top of the mountain to get the vegetables back from Condor. You'll do this by hopping up platforms while avoiding various enemies and obstacles before your time runs out.

Interestingly the Famicom Disk System port is actually based on the arcade version Vs. Ice Climber and differs from the console version in ways such as an animated title screen, stage select menu, 16 additional mountains, occasional blizzard and wind effects, more enemy characters, and bonus multiplier items.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19881118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>A06045E9</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Ice Climber (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ice Climber (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ice Climber (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98648" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jikai Shounen Met Mag (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Jikai Shounen Mettomag</name>
		<desc>The player must go around each stage and collect every sphere in order to progress. Each sphere can change the polarity of the character from red to blue and vice versa. Each stage is littered with blue and red arrows: Being the same color as these arrows will magnetize the player character, which has different effects depending on the direction the arrow is pointing: For instance, an arrow pointing down will push the player to the ground if they are the reverse color but a same-colored character can hover across as the blocks will hold them up. Conversely, an arrow pointing up will allow players of the opposite color to jump far higher from the arrow, but will almost entirely eliminate the jumping power of a same-colored character as it pulls them down.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870703T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thinking Rabbit</developer>
		<publisher>Disk Original Group (DOG)</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C8CE0200</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Jikai Shounen Met Mag (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jikai Shounen Met Mag (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Jikai Shounen Met Mag (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="99377" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kaettekita Mario Bros. (1988)(Nintendo).zip</path>
		<name>Kaettekita Mario Bros.</name>
		<desc>Kaettekita Mario Bros. ("The Return of Mario Bros.") is an updated rerelease of the original Mario Bros. arcade game, which was one of the first games to be ported to the NES console. It adds a few new features to the format, including improved controls for Mario, cutscenes and the ability to save high scores with the Famicom Disk Reader's save function, but is otherwise identical.

The game was part of the Disk Writer system in Japan, where players could write new games over old Famicom disks at special machine vendors found in video game stores and other likely locales. This made the games cheaper to buy (as it minimized production costs) but also made games that were exclusive to this service, such as Kaettekita Mario Bros, harder to find for collectors.

Inexplicably, the game also has a sponsor: Nagatanien, a Japanese producer of seasonings for rice and noodle dishes. Mario had also previously appeared on Nagatanien Japanese TV commercials. This makes Kaettekita Mario Bros. an early example of an advergame.

The European version of Mario Bros., named Mario Bros. Classic, was based off this game rather than the NES original.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19881130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>4F4AAB3D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Kaettekita Mario Bros. (1988)(Nintendo).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kaettekita Mario Bros. (1988)(Nintendo).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kaettekita Mario Bros. (1988)(Nintendo).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88196" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kalin no Tsurugi (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Kalin no Tsurugi</name>
		<desc>Monsters have appeared in the once peaceful land of Alitania, and the people have fallen into terror. The king's orders have fallen upon you, the bravest knight of Alitania.

"The fate of the country hangs by a thread. It may be possible to save the country with Gladrif's magic, but he is nowhere to be found. Therefore, I want you to search for him! Find Gladrif, defeat the monsters, and restore peace to this land once again!"</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xtalsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Disk Original Group (DOG)</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9F80CB9B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Kalin no Tsurugi (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kalin no Tsurugi (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kalin no Tsurugi (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88197" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kamen Rider Black - Taiketsu Shadow Moon (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kamen Rider Black : Taiketsu Shadow Moon</name>
		<desc>The game is based on the Kamen Rider Black television series, which was the eight installment of the Kamen Rider superhero series.In the game, players take control of Kamen Rider Black, who must defeat numerous Gorgom mutants. There are five levels of four stages each. In the first four levels, players must complete three side scrolling stages with a boss at the end. In the fourth stage, the player must fight against a final level boss using a zoomed in perspective with larger sprites. The player gets to ride Battle Hopper motorcycle throughout the second and fourth levels. The fifth level is composed entirely of boss fights, first against three Evil Lords, and then against Shadow Moon. If the player loses against Shadow Moon, the bad ending is shown before the game ends.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880415T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>566C6DDF</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Kamen Rider Black - Taiketsu Shadow Moon (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kamen Rider Black - Taiketsu Shadow Moon (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kamen Rider Black - Taiketsu Shadow Moon (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98649" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kick and Run (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kick and Run</name>
		<desc>A soccer game based on the arcade game of the same name.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>23BEFAE6</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Kick and Run (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kick and Run (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kick and Run (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88199" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kick Challenger Air Foot - Yasai no Kuni no Ashi Senshi (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kick Challenger: Air Foot</name>
		<desc>Kick Challenger - Air Foot - Yasai no Kuni no Ashi Senshi  (lit. Kick Challenger: Air Foot: Vegetable Country Foot Soldier) is an action game developed by Vap for the Famicom Disk System and published in 1987. It is a single player game where the player takes control of a tomato as he marches upward through four stages in an effort to rescue his country from insects and other invaders.

You control the tomato by independently directing his two feet, one foot at a time. He make kick in eight directions with whichever foot is not planted in the ground at the given moment. Power ups are revealed by kicking trees, flowers, mushrooms, and other obstacles that are scattered throughout each stage. They may take the form of shoes which grant him the ability move on certain surfaces, or candy which gives him special abilities. Each stage has a "back side" which is accessed by stepping on holes in the ground reveal under kicked obstacles, and provide more power-ups to find.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vap</developer>
		<publisher>Vap</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>78A12D0A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Kick Challenger Air Foot - Yasai no Kuni no Ashi Senshi (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kick Challenger Air Foot - Yasai no Kuni no Ashi Senshi (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kick Challenger Air Foot - Yasai no Kuni no Ashi Senshi (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88200" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kieta Princess (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kieta Princess</name>
		<desc>The Kingdom of Rabia's princess goes missing during a visit to Japan, surrounding the investigation of the medicine to an "epidemic dementia," known as "Oninofuguri", and the prevention of its importing. The player takes the role of a detective determined to unravel the mystery of the missing princess Kilala, in this RPG style adventure game. Yasuko Tomita served as the model of one of the characters. Certain telephone numbers would appear, which, if called, would provide the player with a hint, spoken by Yasuko Tomita.

In order to track down Kobayashi, the criminal protagonist, you must visit five different towns and collect information. Neary every house and building can be entered, which was unique for its time. The game also features a high degree of freedom, allowing you to visit restaurants for a bite, or a Dojo to train, or to hunt for vegetation to sell for money, while you are looking for the princess.

Another introduced concept that was novel for its time was the notion of day and night changing the appearance of the city. During the evening, you may encounter a street gang, and they may open fire on you, although you can defend yourself with a revolver. However, if over 20 innocent people are gunned down, you will be arrested and sent to the police station where you must pay a fine and return to the starting point.

The degree of difficult throughout the game is considered quite high, with very few hints to help you out, while other hints are misleading. For example, one hint suggests that you if you sleep over night at a particular crossroad in a city, you will get a key item, but this hint is false. Although you are supposedly a detective, you never actually get to accuse anyone of a crime.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagineer</developer>
		<publisher>Wave Jack</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E57AD002</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Kieta Princess (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kieta Princess (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kieta Princess (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98650" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kiki Kaikai - Dotou Hen (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kikikai-kai : Dotou Hen</name>
		<desc>The game follows the adventures of "Sayo-chan", a young Shinto shrine maiden living in Feudal Japan. One night, while Sayo-chan is fanning a ceremonial fire, she is visited by the Seven Lucky Gods, who warn her of a great, impending danger. Suddenly, a band of mischievous goblins appear and kidnap the gods, quickly retreating to a faraway mountain range. Sayo-chan, determined to help the gods, sets off on a journey across the countryside, where she confronts a number of strange creatures from Japanese mythology, including yokai, obake, and yurei-like monsters. After defeating several powerful goblin leaders, Sayo must battle their leader, the ancient serpent Orochi.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>4C791779</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Kiki Kaikai - Dotou Hen (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kiki Kaikai - Dotou Hen (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kiki Kaikai - Dotou Hen (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88219" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kineko - Kinetic Connection - The Monitor Puzzle (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Kinetic Connection</name>
		<desc>A Disk Writer only release, The Monitor Puzzle Kinetic Connection - Kineco II is the sequel in which new puzzles are introduced. Like it's prequel the game challenges player to piece together ten images in a jigsaw puzzle like fashion. However, every piece is exactly the same size, and the images on the pieces move. Rather than using the shape of the edges to determine what pieces fit next to one another, you must use the animation on the pieces to determine their arrangement. When each puzzle begins, the pieces are also oriented randomly, so you may be required to flip them vertically or horizontally in order to complete the puzzle. There are 10 different animations, and you can choose between dividing the images into 16, 24, or 48 distinct pieces before attempting to solve the puzzle. Obviously, the fewer pieces, the easier it is to solve.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tamtex</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6833B0EB</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Kineko - Kinetic Connection - The Monitor Puzzle (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kineko - Kinetic Connection - The Monitor Puzzle (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kineko - Kinetic Connection - The Monitor Puzzle (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88204" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kobayashi Hitomi Shocking Tennis (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Kobayashi Hitomi Shocking Tennis</name>
		<desc>Kobayashi Hitomi Shocking Tennis is a tennis game for adults developed and published by Hacker International for the Famicom Disk System in 1990.
In this solo game, you play a game of tennis with the beautiful model Kobayashi Hitomi.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900708T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hacker International</developer>
		<publisher>Hacker International</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>187EC24C</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Kobayashi Hitomi Shocking Tennis (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kobayashi Hitomi Shocking Tennis (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kobayashi Hitomi Shocking Tennis (Japan) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88205" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Konamic Ice Hockey (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Konamic Ice Hockey</name>
		<desc>Blades of Steel, later released in Japan as Konamic Ice Hockey is an ice hockey video game released by Konami for North American arcades in 1987, and ported to the Family Computer Disk System and Nintendo Entertainment System in 1988. All teams are fictional but based out of real Canadian and American cities. The game is known for its fast paced hockey action and especially for the fighting. It is a one or two player game. When playing against the computer, there are three difficulty levels to choose from: Junior, College, and Pro (with Pro being the most difficult and Junior being the easiest). Each team consists of three forwards, two defense men, and a goaltender.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>FEF5125F</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Konamic Ice Hockey (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Konamic Ice Hockey (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Konamic Ice Hockey (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98653" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Konamic Tennis (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Konamic Tennis</name>
		<desc>Konamic Tennis is part of a long line of Konami sports games made specifically for the Famicom and its Famicom Disk System peripheral, which had previously used the term "Exciting" to signify its Konami status: As is the case with games such as Exciting Baseball or Exciting Basketball (known in the west as Double Dribble). Instead, this and future Konami sports games for the system would have the "Konamic" appellation; a portmanteau of "Konami" and "dynamic". At least, this is how the same pun in its original Japanese is commonly transliterated.

Konamic Tennis follows a similar design philosophy as other tennis games at the time (and would be used for most of the ones to follow) by depicting the action from behind the serving player's side of the court. It follows the rules of the sport precisely, with a single game usually ending after four successful volleys (scored as 15, 30, 40 and Game) and the first to win six games deciding a set. Players can choose between a single set match or a longer 3-set match. They can also play in a tournament or a single one-on-one game with a CPU (or human) opponent of their choosing.

One feature Konamic Tennis introduces to the genre is that of the serving view, shown as an inset whenever a player serves the ball to start a game. The goal is to hit the ball at precisely the right moment to serve an excellent shot; too early or too late will cause the player to either hit the net or send the ball too far, or simply not hit the ball at all. In all these cases, it counts as a foul and the player has one more chance to correctly serve the ball, otherwise points are awarded to the opponent.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880819T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>AC4ED201</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Konamic Tennis (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Konamic Tennis (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Konamic Tennis (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88206" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Koneko Monogatari - The Adventures of Chatran (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Koneko Monogatari : The Adventures of Chatran</name>
		<desc>Koneko Monogatari: The Adventures of Chatran is a game developed for the Family Computer Disk System in 1986 by Pony Canyon and the NES in 1987. It is actually a movie license title based on the cinema release of Koneko Monogatari, better known in the United States as The Adventures of Milo and The video game representation of this movie is quite different, and regretfully slow. It gives the player control over the kitten Milo, as he attempts to navigate through a side scrolling world of trees, hostile animals, and other obstacles. Milo plods along at a very slow pace, and can jump from tree branch to tree branch, popping fruit out from the leaves, which he must collect before they turn rotten and disappear. Every moving object from mice to beetles, is lethal to Milo and must be avoided. Fruit can be dropped on enemies for extra points. Eggs can be collected to use as weapons which must be dropped on enemies. Bottles of milk grant temporary invincibility. And if the player manages to collect four eggs that spell out the word HELP, Otis will appear to attack enemies that are headed Milo's way. However, touching Otis will also kill Milo..</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marionette Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>53A7A482</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Koneko Monogatari - The Adventures of Chatran (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Koneko Monogatari - The Adventures of Chatran (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Koneko Monogatari - The Adventures of Chatran (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88208" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Legend of Zelda 2, The - Link no Bouken (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Link no Bouken : The Legend of Zelda 2</name>
		<desc>Link no Bouken - The Legend of Zelda 2 is the second installment in The Legend of Zelda series, published by Nintendo for the Nintendo Entertainment System. It was originally released in Japan on the Famicom Disk System less than a year after the release of The Legend of Zelda. 

The Adventure of Link is a direct sequel to the original The Legend of Zelda, and again involves the protagonist Link on a quest to save Princess Zelda -- who is not the same Princess from the first game, but another member of the royal family by the same name, who was placed under a sleeping spell a long time ago. The Adventure of Link's emphasis on side-scrolling and RPG-style elements, however, was a significant departure from its predecessor and has given it a reputation as the "black sheep" of the Zelda series. It is arguably the hardest Zelda game. Despite this reputation, the game was highly successful and introduced many elements that would become commonplace in future Zelda games.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>ACEB8D17</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Legend of Zelda 2, The - Link no Bouken (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Legend of Zelda 2, The - Link no Bouken (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Legend of Zelda 2, The - Link no Bouken (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88215" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Meikyujin Dababa (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Meikyuu Jiin Dababa</name>
		<desc>The game takes place in India, where a young man's significant-other is kidnapped by an evil wizard. He must then tackle the four areas of the labyrinth temple of Dababa to rescue her.

In order to accomplish this task, the player cannot simple move across the floor. Rather, the player and all of the enemies hop from one square tile to another, throughout the game. In a majority of stages, the player must uncover the seals which will unlock the door to the next stage by leaping on to the particular tiles which keep the seals concealed. Not every door will take the player forward, however, as some doors are trick doors that may take the player to a previous stage. In some stages, the player must simply survive the onslaught of enemies, while in others, the player is racing against the clock.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870529T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>16321DCB</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Meikyujin Dababa (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Meikyujin Dababa (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Meikyujin Dababa (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88218" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Moero TwinBee - Cinnamon Hakase wo Sukue! (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Moero TwinBee : Cinnamon Hakase wo Sukue!</name>
		<desc>Moero TwinBee can be played by up to three player simultaneously: the first two players control TwinBee and WinBee (the ships from the previous game) using the standard Famicom controllers, whereas the third player controls GwinBee (a green ship) by connecting an additional controller into the console's expansion port. Unlike the original TwinBee, which only featured vertical-scrolling stages, Stinger adds side-scrolling stages to the mix as well. There are seven stages in the game. Stage 1, 3, and 7 are side-scrolling stages, while the rest are vertical-scrolling stages. The controls remain the same between the two styles of gameplay, with the only difference being that in the side-scrolling segments, the A button shoots hearts over the ship instead of dropping bombs into the ground like the vertical-scrolling segments, which helps the player keep the power-up bells afloat in the side-scrolling stages.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<hash>39F22B73</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Moero TwinBee - Cinnamon Hakase wo Sukue! (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Moero TwinBee - Cinnamon Hakase wo Sukue! (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Moero TwinBee - Cinnamon Hakase wo Sukue! (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88221" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Namida no Soukoban Special (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Namida no Soukoban Special</name>
		<desc>Namida no Soukoban Special (which roughly translates into Warehouse Keeper's Tears Special) is a game that was released for the Famicom Disk System in 1986 by ASCII Entertainment. By 1986, many of Japan's game players were familiar with Soukoban in one form or another since its introduction in 1982. Rather than publish yet another version of the same old game, ASCII attempted to enhance the Soukoban experience for its debut on the Famicom by providing players with a unique set of tools that let players "cheat" in some fashion in comparison to the original rules. Objects like Magnets and Pulleys provided players with a limited ability to pull boxes, something which the original versions of the game prohibited. Objects such as these, or pepper, or oil, were discovered by pushing certain boxes that hid the items underneath. Progress through the game could be saved to the disk to prevent forcing players to solve puzzles that had already been solved.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thinking Rabbit</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C0D538C0</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Namida no Soukoban Special (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Namida no Soukoban Special (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Namida no Soukoban Special (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88222" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Nazo no Kabe : Block Kuzushi</name>
		<desc>In the year 30XX, the mankind has exhausted all the metal resources on the Earth, so they had to travel into space in order to find more. They find a planet high in minerals, and they name it Selim.

But soon they discover that there is someone watching, spying on them; it's some kind of alien race. These aliens find a hole in the humans' main computer and get inside it. The computer, programmed to self-destruct in case of a failure, starts its countdown.

There is only one way to avoid self-destruction, which is entering a 14 digit code into the machine; but these digits are hidden in the walls of the corridors in the complex. Your mission is to find these letters and avoid self-destruction, aboard the "Red Warrior", and using your only weapon, an energy ball.

Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi  is an Arkanoid clone for the NES, but it's probably one of the most singular clones. You'll have to destroy all blocks but also the walls surrounding them, as the 14 letters are spread inside them, apart from killing the alien bosses here and there. In your way, you will find a bizarre mixture of enemies, from alien forms to parts of the body (eyes, lips, skulls...), who will make your game tougher by changing the direction of your ball; but also happier by dropping a sweet variety of power-ups such as the cherries (extra life), the clock (the enemies freeze), a rocket (to throw into the blocks), a fire device (the ball fires missiles), a parachute (slows the ball) an extra ball, or the weirdest of them all, the so-called Konami Man, who will take you to a secret parallel complex with different (and harder) levels.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>0D518DDC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Nazo no Kabe - Block Kuzushi (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88223" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Nazo no Murasame Jou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Nazo no Murasamejou</name>
		<desc>In feudal Japan, an evil alien descends upon Murasame castle and takes over a giant statue, which then continues to spread its influence over four neighbouring castles. The samurai apprentice Takamaru is thus summoned to recapture the castles and then take on the alien itself.

Nazo no Murasamejou is a fast-paced action game that has some similarities with The Legend of Zelda, although it is faster and has none of the RPG/Adventure elements. It is also much more linear: You fight through the castles one after the other, with each stage consisting of the path to the castle and the castle itself, where the boss is waiting.

Your have two weapons: (unlimited) shurikens for ranged attacks and a sword for melee combat. The sword is automatically used when you are close enough to an enemy, and it can also be used to deflect enemy shurikens. But since you are constantly under attack by ninjas from all directions and also have only a limited time to finish each stage, the game is still quite hard.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860414T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>FC2E653E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Nazo no Murasame Jou (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nazo no Murasame Jou (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Nazo no Murasame Jou (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="99381" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Nazoler Land Dai 3 Gou (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Nazoler Land : Dai 3 Gou</name>
		<desc>Nazoler Land Dai 3 Gou was the third and final "Magazine Disk" published by Sunsoft for the Famicom Disk System. This last disk was released in 1988. The full title of the disk is Nazo no Magazine Disk Nazoler Land Dai 3 Gou which translates as "Puzzle Magazine Disk Nazoler Land 3rd Issue." Rather than featuring one game, it contains a collection of 6 games which would be considered "mini-games." The player selects which game to play from the menu screen.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>4B781E6D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Nazoler Land Dai 3 Gou (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nazoler Land Dai 3 Gou (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Nazoler Land Dai 3 Gou (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="99382" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Nazoler Land Soukan Gou (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Nazoler Land : Soukan Gou</name>
		<desc>Nazoler Land Soukan Gou is the first in a series of minigame collections from SunSoft developed especially for Nintendo's Famicom Disk System peripheral. It was followed by two direct sequels and a quiz-based spin-off.

Nazoler Land Soukan Gou (or Nazoler Land Vol. 1) has eight minigames that the player can select from a menu after loading the game up and switching the disk around. These are:
Rotation Maze

A maze-like puzzle game where a small circular being has to pass through a maze filled with dividers. The player can only pass through these dividers if there is room for it to turn around, otherwise it blocks the player's progress. The goal is to find the correct path through the maze.
Nazoler Fortune-Telling

Despite using signs of the Zodiac and suggesting a fortune-telling aspect, the game is actually a variant on the classic strategy board game Mastermind: The goal is to find the right combination of Zodiac symbols, and the game will provide hints by reporting whenever the player includes the right symbol, either in the correct place (represented by a solid star) or the wrong place (represented as a hollowed star).
Super Jigsaw

In this game the player simply has to reconstruct an image after pieces of it have been jumbled up. All the player must do is use two cursors to point to the two pieces they wish to switch around. Restoring the image to its initial state completes the challenge.
Save Princess Momoko!

Promoted as the "major feature", or the most fully-developed of the minigames. The goal is to explore a dungeon in a first-person perspective, similar to classic dungeon crawlers such as Wizardry, Dungeon Master or Shining in the Darkness, while finding items and using the correct items on the right monsters to proceed past them. Encountering these monsters before finding the right item to defeat them causes the player to lose, so there's a degree of trial and error.
Japan's Best Surroundings: Ultra Travel Quiz

A quiz based on traveling around Japan and general geographical facts. The player selects which type of transportation (train, plane, etc.) they wish to take and answers questions relating to it.
Famicom Reaction Test

In this simple "game", two players compete to hit the button on their controller as many times as they can in the short time limit. This test is presented like a Wild West duel.
Extrusion Puzzle

Similar to Super Jigsaw, only the player is sliding blocks around to make a puzzle appear. Pushing one block that's against another causes all touching blocks to move at once.
3D Maze

A simple 3D maze, presented in the same first-person perspective as the Saving Princess Momoko game, though with a stark blue and white appearance. The goal is to simply find the way out.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>65285D1C</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Nazoler Land Soukan Gou (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nazoler Land Soukan Gou (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Nazoler Land Soukan Gou (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88229" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Omoikkiri Tanteidan Haado Gumi - Matenrou no Chousenjou (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Omoikkiri Tanteidan HaadoGumi : Matenrou no Chousenjou</name>
		<desc>Based upon a Japanese television series that aired in 1987. It features a group of five detective kids on a mission to retrieve various objects stolen by a mysterious thief who wears a golden mask. The group counts the leader Hiroshi, the cute and Aikido expert Yasuko who also happen to be the only girl of the group, Susumu, Satoru and Takeo. The mysterious thief uses many ingenious tricks to escape his pursuers, such as a huge and colorful air-balloon.nnBefore getting to the main portion of the game, the player must pass the organization's test. After entering personal information such as name, birth-date and blood type, the player must go through two challenges. The first one is a memory test. Eight character faces (from a list of four) appear at random on the screen and the player needs to remember the order in which they came in. The second test is action based and the player must catch roses thrown by the thief, himself hanging from an air-balloon. Once the tests are passed, the real game starts. Our hero can move around town and visit buildings to gather information. He can also use various items such as a slingshot, a metal detector, a radio, binoculars etc. Baddies also wander around the city and must be avoided. They can also be knocked down using any weapon our hero may carry (like the slingshot) or by punching them on the chin.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>CBCA97F5</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Omoikkiri Tanteidan Haado Gumi - Matenrou no Chousenjou (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Omoikkiri Tanteidan Haado Gumi - Matenrou no Chousenjou (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Omoikkiri Tanteidan Haado Gumi - Matenrou no Chousenjou (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88175" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Family Computer Othello (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Othello</name>
		<desc>Othello is a conversion of the board game. Each player tries to fill the game board with as many discs of his color as possible. On each turn the player places a disc on the board by selecting a location where the opponents discs will become trapped between two of his discs. The trapped discs are flipped over to the players color. The game ends when the board is filled or time runs out, and the player with the greatest number of his color discs on the board wins. Two players can play against each other, or one player against the computer.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861013T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Kawada, Co. Ltd</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>B60E66B3</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Family Computer Othello (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Family Computer Othello (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Family Computer Othello (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98665" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Otocky (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Otocky</name>
		<desc>Otocky can be described as a musical side-scrolling shoot 'em up. The player's spaceship has a ball for a weapon, which can be fired in eight directions; each direction corresponds to a different musical note. The note plays when the player presses the fire button, and is also quantized in time so that it matches the beat playing in the background. By using the weapon selectively the player can improvise music while playing.

Otocky is notable for being one of the first games that include creative/procedural generative music.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870327T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Scitron, Art SEDIC</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>31DC1C4A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Otocky (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Otocky (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Otocky (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98666" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pachi Com (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Pachicom</name>
		<desc>The game is based on standard pachinko rules, replicating the experience of playing pachinko in a parlor. The game board has a layout with nails sticking out. Metal balls would either of or fall in between the holes created by the pegs in order to traverse the board. Certain compartments are added to the board. Should a metal ball find its way to one of these compartments, the player will receive points that are similar to credits on a slot machine.[3] Players can expect to lose that ball (and a point) if it falls below the bottom of the board (similar to falling down a bottomless pit in an action game). Initially, the player starts off with one hundred balls.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19881004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shouei System</developer>
		<publisher>Toshiba-EMI Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>65E47753</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Pachi Com (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pachi Com (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pachi Com (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98667" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pachinko Grand Prix (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Pachinko GP</name>
		<desc>Pachinko GP (or Pachinko Grand Prix) is a Pachinko simulator from Data East for the Famicom Disk System. The goal is to play Pachinko in various machines found in Pachinko parlors across Japan, attempting to reach a Pachinko ball target (the total grows each time the player successfully fires a ball into a point-scoring zone) before a time limit expires before they move onto the next machine.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19881118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9902AA6F</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Pachinko Grand Prix (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pachinko Grand Prix (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pachinko Grand Prix (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="99384" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pac-Man (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Pac-Man</name>
		<desc>The player controls Pac-Man through a maze, eating pac-dots. When all pac-dots are eaten, Pac-Man is taken to the next stage. Between some stages one of three intermission animations plays. Four enemies (Blinky, Pinky, Inky and Clyde) roam the maze, trying to catch Pac-Man. If an enemy touches Pac-Man, he loses a life. Whenever Pac-Man occupies the same tile as an enemy, he is considered to have collided with that ghost. When all lives have been lost, the game ends. 

Near the corners of the maze are four larger, flashing dots known as power pellets that provide Pac-Man with the temporary ability to eat the enemies. The enemies turn deep blue, reverse direction and usually move more slowly. When an enemy is eaten, its eyes remain and return to the center box where it is regenerated in its normal color. Blue enemies flash white to signal that they are about to become dangerous again and the length of time for which the enemies remain vulnerable varies from one stage to the next, generally becoming shorter as the game progresses. In later stages, the enemies go straight to flashing, bypassing blue, which means that they can only be eaten for a short amount of time, although they still reverse direction when a power pellet is eaten; in even later stages, the ghosts do not become edible (i.e., they do not change color and still make Pac-Man lose a life on contact), but they still reverse direction.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>E1C1C60D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Pac-Man (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pac-Man (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pac-Man (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88230" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor - Dai 2 Shoutai Shutsudou Seyo! (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Patlabor : The Mobile Police, Dai 2 Shoutai Shutsudou Seyo!</name>
		<desc>Patlabor - The Mobile Police - Dai 2 Shoutai Shutsudou Seyo is an action-platformer-shooter game from Bandai and yet another licensed game from the publishing giant. In this case, it is an adaptation of the anime and manga of the same name.

Patlabor is a portmanteau of "patrol" and "labor", with labor being the common name for technologically advanced mechanical walkers used by various construction companies to perform heavy-duty work that a human wouldn't be capable of achieving on their own. Because more and more of these labors are being hijacked by criminals, an equally powerful force of police-issued labors are commissioned and manned by members of the police force. The show follows Section 2 of the Mobile Police Patlabor division in particular.

The game is divided between side-scrolling platformer/run-and-gun levels and first-person shooter modes in which the player character, in their patlabor, must keep the peace by subduing criminals and other villains, some of which have their own labors.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Advance Communication Company</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>094ACC80</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor - Dai 2 Shoutai Shutsudou Seyo! (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor - Dai 2 Shoutai Shutsudou Seyo! (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor - Dai 2 Shoutai Shutsudou Seyo! (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98669" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pinball (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Pinball</name>
		<desc>Pinball is a game where the player controls the paddles of a virtual pinball machine. The game has two screens to represent the traditional pinball table and one for a bonus mode. Play begins when the player launches a ball with the plunger from the first screen?the bottom of the pinball table?through the top of the screen to the second screen. Play will move to the first screen if the ball falls through the bottom of the top screen and will return to the top screen if the ball is hit back through the space at the top of the first screen. The player controls the flippers on either screen to deflect the ball to keep it from falling off the bottom of the lower screen.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890530T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>5218D0A8</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Pinball (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pinball (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pinball (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98670" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pro Golfer Saru - Kage no Tournament (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Pro Golfer Saru : Kage no Tournament</name>
		<desc>Pro Golfer Saru: Kage no Tournament is a golf game with fantasy elements thrown in, developed by Bandai and published on the Family Computer Disk System in 1987. The game is based on a manga (Japanese comic book) known as Pro Golfer Saru published by Fujiko Fujio (also responsible for Doraemon) about a young cave man or neanderthal-like boy who desires to become the greatest golfer in history. To accomplish this goal, he trains in the most desolate of locations, driving golf balls over giant chasms in an effort to hit greens several hundred meters away.

The game is composed of a training mode as well as the tournament challenge. The first nine holes replicate the desolate, and almost prehistoric locations that Saru normally trains in. Balls must be driven over wide spaces in order to stay in bounds and continue play. The back nine holes take place is a more modern, and even slightly futuristic locale, where Saru must sink balls from across rooftops. The game will save one players performance to disk. It was never released outside of Japan.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870525T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<hash>8261910E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Pro Golfer Saru - Kage no Tournament (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pro Golfer Saru - Kage no Tournament (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pro Golfer Saru - Kage no Tournament (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88231" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Professional Mahjong Goku (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Professional Mahjong Gokuu</name>
		<desc>Professional Mahjong Gokuu is the third game for the Famicom to be based on Mahjong, the competitive tile game popular in China and Japan. It is a four-person version of the game, which is generally how the game is played in real life, though uncommon in simulations during this era due to the additional computing power needed for three AI opponents.

As a "professional" Mahjong game, there is an opportunity to play a mode where the player can gamble on outcomes beforehand. The amount of cash gained or lost is usually based on the quality of the winning hand, but occasionally the player can also make bets to increase their take should they win (though, of course, any money gambled in this way is lost if someone else wins the hand).</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chat Noir</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>4B684FCA</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Professional Mahjong Goku (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Professional Mahjong Goku (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Professional Mahjong Goku (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98671" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pro Wrestling - Famicom Wrestling Association (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Puroresu Famicom Wrestling Association</name>
		<desc>The player chooses a wrestler with unique skills and presses various combinations of buttons to use different wrestling moves. It is possible to leave the ring; however, a player who does so must re-enter the ring before the referee's 20-count. Failure to do so results in a loss (via count-out) or a draw (double count-out), if both wrestlers fail to re-enter in time. (Note: The referee's count is broken only after both wrestlers have re-entered the ring. That is, as long as at least one wrestler is outside the ring, the referee's count continues. Moreover, it is possible for a wrestler to be counted out while executing a "plancha" if he has crossed the ring ropes by the count of 20.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861013T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>D870EBCC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Pro Wrestling - Famicom Wrestling Association (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pro Wrestling - Famicom Wrestling Association (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pro Wrestling - Famicom Wrestling Association (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98674" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Puzzle Boys (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Puzzle Boys</name>
		<desc>A puzzle game in which you must control a potato character and navigate mazes by pushing blocks and solving puzzles to rescue his vegetable friends in a deep labyrinth.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19901116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>4A9C34DB</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Puzzle Boys (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Puzzle Boys (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Puzzle Boys (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98675" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Radical Bomber!! Jirai-kun (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Radical Bomber!! Jirai-kun</name>
		<desc>Radical Bomber!! Jirai-kun FDS is a strategy game developed and published by Jaleco for the Famicom Disk System in 1988. The environment of the game resembles a giant board game where each player moves from one space to another. The goal of Radical Bomber is to carefully think out a plan of action and find a way to trap the opponents by removing connections between each "square" on the map. Successfully isolating an opponent from the rest of the board causes them to forfeit the game. If you manage to isolate every every opponent, Jirai-kun will advance the next level. This game was only released in Japan, and has never been translated from its original Japanese language.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880729T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>592D32BB</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Radical Bomber!! Jirai-kun (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Radical Bomber!! Jirai-kun (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Radical Bomber!! Jirai-kun (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98676" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Reflect World (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Reflect World</name>
		<desc>Reflect World is a hybrid RPG/Shooter developed by East Cube for the Family Computer Disk System. It is the only game developed by East Cube for any console.

You fly around a planet collecting various items to advance to different areas.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>East Cube</developer>
		<publisher>East Cube</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E269FCA3</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Reflect World (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Reflect World (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Reflect World (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98677" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Relics - Ankoku Yousai (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Relics : Ankoku Yousai</name>
		<desc>At some point in the early history of earth, the forces of darkness known as HELL were at war with the forces of light known as HEAVEN, and the took this battle to our planet. The HELL forces quickly enslaved human beings, and the earth was cast in darkness and despair. Somewhere on the planet, a fortress was built to harness the power of the sun in order to defeat the forces of HELL, should they ever come to our planet, but it fell into ruin after centuries of neglect. The Shining Princess of HEAVEN was captured and imprisoned on the top floor of this fortress. Also inside are the spirits of the Holy Warriors of Light who have the power to defeat the forces of HELL. However, they are asleep and unable to awaken. Earth's only hope is you, a being who has sacrificed his body in order to inhabit the fallen bodies of the departed. To succeed, you must use each body to obtain the key words which are found in, and used to open, the dungeons of the fortress.nnRelics: Ankoku Yosai (Lit. "Relics: Darkness Fort") is an action-adventure game developed by Bothtec for play on the Family Computer Disk System and published in 1987. It is somewhat related to, but entirely different from, a game known as Relics which was released on several popular Japanese home computer formats, including the MSX. In the game, you control a spirit who has the ability to enhabit the body of certain defeated enemies, effectively powering up by inhabiting the body of stronger foes.nn</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870410T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bothtec</developer>
		<publisher>Bothtec</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>16465E46</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Relics - Ankoku Yousai (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Relics - Ankoku Yousai (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Relics - Ankoku Yousai (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98678" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Replicart (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Replicart</name>
		<desc>The game takes place at the end of the 21st century. A gigantic snake-like alien called Sonada invades Earth and constructs a base under the soil. Sonada attacks various locations, stealing precious resources, and appears invulnerable to all forms of modern offenses. Engineers regroup and construct a base where a new weapon can be developed. They create the Replicart in the image of Sonada, and give it the power to convert resources into new material that can extend the Replicart and increase its strength until it reaches enough power to destroy the invader.

Replicart is to the original Snake game what Arkanoid is to Breakout; an upgrade that takes the core features of the game and expands upon them by adding enemies, power-ups and more elaborate play settings. In it you must move a robotic snake through mazes in an effort to collect a required number of pieces before the exit will open. The snake's length extends by one unit for every piece collected. If the snake's head touches any of the walls, enemies or its own body, it is destroyed and the player loses one life.

The conversion to the Famicom Disk System by Taito is quite different than the MSX2 original. The number of levels has been reduced to 100, but between every 10 levels, a boss battle occurs in which the player must chase a monster around the screen and blast it until the monster takes enough damage. A bonus level is provided for the player after each boss is defeated before they progress to the next level.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dual</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C3CBC847</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Replicart (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Replicart (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Replicart (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98679" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Roger Rabbit (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Roger Rabbit</name>
		<desc>Help Roger Rabbit collect hearts in various levels and save Jessica Rabbit while avoiding the dastardly weasels! This was eventually released in the US as Bugs Bunny's Crazy Castle and changed the hearts to carrots and the weasels into various characters from Looney Tunes. This was due to Kemco losing the rights to Roger Rabbit in the US.

While presented in a side-scroller format, Roger Rabbit differed from standard side-scrollers such as Super Mario Bros. in that Roger Rabbit did not have a jump function; therefore, only by taking different routes could Roger avoid enemies. Some of the levels had boxing gloves, invincibility potions, safes, crates, flower pots, or ten-pound weights that could be used against the enemies in the game. As a result, the game had a "puzzle-solving" atmosphere.

Players score 100 points for every carrot with the last one in each floor giving the player an extra life, 100 points for every enemy defeated using invincibility bottles, 500 points per enemy using boxing glove and 1000 points per enemy that gets hit with heavy objects.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>33CF8AE8</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Roger Rabbit (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Roger Rabbit (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Roger Rabbit (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88243" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Samurai Sword (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Samurai Sword</name>
		<desc>Samurai Sword is an adventure game developed and published by Capcom for the Famicom Disk System in Japan towards the end of 1988. The player is an unnamed hero who is promptly defeated by the game's antangonist Soron and whisked away before the moment of his demise in order to find a way to counter Soron's considerable magical might.

While the game may resemble an RPG at first, it is actually a traditional Famicom adventure game, similar to Portopia Renzoku Satsujin Jiken or Princess Tomato in the Salad Kingdom. The player can select from a set of commands for the hero to follow such as looking around, talking to NPCs, picking up items and so on. While there are battles, they can only be resolved by finding the right command (often the right spell) rather than the standard RPG method of exchanging blows governed by various statistics.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19881115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F5420F86</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Samurai Sword (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Samurai Sword (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Samurai Sword (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88244" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Santa Claus no Takarabako (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Santa Claus no Takarabako</name>
		<desc>Santa Claus no Takarabako (Lit. Santa Claus' treasure chest) is a Christmas themed party game. There are two modes to play: creating a Christmas card and or playing a few party games with friends. While you can play with it by yourself, it was not particular designed for that.

The four games are Poker Dice, Roulette, Slot Machine, and Bingo.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Musical Plan</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D58BB23A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Santa Claus no Takarabako (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Santa Claus no Takarabako (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Santa Claus no Takarabako (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="97407" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SD Gundam World - Gachapon Senshi - Scramble Wars (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>SD Gundam World : Gachapon Senshi, Scramble Wars</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>71436896</hash>
		<image>./mixart/SD Gundam World - Gachapon Senshi - Scramble Wars (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/SD Gundam World - Gachapon Senshi - Scramble Wars (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/SD Gundam World - Gachapon Senshi - Scramble Wars (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88245" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Seiken Psycho Calibur - Maju no Mori Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Seiken: Psycho Calibur</name>
		<desc>Many years ago there was a country called Earth Maral. One day it was invaded by the forces of the Dark World and torn apart. People lived in fear, there only hope a legend?nn'A hero holding a sword will appear and restore peace to our land once again.'nnNo one knew when this hero would arrive?nnSaid the devil beast: "What's that? You challenge me? I see. Very well then. I accept your challenge. However, you will never win!"nnSeiken Psycho Calibur: Maju no Mori Densetsu is an adventure game for the Famicom Disk System, developed by Imagineer and published in 1987. It is part of the Wave Jack series of games produced by Imagineer that come with more accessories than the average video game, including a story book and audio cassette tape.nnSeiken Psycho Calibur is, in many ways, an attempt to copy the success of The Legend of Zelda. However, it fails to inspire the same level of wonder and fascination. It also lacks a good degree of polish that made the afore mentioned title so great. Nevertheless, Seiken Psycho Calibur is a relatively fun game to play, as long as you have a fair degree of insight into how the game is played. There are some unintuitive aspects of the game that can make progress in the game quite difficult.nnFor example, you begin the game in a town which offers a variety of goods for sale, but you only receive so much money, and you can never return to the town once you leave. Therefore, what you decide to invest your money in has a substantial impact on the difficulty of the game early on. Many items can be bought for less money later on, but only if you know the location of the hidden shops that contain them. Other less obvious points in the game require a bit of back tracking from later areas to earlier areas in order to acquire items that allow you to proceed, and boss battles that are at times incredibly difficult.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870519T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>C-Lab</developer>
		<publisher>Wave Jack</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>747FD83C</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Seiken Psycho Calibur - Maju no Mori Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Seiken Psycho Calibur - Maju no Mori Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Seiken Psycho Calibur - Maju no Mori Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="99389" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Silvania - Ai Ippai no Boukensha (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Silviana : Ai Ippai no Little Angel</name>
		<desc>Sylviana lived with her mom in relative peace after her father passed away. One day, her mom came down with a mysterious illness. Despite everything Sylviana tried, her mother's condition only got worse. Then one day, she heard a rumor about a Dr. Doppler, who can create a medicine that will cure any disease. She decides to head out and find this Dr. Doppler, and convince him to give her the medicine. However, she soon finds out that the doctor is unable to help her, due to having had his eight treasures stolen from him by demons. Sylviana vows to return the treasures to him in exchange for the medicine.nnThe game borrows it's combat system from games like Hydlide and Ys: Ancient Ys Vanished, where damage is inflicted upon (and exchanged with) enemies by crashing into them. However, there are no levels or experience points, so Sylviana's power only grows by virtue of the improved equipment that she purchases or finds. Throughout the game, the player wanders around a world map in order to find towns where goods may be purchased, and caves or towers which must be explored to find treasure. Eventually, the player enters a cave and steps through a mirror to enter the mirror image of the original world map, with increased difficulty.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pack-In-Video Co., Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Pack-In-Video Co., Ltd</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F42B45D8</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Silvania - Ai Ippai no Boukensha (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Silvania - Ai Ippai no Boukensha (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Silvania - Ai Ippai no Boukensha (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88249" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Smash Ping Pong (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Smash Ping Pong</name>
		<desc>Smash Ping Pong simulates the game of ping-pong or table tennis in a remarkably different manner than prior simulations of any variety of tennis. Rather than putting the emphasis on precise control and placement of the paddle in order to return the ball, the emphasis is on timing and strategic control of the ball's speed and trajectory. The player sees no other on-screen representation of themselves beyond a hand holding a paddle. The hand and the paddle automatically move left and right to match the horizontal position of the ball. Players need only concern themselves with the timing of their paddle swing, and the style of swing to use. Players can choose between three different swings, along with the choice of forehand or backhand. 

The Famicom Disk System conversion was developed by Konami, and published directly by Nintendo as Smash Ping Pong. As a result,Konami's penguin mascot Pentarou was replaced by Diskun, the Famicom Disk System mascot, on the title screen, and Donkey Kong Jr. appears in the stands on the right side. The conversion offers several variations of play, including one or two player games, plays to 11 or 21 points, and five levels of difficulty. Additionally, Deuce win conditions do not end at 15 points, but can climb as high as 99 points.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>D4DAAFFC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Smash Ping Pong (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Smash Ping Pong (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Smash Ping Pong (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88250" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Soccer (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Soccer</name>
		<desc>Soccer is an action game for two players or one player against the computer. You can play the game in one of five skill levels, choose from several different teams, and select the amount of time the match will take. Soccer features throw-ins, goal kicks, corner kicks, penalty kicks and an overhead view of the field which scrolls to follow the action.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>D2139DEC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Soccer (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Soccer (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Soccer (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98681" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Solomon no Kagi (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Solomon no Kagi</name>
		<desc>The main character, named Dana, is sent to retrieve "Solomon's Key" to restore the world to light from demons that were accidentally released. The object of the game is to advance through the 50 rooms of "Constellation Space" by acquiring a key to the door that leads to the next room before a timer runs out. The game incorporates elements of the platform shooter genre. Dana can run, jump, create or destroy orange blocks adjacent to him as well as create fireballs to destroy demons. The orange blocks can also be destroyed by hitting them with the character's head twice. Along the way Dana can acquire items to upgrade his firepower and extra lives as well as items that award bonus points and unlock hidden rooms. With certain items, Dana must make, then break blocks (sometimes in a certain manner) to make these appear.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>FE281A8E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Solomon no Kagi (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Solomon no Kagi (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Solomon no Kagi (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98682" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Suishou no Ryuu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Suishou no Ryuu</name>
		<desc>"last transmission mentioned a so-called crystal dragon"
That dragon intercepted a shuttle bearing my friends Cynthia and Nial. Where could it have taken them? There's got to be a clue somewhere.
"Are you sure it wasn't a hallucination?"</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Disk Original Group (DOG)</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F106F568</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Suishou no Ryuu (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Suishou no Ryuu (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Suishou no Ryuu (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88252" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Boy Allan (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Boy Allan</name>
		<desc>In the game, Allan Colada journeys from his home in the foothills into the mountains to retrieve a remedy for his sister Leela's fever.

Super Boy Allan is the second game in Sunsoft's "Intelligence Game" edutainment series for the Famicom Disk System, featuring two different game modes.

The first game mode, which is also the main game, the player has to avoid contact with enemies and push logs in order to solve math-based problems to get extra items. Solving math problems also increases your ability to move several logs at once, which is needed to make further progress.

The second, and much simpler game mode, has the player to finish a 39-steps marathon run by correctly answering simple math questions to accumulate as many points as possible.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870327T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>72F6194B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Super Boy Allan (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Boy Allan (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Super Boy Allan (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88254" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Lode Runner II (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Lode Runner II</name>
		<desc>The second compilation of levels from Irem's Lode Runner Arcade series. Developed for the Famicom Disk System, it was never released outside of Japan.
Irem created four Arcade versions of the original Lode Runner, each with a unique set of levels as well as added features like a co-operative mode for two players. For the FDS home versions, Irem compiled several levels from each of these Arcade versions onto one disk. Super Lode Runner II has fewer single-player levels than its predecessor, but contains more co-op levels to make up for it.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>40D11036</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Super Lode Runner II (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Lode Runner II (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Super Lode Runner II (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88253" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Lode Runner (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Lode Runner</name>
		<desc>Douglas E. Smith's Lode Runner was introduced to Japan in 1983 on various popular Japanese home computer platforms, including the MSX, Sharp X1, and NEC PC family computers. Hudson Soft licensed the rights to bring the game to Nintendo's Famicom, and it was released in 1984 as one of the first 3rd party games ever made for the system and it was an incredible hit. Around the same time, Irem licensed the rights to produce an arcade version of Lode Runner which they also released in 1984, along with three other sequels through 1986. These arcade versions made a few tweaks to the original game play, and the final arcade game introduced a two player cooperative mode.

In 1987, Irem decided to package a number of select stages from all four of the arcade games into one title, and released it in disk format for the Famicom Disk System, entitled Super Lode Runner. Though the graphics were not quite as good as the arcade games, they were close, and Irem brought many of the game play changes to Famicom players, including the new two player mode. Irem released a sequel later on that same year. A different version of the game was released for the MSX with the same title.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>9064ECCD</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Super Lode Runner (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Lode Runner (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Super Lode Runner (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88256" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Mario Bros. 2 (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. 2</name>
		<desc>Originally released in Japan as Super Mario Bros.® 2, this game has previously made only brief cameo appearances in the Western hemisphere. Mario fans will appreciate the familiar look and feel of the game, while finding that its updated game play creates an entirely new challenge. No longer content just to wear different-colored overalls, Mario and Luigi also possess different skill sets (Mario can stop quicker, while Luigi can jump higher). In addition to the classic enemies already known to fans worldwide, there are also Poison Mushrooms, backward Warp Zones, and the occasional wind gust (which can help or hinder your progress) to take into account. And if that?s somehow not enough, expert players can go looking for the game?s secret worlds. So get ready to put your Mario skills to the ultimate test, and save the Princess again. Just don?t be surprised if she?s in another castle!</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19860603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>077B1892</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Super Mario Bros. 2 (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Mario Bros. 2 (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Super Mario Bros. 2 (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88255" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Mario Bros. (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros.</name>
		<desc>Do you have what it takes to save the Mushroom Princess?

You'll have to think fast and move even faster to complete this quest! The Mushroom Princess is being held captive by the evil Koopa tribe of turtles. It's up to you to rescue her from the clutches of the Koopa King before time runs out. But it won't be easy. To get to the princess, you'll have to climb mountains, cross seas, avoid bottomless pits, fight off turtle soldiers and a host of black magic traps that only a Koopa King can devise. It's another non-stop adventure from the SUPER MARIO BROTHERS!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
		<hash>CD1D8CE3</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Super Mario Bros. (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Mario Bros. (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Super Mario Bros. (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98683" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tama &amp; Friends - 3 Choume Dai Bouken (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Tama &amp; Friends : 3 Choume Daibouken</name>
		<desc>The game is based on a manga and anime for children of the same name that concerns the cats and dogs of a close-knit neighborhood. 



The game has a subtitle: 3 Choume Daibouken. The "3 Choume" part refers to the district in which Tama and his friends live, while "Daibouken" simply means "great adventure".



As a game, Tama and Friends is very basic, and quite clearly meant for very young children. The goal is to simply walk right across a suburban environment while avoiding enemies like birds and random flying junk. Tama can also climb telegraph poles to help him get higher, which occasionally lead to bonus areas, and there are also bosses to be fought at the end of certain stages.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Advance Communication Company</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash />
		<image>./mixart/Tama &amp; Friends - 3 Choume Dai Bouken (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tama &amp; Friends - 3 Choume Dai Bouken (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Tama &amp; Friends - 3 Choume Dai Bouken (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88257" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tanigawa Kouji no Shougi Shinan II - Meijin heno Michi (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Tanigawa Kouji no Shougi Shinan II : Meijin e no Michi</name>
		<desc>Shogi, a Japanese board game similar to chess, is a board game as popular as Mahjong in Japan. Tanigawa Kouji no Shougi Shinan II - Meijin e no Michi  is the second in a series of instructional Shogi games hosted by then-top tier champion and expert Shogi player Tanigawa Kouji to help improve the player's game.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pony Canyon, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>60BD6A81</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Tanigawa Kouji no Shougi Shinan II - Meijin heno Michi (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tanigawa Kouji no Shougi Shinan II - Meijin heno Michi (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Tanigawa Kouji no Shougi Shinan II - Meijin heno Michi (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88258" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tennis (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Tennis</name>
		<desc>The game features single-player and two-player modes for singles and doubles matches, with either competitive or cooperative gameplay. A computerized opponent's artificial intelligence can be set to one of five difficulty levels. Mario referees the matches.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>CB9A1BA3</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Tennis (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tennis (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Tennis (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98691" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tobidase Daisakusen (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Tobidase Daisakusen</name>
		<desc>Tobidase Daisakusen was developed by Square in 1987 and was published by DOG, a now-defunct label of Square. The North American release, which was the first Square game to reach American shores, was published by Acclaim Entertainment, Inc. for the NES under the name The 3-D Worldrunner.

The gameplay can best be described as an attempt to merge Super Mario Bros. game mechanics with Space Harrier's third person perspective. In the game, the player assumes the role of Jack, a wild "space cowboy" on a mission to save various planets overrun by serpent-like beasts. The game takes place in Solar System #517, which is being overrun by a race of aliens known as Serpentbeasts, who are led by the evil Grax. As WorldRunner, the player must battle through eight planets to destroy Grax. For its time, the game was technically advanced; the game's three dimensional scrolling effect is very similar to the linescroll effects used by Pole Position and many racing games of the day.

Part of the appeal and selling point of 3-D WorldRunner was its "3-D mode," and it was the first of three games by Square to feature such an option (the other two being JJ, the sequel to 3-D WorldRunner, and Rad Racer). When the 3-D mode is selected, the game uses computer image processing techniques to combine images from two slightly different viewpoints into a single image, known as anaglyph images. The game was packaged with cardboard "anaglyph glasses," which use red and cyan color filters to moderate the light reaching each eye to create the illusion of a three dimensional image.

Tobidase Daisakusen was designed by Hironobu Sakaguchi, Nobuo Uematsu, and Nasir Gebelli, all whom would later rise to fame as core members of the team behind the popular RPG Final Fantasy. The three also developed JJ - Tobidase Daisakusen Part II, the sequel to 3-D WorldRunner.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870312T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Disk Original Group (DOG)</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>95546107</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Tobidase Daisakusen (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tobidase Daisakusen (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Tobidase Daisakusen (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98692" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Topple Zip (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Topple Zip</name>
		<desc>Topple Zip is a vertically scrolling shooter that is also labeled as a race game. The player pilots an air craft and flies in competition against several computer controlled craft. In addition to firing upon your opponents, you may ram into them (and they may ram into you) and dislodge a power-up from them which you can then shoot and collect. There are eight distinct scenes, each of which contain a number of warps which link to other scenes. How the scenes connect is random on each play through. The goal is to locate the key which is necessary to access to warp which leads to the eight and final scene, collect it from whichever scene it is hidden inside of, and access the eighth scene before any other competitor.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871009T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bothtec</developer>
		<publisher>Bothtec</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7BF73C75</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Topple Zip (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Topple Zip (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Topple Zip (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98693" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Transformers - The Headmasters (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Transformers : The Headmasters</name>
		<desc>Transformers: The Headmasters is a 1987 Family Computer Disk System game by Takara based on the popular cartoon series of the same name and released only in Japan. The game stars the Autobot Headmasters as the protagonists and playable characters. The game is infamous for its high level of difficulty and off-key background music.

You play as one of the Autobot Headmaster through four planets, fighting the Decepticons. Unlike it predecessor, Transformers: Convoy no Nazo, players cannot switch between robot and vehicle mode. Instead, each level contains an initial vehicle mode stage, followed by a robot mode stage. Players start out with only Chromedome. They can switch between Autobots at any time, but only if that Autobot has been collected. Players must rescue them throughout the game, as they will be flown in by helicopter in the vehicle mode stage, or found in one of the rooms of the robot mode stage. Since Headmasters was developed for the FDS, it contains a save game feature similar to those found in early The Legend of Zelda and Metroid games.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Takara</developer>
		<publisher>Takara</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3B46DBBF</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Transformers - The Headmasters (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Transformers - The Headmasters (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Transformers - The Headmasters (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88263" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./TwinBee (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>TwinBee</name>
		<desc>TwinBee can be played by up to 2-players simultaneously. The player takes control of a cartoon-like anthropomorphic spacecraft, with Player 1 taking control of TwinBee, the titular ship, while Player 2 controls WinBee. The game controls consists of a joystick and two buttons: one for shooting enemies in the air and the other for dropping bombs to ground enemies (similarly to Xevious).

The player's primary power-ups are bells that can be uncovered by shooting at the floating clouds where they're hidden. If the player continues shooting the bell after it appears, it will change into one of four other colors: the regular yellow bells only grant bonus points, the white bell will upgrade the player's gun into a twin cannon, the blue bell increases the player's speed (for up to five speed levels), the green bell will allow the player to create image copies of its ship for additional firepower, and the red bell will provide the player's ship a barrier that allows it to sustain more damage. The green and red bells cannot be combined together. Other power-ups can also be retrieved from ground enemies such as an alternate bell that gives the player's ship a three-way gun, a star which eliminates all on-screen enemies.

As with other games of the same genre, getting shot by a single enemy bullet will cause the player to lose a life. However, if the bullet only strikes either side of the ship instead, the player's ship will only lose one of its arms. If the player's ship loses both arms, it will lose the ability to throw bombs and the player must wait for an ambulance to arrive. The player must navigate their ship to the ambulance to repair their arms. However, if the player's ship loses both arms for the second time, no ambulance will arrive.

If two players are playing at the same time, they can align their ships vertically or horizontally together to perform more powerful attacks</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
		<hash>3688F585</hash>
		<image>./mixart/TwinBee (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/TwinBee (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/TwinBee (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88264" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ultraman 2 - Shutsugeki Katokutai!! (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Ultraman 2 : Shutsugeki Katoku Tai</name>
		<desc>Ultraman 2: Shutsugeki Katoku Tai!! (Loosely translated as Ultraman 2: Sortie Department Group) is an action game developed by Bandai for the Famicom Disk System and published at the end of 1987. As the title implies, it revolves around the Ultraman series that was popular in Japan. However, rather than making Ultraman the focus of this game, it is the defense support team that goes into action whenever Japan is attacked by a giant monster which gets the majority of the game time.

The game takes place in modern Japan, with a bird's eye view presentation of much of Japan's metropolis. Players must send a team out to search for, and obtain, a cube which permits the defense team to damage monsters when they appear. Once the cube is found, monsters begin to appear and attack the buildings of Japan. The team must deploy vehicles to help aid in the destruction of these monsters until they have all been defeated. If a monster destroys a critical building, the game is instantly over.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8F7F0352</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Ultraman 2 - Shutsugeki Katokutai!! (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ultraman 2 - Shutsugeki Katokutai!! (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ultraman 2 - Shutsugeki Katokutai!! (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="1557" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Volleyball (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Volleyball</name>
		<desc>Slam the perfect serve. Spike the game-winning point. Make the save that saves the game! It's all up to you. Because you call the shots in Nintendo VOLLEYBALL. You'll start by selecting a team from the country of your choice. As Captain, you'll lead your team through a fast-paced warm-up round, then quickly move into the heat of real volleyball competition. You'll decide when to spike, when to lob, when to make a diving save - everything just like the captain of a real volleyball team! Play against a friend or challenge the computer. Either way, Nintendo's true-to-life graphics and realistic game play will bring all the fun and excitement of voleyball right into your home!</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19870301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>A3D2307C</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Volleyball (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Volleyball (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Volleyball (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88266" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Vs. Excitebike (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Vs. Excitebike</name>
		<desc>Vs. Excitebike is a motorcross racing simulation game developed by Nintendo as a sequel to Excitebike for the Famicom Disk System. It was also released in the arcades but the Famicom Disk System is arguably better with additional features.  It comes with some improved features, including a simultaneous two player mode that the original game lacked, and an improved track save system (the tracks were saved to the writable portion of the disk). The music is completely different; none of the songs from the original game are present in this version, and a background theme is played during gameplay. There is also a new bonus round that has you jumping over trucks.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19881209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>69050650</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Vs. Excitebike (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Vs. Excitebike (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Vs. Excitebike (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88267" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wakusei Aton Gaiden (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Wakusei Aton Gaiden</name>
		<desc>Wakusei Aton Gaiden ("Planet Aton Side-Story") is a vertical-scrolling shoot 'em up that was created by the Japanese National Tax Agency (Kokuzeichou) in order to teach children and older players about the issues surrounding Japan's bubble economy by way of a sci-fi themed parable. The story concerns the eponymous planet Aton and two young pilots who attempt to save it from some sort of economy-based crisis - one that just so happens to manifests itself as an alien invasion. The game can be played by one or two players, with player one assuming the role of the male pilot Kanta while the second player assumes the role of the female pilot Yuki.

The game was made accessible to players via a system not unlike the Disk Writer service, though presumably as a government-funded game it was made freely available. It is thought that copies were given away at some manner of a Japanese tax awareness convention or from an educational group that went to various schools across the country to lecture students. As with many Disk Writer exclusive games, it is extremely difficult for modern day Famicom collectors to find.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kokuzeichou</developer>
		<publisher>Kokuzeichou</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>2437FA88</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Wakusei Aton Gaiden (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wakusei Aton Gaiden (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wakusei Aton Gaiden (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98696" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wardner no Mori (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Wardner no Mori</name>
		<desc>Wardner no Mori  (Lit. Forest of Warnder) is a platform style arcade game developed by Toaplan and released by Taito in 1987. In America, the arcade game was released under the title Pyros. The player controls a character by the name of Dover through various forest stages in an attempt to save his kidnapped girlfriend from the evil Wardner. The simple run and jump controls are supplemented with the ability to throw balls of fire. Gold coins can be collected throughout the game and exchanged for extra abilities in a shop at the end of each level.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9D9B3FED</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Wardner no Mori (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wardner no Mori (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wardner no Mori (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98697" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Winter Games (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Winter Games</name>
		<desc>Winter Games is a sports game developed by Epyx based on sports featured in the Winter Olympic Games. A snow-and-ice themed follow-up to the highly successful Summer Games.

The game was presented as a virtual multi-sport carnival called the "Epyx Winter Games" (there was no official IOC licensing in place) with up to 2 players each choosing a country to represent, and then taking turns competing in various events to try for a medal.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870327T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epyx, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>DA2A3EA4</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Winter Games (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Winter Games (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Winter Games (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98699" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Xevious (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Xevious</name>
		<desc>Xevious tells the story of the fight between humankind and the biocomputer GAMP, which controls the alien forces of planet Xevious. It turns out that the Xevious inhabitants are originally from Earth, and GAMP (General Artificial Matrix Producer) is the product of an ancient civilization that prospered on earth a hundred thousand years ago. During this golden age, the Gamps were human clones used in heavy labor, until they rebelled to their own creators. In order to survive the upcoming Ice Age, they planned to leave earth and migrate in search of a new homeland. They finally selected seven planets that were likely suitable to human life.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>CA9E574E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Xevious (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Xevious (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Xevious (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88270" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Yu Maze (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Yuu Maze</name>
		<desc>Yuu Maze ("Maze Play") is a single-screen maze game akin to Namco's classic Pac-Man and its many other imitators in that the goal of the game is to drive the futuristic vehicle around a maze collecting dots while avoiding (or temporarily eliminating) the enemies. Taito, one of the largest manufacturers of Arcade games at the time (not to mention the creators of Space Invaders), would produce similarly Arcade-reminiscent games for the system in order to tap into the portion of the market nostalgic for classic Arcade experiences.Yuu Maze adds a few innovations to the format: Each maze has a different structure, different enemies and different lay-outs for the pellets that are required to complete the level; the player can find power-ups which grant weapons, shields and speed-ups to their vehicle. The player's vehicle also has some degree of inertia: There's a slight delay when attempting to accelerate after stopping or performing a U-turn, but if the player keeps moving and changes direction only at 90 degree intervals, they can keep moving at their maximum speed. This is often necessary to keep ahead of the fast moving enemies.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19881028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Daiei Seisakusho</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>21B0A8C6</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Yu Maze (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Yu Maze (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Yu Maze (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="98701" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Zanac (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Zanac</name>
		<desc>In Zanac, the player controls the spaceship AFX-6502 Zanac as it flies through various planets, space stations, and outer space and through an armada of enemies comprising the defenses of the game's main antagonist?the "System." The player must fight through twelve levels and destroy the System and its defenses. The objective is to shoot down enemies and projectiles and accumulate points. Players start with three lives, and they lose a life if they get hit by an enemy or projectile. After losing a life, gameplay continues with the player reappearing on the screen and losing all previously accumulated power-ups; the player remains temporarily invincible for a moment upon reappearing on the screen. The game ends when all the player's lives have been lost or after completing the twelfth and final area. However, the player can earn 1-ups (extra lives) throughout the game by accumulating high point scores. Zanac has a continue option which allows players to restart the game from the level in which they lost all their lives.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>349B244B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Zanac (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Zanac (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Zanac (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="88273" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Zelda no Densetsu : The Hyrule Fantasy</name>
		<desc>A small kingdom in the land of Hyrule, the setting of the game, is engulfed in chaos after an army led by Ganon, the Prince of Darkness, invaded it and stole the Triforce of Power, a part of a magical artifact bestowing great strength. In an attempt to prevent Ganon from acquiring the Triforce of Wisdom, another of the pieces, Princess Zelda splits it and hides the eight fragments in secret dungeons throughout the land. Before the princess is eventually kidnapped by Ganon, she commands her nursemaid Impa to find someone courageous enough to save the kingdom. While wandering the land, the old woman is surrounded by Ganon's henchmen, though a young boy named Link appears and rescues her.  After hearing Impa's plea, he resolves to save Zelda and sets out to reassemble the scattered fragments of the Triforce of Wisdom, to become powerful enough to defeat Ganon.

The Legend of Zelda incorporates elements of action, adventure, and role-playing games. The player controls Link from a flip-screen overhead perspective as he travels in the overworld, a large outdoor map with varied environments. Link begins the game armed only with a small shield, but a sword becomes available to Link after he ventures into a cave that is accessible from the game's first map screen. Throughout the game, various characters aid Link by giving or selling equipment and clues. These people can be found in caves scattered throughout the overworld; some are readily accessible, while others are hidden behind obstacles such as rocks, trees, and waterfalls

Nintendo originally released the game as the launch title for the Family Computer's new Disk System peripheral. The Legend of Zelda was joined by a re-release of Super Mario Bros., Tennis, Baseball, Golf, Soccer, and Mahjong in its introduction of the Disk System. It made full use of the Disk Card media's advantages over traditional ROM cartridges with a disk size of 128 kilobytes, which was expensive to produce on cartridge format. Due to the still-limited amount of space on the disk, however, it was only in katakana. Rather than passwords, it used rewritable disks to save the game. It used the extra sound channel provided by the Disk System for certain sound effects; most notable are the sounds of Link's sword when his health is full, the roars and growls of dungeon bosses, and enemy death sounds. The sound effects used the Famicom's PCM channel in the cartridge version. It also used the microphone built into the Famicom's controller that was not included in the NES. This led to confusion in the U.S. as the instruction manual reads that Pols Voice, a rabbit-like enemy in the game, "hates loud noise". Blowing or shouting into the Famicom's microphone kills these creatures. However, they cannot be killed through use of the recorder, and on the NES must be killed with weapons.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7DDE918E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Akumajou Dracula II - Noroi no Fuuin (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Akumajou Dracula II: Noroi no Fuuin</name>
		<desc>The game's setting takes place seven years after the original Castlevania. The prologue begins when Simon visits his family's resting ground. His back is critically injured from his last encounter with Dracula in the previous game. He suddenly feels someone's presence, and turns to see a young woman standing within the mist. She tells him that a curse was placed upon him by Dracula during their last battle, and that he does not have long to live. The woman continues to say that the curse can be undone if he resurrects Dracula himself. She further explains that Dracula's body was split into five different parts after his defeat seven years ago, and Simon must recover these and bring them to the ruins of Dracula's castle. There, he must seal Dracula and defeat him. Before disappearing, the unknown woman says she cannot guarantee that this will destroy Dracula permanently.

Dracula II - Noroi no Fuuin (Lit. "Dracula II: The Seal of the Curse") is an action-adventure game produced by Konami. It was originally released for the Family Computer Disk System in Japan in 1987, and for the NES in North America in 1988. It is the second Castlevania title released for the NES, following the original Castlevania. Set in 1698, seven years after the events of the first installment, the player once again assumes the role of vampire hunter Simon Belmont, who is on a journey to undo a curse placed on him by Dracula at the end of their previous encounter. Small differences exist between the Japanese version and the American version. Specifically the Japanese version takes advantage of the expanded FM processing capabilities of the FDS hardware to produce better sound, but it contains load scenes when entering or exiting any town or mansion. The FDS version also has three save slots instead of the NES password system.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Akumajou Dracula II - Noroi no Fuuin (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Akumajou Dracula II - Noroi no Fuuin (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Akumajou Dracula II - Noroi no Fuuin (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870827T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./All Night Nippon Super Mario Bros. (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>All Night Nippon Super Mario Brothers</name>
		<desc>All Night Nippon - Super Mario Bros. was a promotional item given out as a contest prize by the Japanese radio show "All Night Nippon" to celebrate its twentieth year on the air. It combines levels from both Super Mario Bros 1 &amp; 2 and also changes graphics of items and their placements as well as graphics of enemies and mushroom retainers to members of the show.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/All Night Nippon Super Mario Bros. (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/All Night Nippon Super Mario Bros. (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/All Night Nippon Super Mario Bros. (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Fuji Television Network</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yumekoujou - Doki Doki Panic (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Yume Koujou Doki Doki Panic</name>
		<desc>Yume Koujou Doki Doki Panic  (translated as "Dream Factory: Heart-Pounding Panic") is a Japan-only video game developed by Nintendo in cooperation with Fuji Television for the Family Computer Disk System to promote its event called Yume Koujou '87 (translates to Dream Factory '87).

It was later released outside of Japan in an altered format under the name Super Mario Bros. 2, since the original Japanese Super Mario Bros. sequel, Super Mario Bros.: The Lost Levels, was deemed too similar to the original and too difficult for overseas players. Eventually, the altered Mario version of Doki Doki Panic was released in Japan as well, under the title Super Mario USA. 

The story starts with two chidren, the young twins Piki and Poki, peacefully reading a story book. However, they accidentally tear off the last page of the book - little did they know that the book is actually magic! The evil Mamu suddenly appears, and his huge three-fingered hand pulls them into a quirky dream world. 

The goal of Doki Doki Panic is to help the whole family (namely Imajin, Lina and their parents Mama and Papa) rescue their poor children kidnaped by the evil king lizard. Each member has its own strengths and weaknesses - Imaji is a balanced character whereas Lina is fairly light weight and can effortlessly hover and fly over short distances, but she is really slow at picking up items. Papa is the strongest of the group and can throw enemies and items really far, whereas Mama can jump higher than anyone. As aforementioned, each character can carry enemies, items, and especially radishes and other vegetables that can be pulled out of the ground and used as lethal weapons. The game features a myriad of other items, such as bombs (self explanatory), Power blocks (similar to Mario Bros's POW blocks that kill all enemies on screen), Stars (temporary invincibility), keys (to unlock doors), Hearts (extra health) or the mysterious magic lamps that open doors to the Dark World - mirror areas where our heroes can find special items or heart containers. 

Doki Doki Panic follows a story book structure, and is made out of seven chapters (areas) and twenty pages (levels). Interestingly, although the player can play the Doki Doki Panic with any character, it has to eventually defeat the evil Mamu with all four to finally beat the game (the player can separately save each character's progress).</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Yumekoujou - Doki Doki Panic (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Yumekoujou - Doki Doki Panic (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Yumekoujou - Doki Doki Panic (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Fuji Television Network</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nazoler Land Dai 2 Gou (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Nazoler Land : Dai 2 Gou</name>
		<desc>Nazoler Land Dai 2 Gou was the second of three "Magazine Disks" published by Sunsoft for the Famicom Disk System in the middle of 1987. The full title of the disk is Nazo no Magazine Disk Nazoler Land Dai 2 Gou which translates as "Puzzle Magazine Disk Nazoler Land 2nd Issue." Rather than featuring one game, it contains a collection of 6 games which would be considered "mini-games." The player selects which game to play from the menu screen.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Nazoler Land Dai 2 Gou (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Nazoler Land Dai 2 Gou (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nazoler Land Dai 2 Gou (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870612T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Putt Putt Golf (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Putt Putt Golf</name>
		<desc>Putt Putt Golf by Pack-In-Video is one of many golf games for the Famicom and the Famicom Disk System, but one of the few to take players through an abstract world rather than an approximation of a real golf course. The goal of each stage is to reach the hole on the green and pot the ball in as few strokes as possible, but each of the courses are covered with various obstacles - some animated, some stationary. The player must navigate around them (or use them to their advantage, in some cases) in order to achieve the best score.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Putt Putt Golf (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Putt Putt Golf (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Putt Putt Golf (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pack-In-Video Co., Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Pack-In-Video Co., Ltd</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dr. Chaos - Jigoku no Tobira (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Dr. Chaos : Jigoku no Tobira</name>
		<desc>Dr. Chaos is a side-scrolling action adventure developped by Marionette and published by Pony Canyon. The genius scientist Dr Ginn Chaos has gone missing. Before his disappearance, he was actively working in his large mansion on a device allowing access to alternate dimensions. Armed only with a knife, his brother decides to look for him and ultimately unveil the mystery behind the incident. Something obviously went terribly wrong with Dr. Chaos's experiment, and the goal of the game is to locate all the eleven dimensional warp-zones hidden within the mansion, as well as assembling a powerful laser gun, the only weapon capable of taking down the last boss.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dr. Chaos - Jigoku no Tobira (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dr. Chaos - Jigoku no Tobira (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dr. Chaos - Jigoku no Tobira (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marionette Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon, Inc.</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bubble Bobble (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Bubble Bobble</name>
		<desc>The game stars the twin Bubble Dragons Bub and Bob in an action-platform game in which players travel through one hundred different stages, busting and pushing bubbles, avoiding enemies and collecting a variety of items. The main goal of the game is to rescue Bub and Bob's girlfriends from monsters. In the game, each player controls one of the two Bubble Dragons, Bub and Bob. The player can move along platforms, as well as jump to those above and to the side, similar to most platform games. The dragons can blow bubbles. These can trap enemies, who are defeated if the bubble is then burst by the player's spiny back. The bubbles also float for a time before bursting, and can be jumped on, allowing access to otherwise inaccessible areas. Players progress to the next level once all enemies on the current level are defeated.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Bubble Bobble (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Bubble Bobble (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bubble Bobble (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gun.Smoke (1988)(Capcom)[a].zip</path>
		<name>Gun.Smoke</name>
		<desc>The objective is to free the town of Hicksville from the band of criminals known as the Wingates. But in order to capture their most dangerous henchmen, in each stage the player must retrieve a Wanted sign of said henchman, otherwise it is impossible to clear the stage. In this game, the main character is a bounty hunter named Billy Bob.

Although virtually identical to the NES version, the FDS version featured several differences:

This game, like virtually all other FDS games, feature load times.

The font is similar to what is used in most Capcom games on the Famicom/NES. However, on the NES version, the font is changed to the military-font, also seen in the arcade version.

"In America" is changed to "In 1849".
Bandit Bill's mugshot on the wanted poster is slightly different in both versions of the game. In the FDS version, his shirt has an open collar, with part of his body showing. In the NES version, his shirt has a scarf around it. On top of that, the mugshots for the wanted posters originally had an Anime look, whereas in the NES version, they had a realistic look.

In this version, the shopping music features less instruments. Also, many of the tunes featured in the NES version are nowhere to be found in this version, and instead recycle the same music for certain scenes in the game. This is due to the limited memory space in FDS disk cards.

There is no game demonstration like there is in the NES version.

After beating the game the first two times, the player is rewarded with a Japanese message that tells the player to try the game again. After the third time, the player will be rewarded with a simple message that says "THE END". The Japanese message was thrown out in the NES version, instead of being translated into English.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Gun.Smoke (1988)(Capcom)[a].png</image>
		<video>./snap/Gun.Smoke (1988)(Capcom)[a].mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gun.Smoke (1988)(Capcom)[a].png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Knight Move (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Knight Move</name>
		<desc>The game is based around the concept of how a knight piece is moved in the game of chess. The player controls a knight chess piece that is constantly jumping and must continually choose which of the possible legal moves to make before the knight lands back on the board.

When the knight lands on any square on the board, it turns from white to light teal. Landing there again, turns it dark teal. Landing there yet again destroys the square altogether, leaving a hole that the player must avoid. Falling in a hole will result in a game over. Consecutively creating several holes results in a chain increasing the player's score in differing increments.

At the beginning of each "round", a heart is placed somewhere on the board. A heart (or multiple hearts) must be collected to advance to the next round, which thereby replaces all holes on the board with new white squares and places a new heart somewhere on the board. Depending on the game mode, hearts will sometimes move themselves every few jumps of the knight.

The player can also gather a small amount of extra points, at any time, by holding the A button and speeding up the knight's movement. The main objective in Knight Move is to continue this cycle, despite the increasing game speed, and reach the highest score possible.

The game also includes a simultaneous 2 player versus mode similar to the single player modes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Knight Move (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Knight Move (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Knight Move (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900605T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JV Dialog</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Section-Z (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Section-Z</name>
		<desc>An enemy space fortress of the Balangool Empire is approaching Earth. Captain Commando has to infiltrate it and find his way to Section-Z to destroy L-Brain, the computer controlling the fortress.nnSecton-Z is a side-scrolling game in which the player is a space soldier who can land on the ground and other platform structures and run along them. It is one of the first games which gives players the ability to not only shoot forward, but backwards. It is also one of the first games to give players a choice of paths at the end of each level. Depending on which path they took, they could get special weapons or bombs which wouldn't show up if the other path was taken. To compensate for this, the path without the weapon is often easier. They can activate these special weapons by pressing Select.nnSometimes, one of the paths will be flashing red instead of the usual yellow. This indicates that it is impassable unless the player locates and destroys the Generator Boss that is creating the field. Therefore, it is imperative to find the right paths through the fortress to get to the Generator and blow it up. Once this is done, it is possible to safely pass through the red gates and move onto the rest of the area, and eventually, the area boss. Each time a generator is destroyed the player will earn a capsule that increases total HP.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Section-Z (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Section-Z (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Section-Z (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870525T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wrecking Crew (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Wrecking Crew</name>
		<desc>The player controls Mario (or Luigi in two-player mode) and attempts to destroy all of a certain set of objects with a large hammer on each of 100 levels. Mario cannot jump because of the hammer's weight. The player can select any level to start on from the title screen. Each level takes place on a playfield divided into an invisible grid, each space of which can contain one object. Objects include destructible walls, pillars, and ladders, indestructible barrels and ladders, bombs that destroy all connected destructible objects, and various enemies that Mario must avoid. Doors may also exist, which can be opened to cause enemies to move harmlessly into the background. The game also introduced a new character, a construction foreman named Spike (believed to be an early version of Wario), who chases Mario and attempts to disrupt him by knocking down objects and causing him to fall to the bottom of the playfield. The player starts the game with five lives and loses a life whenever Mario comes in contact with an enemy or fireball. The game is over when all lives are lost. The game can also be aborted at any time, and must be aborted if Mario becomes trapped in a barrel.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Wrecking Crew (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Wrecking Crew (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wrecking Crew (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Rock (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Fire Rock</name>
		<desc>Fire Rock is an action game developed for the Famicom Disk System by System Sacom, and published in Japan by Use in 1988. The design of the game is credited to Mark Flint. In the game, the player controls what appears to be a cave man, whose goal is to navigate a series of item filled caverns in an effort to locate the boss of the level, defeat it, and then locate the door which leads to the next level. The game is commonly sited as having very poor controls, often requiring the player to grab hold of a wall, and very slowly climb it by holding up and tapping jump repeatedly. Other issues include a very low jump that places more platforms and items out of reach, and a difficult time bringing the character back under control if he starts to slip. This game was not released outside of Japan.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fire Rock (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fire Rock (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fire Rock (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860620T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>System Sacom</developer>
		<publisher>Use Corporation</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ice Hockey (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Ice Hockey</name>
		<desc>The play and mechanics of Ice Hockey are mostly similar to that of ice hockey in real life. The objective for both team is to hit a black puck with a hockey stick that each player carries into the opponent's goal. Teams are made up of five players including the goaltender, as opposed to six in real life. Players wear ice skates, which are used to skate across the icy arena. Each game is made up of three periods, with the victory going to the team who has the most points at the end of the game. At the beginning, two opposing players from each team face off in the middle of the rink. There are three kinds of players - the first is fast, weak, and feeble, but is good at the face-off; the second is average in all qualities, and the third is slow and poor at the face-off, but very powerful, both in body checking and shooting strength. The arena is similarly designed to a real-world ice hockey arena. The arena is coated in ice, with a goal on either side of the arena. There are a variety of marked areas, including the goal line that the puck must cross to score, the attacking/defending zone which is situated closely to each goal, the face-off spot, the neutral spot, and others. Each side of the arena has exactly the same design. If two opposing players fight for the puck for a certain amount of time, other players join into the fight, resulting in the player from the losing team in the fight to be put in the penalty box for a period of time.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ice Hockey (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ice Hockey (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ice Hockey (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Moonball Magic (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Moon Ball Magic</name>
		<desc>The game starts out by depositing the pinball in the middle of a simulated pinball table. However, once the ball is shot into one of the holes on the play field, the game enters an elaborate intro sequence which the player can control. The game contains 11 stages, each of which contain a target hole that the player must hit the ball into in order to advance to the next stage. The stages get more elaborate, and more moving obstacles appear to interfere with the behavior of the ball. In addition to controlling the flippers, the control pad can also be used to "nudge" the ball in either direction, although the effectiveness of this varies.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Moonball Magic (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Moonball Magic (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Moonball Magic (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>System Sacom</developer>
		<publisher>Disk Original Group (DOG)</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Karate Champ (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Karate Champ</name>
		<desc>The player assumes the role of a karate competitor and fights against another player or the computer. Using two joysticks, players can execute a number of moves.

Gameplay consists of a two dimensional fight between Karate characters wearing white and red gi, followed by various bonus rounds for the successful player. This pattern repeats itself in the next, more challenging round set against a new background. Unlike most later fighter-type games, there are no health bar or hit points. A hit successfully landed ends the round and earns the player or his opponent either one point or half point (along with a numeric score for the top ten but this has no effect on winning a match per se). The first to score two points is the winner. If the player loses a battle, the game ends. The game also featured some early speech synthesis, in which the judge would call out such phrases as "Fight!" or "Winner!" It's also spoken in Japanese in the Japanese version.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Karate Champ (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Karate Champ (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Karate Champ (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Ai Senshi Nicol</name>
		<desc>Help the brave inventor Nicol rescue his kidnapped girlfriend Stella from a Demon Bull King from the planet Dairass in this overhead action game. Control Nicol through 7 continents as he recovers 3 pieces on each level to his dimensional transporter invention that the Demon King stole and encased in diamonds. You'll blast away at various minions and avoid treacherous terrain while exploring multiple floors of each continent searching out the diamonds to be re-united with Stella and defeat the evil Demon King!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19870424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Big Challenge! Dogfight Spirit (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Big Challenge! Dogfight Spirit</name>
		<desc>Big Challenge! Dogfight Spirit is a vertical scrolling shoot 'em up in which the player controls a blue helicopter fighting against waves of enemy vehicles and ground turrets. Each mission takes the helicopter to a different part of the world, each with a distinctive if chromatically plain visual style.

The game's power-ups, available by destroying smaller supply trucks driving across the screen, change the helicopter's weapons but do not make them stronger. It's even possible to collect the weaker original weapon again if the player is too careless. These range from a stronger forward-firing cannon (or laser) to guns that spread fire forwards and to the sides of the helicopter.

You can beat it more than once with enemies taking more hits on subsequent playthroughs.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Big Challenge! Dogfight Spirit (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Big Challenge! Dogfight Spirit (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Big Challenge! Dogfight Spirit (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19881021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Eggerland - Souzou heno Tabidachi (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Eggerland: Souzou heno Tabidachi</name>
		<desc>Souzou he no Tabidachi translates to "Departure to Creation." Like with "Revival of the Labyrinth" before, this is a fitting description of the game itself. It references the fact that it brings the Creation Mode from the original back to the series, after it was abandoned in the previous two installments. It further resembles the first title in that it's also one of the most basic entries in the franchise, and among the easiest of the Japanese releases. It's also tied for the shortest game in the entire series, with just fifty puzzles in all. Given that the predecessors all had a hundred or more, this might seems like a problem, but the caliber of the puzzles is as high as ever. So if you found the prequels to be a bit overwhelming, then this might be the best of the early titles to start with. Interestingly, this seems to have been one of the FDS titles that were available solely from Disk Writer machines, as it doesn't appear to have ever been released at retail.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Eggerland - Souzou heno Tabidachi (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Eggerland - Souzou heno Tabidachi (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Eggerland - Souzou heno Tabidachi (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880820T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Bam (Japan).zip</path>
		<name>Fire Bam</name>
		<desc>Bam is a fifteen years old courageous boy. Like every boy his age, Bam must pass the village's test and bring back an insect's shell from the forest. But as he returns, and to his surprise, most of the village has been destroyed and his parents turned into demons. Armed with his sword, Bam sets forth in search of what happened to the village and his parents.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fire Bam (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fire Bam (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fire Bam (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Youkai Yashiki (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
		<name>Youkai Yashiki</name>
		<desc>In Youkai Yashiki, you control a boy armed with a flashlight who must explore five stages and locate five talisman before locating and gaining access to a stage boss. The flashlight serves as a weapon against the monsters which inhabit each stage. Your life meter takes the form of a set of batteries. As your life diminishes, the batteries drain and the power of your flashlight, that is the distance that the beams can travel, decreases.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Youkai Yashiki (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Youkai Yashiki (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Youkai Yashiki (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Casio</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
	</game>
</gameList>
