<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>ZX Spectrum</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game id="44503" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Deathchase (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>3D Deathchase</name>
		<desc>3D Deathchase sees you riding a motorcycle through 14 stages, with the aim of shooting out a succession of riders. Each stage starts with 2 bikes to shoot out, although planes and tanks also appear on the horizon, to be shot for bonus points. You start with 3 bikes and an infinite supply of bullets, with one bike lost every time you crash.

The levels are tree-lined, and at top speed it can be terrifying as you try to muscle through the gaps so as not to lose distance on the target bike. Every second level is played out at night, which changes the colour scheme.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mervyn J. Estcourt, R.B.</developer>
		<publisher>Micromega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>CCA317B6</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Deathchase (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Deathchase (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44583" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Ant Attack (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Ant Attack</name>
		<desc>An early isometric game that predates Ultimate's classic Knight Lore by a year. Used what it called the "softsolid 3d" algorithm to represent a large scrolling city from a switchable isometric perspective. The city, identified in the inlay blurb as Antescher, a combination of Ant and Escher, the famous visual paradox artist, is teeming with deadly giant ants. The player controls a boy or a girl and races around the city trying to find his/her lost half while jumping on structures to avoid the ants, or fighting the insects by either jumping on them or throwing grenades.

Ant Attack, like most games of its time, was created almost solely by a single programmer, who also designed the graphics and sound. This game had a unique visual appeal in a time before isometric action-adventures became all the rage.
</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quicksilva Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Quicksilva Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F6BA8828</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Ant Attack (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ant Attack (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ant Attack (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44600" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Arkanoid II - Revenge of Doh (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Arkanoid II: Revenge of Doh</name>
		<desc>Revenge of Doh is a direct sequel to the original arcade smash Arkanoid. Along with improved graphic engine, better sound and music, better hardware support and more levels, Revenge of Doh also features a built-in editor and allows you to create your own level sets!

Revenge of Doh continues Arkanoid's plot as follows, directly taken (including typoes) from the game:

A long time period passed and the dimension controlling force Doh has again come back to life. Occupying the huge starship Xorg, it has entered our universe from a different dimension. Mixtec, Arkanoid type spaceship, has lauched the craft Vaus II to make a preemptive attack on Xorg.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3E3A0B62</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Arkanoid II - Revenge of Doh (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Arkanoid II - Revenge of Doh (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Arkanoid II - Revenge of Doh (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44606" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Asterix and the Magic Cauldron (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Asterix and the Magic Cauldron</name>
		<desc>Goscinny and Uderzos cartoon characters are from the only Gaullish village in 50BC able to resist the Roman invasion. They can do this due to Getafix the druids magic potion, however the cauldron used to make this has been smashed into several pieces. Can brave Asterix and overweight Obelix find the pieces?

In this arcade adventure, it all comes down to you. The fifty screens you must explore take in your home village, a Roman encampment, and the forests in between. You have five pieces of wild boar, and these are used as you become hungry. 

Contact with wild boars or Roman soldiers triggers a one-on-one fight with punches and kicks. Defeating a boar earns you another piece of food, to restore energy once all lives are gone. Some sections are blocked until you collect their keys.

In the US version the character Asterix was replaced by a barbarian and the game's title was changed to Ardok the Barbarian.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software Pty., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>027D7533</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Asterix and the Magic Cauldron (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Asterix and the Magic Cauldron (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Asterix and the Magic Cauldron (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="132796" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Astro Blaster (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Astro Blaster</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>John Edwards, Glenn Flood</developer>
		<publisher>Quicksilva</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>5296C1BF</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Astro Blaster (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Astro Blaster (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44611" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Atic Atac (1983)(Ultimate).tzx</path>
		<name>Atic Atac</name>
		<desc>As the game begins, you fall through a trapdoor and end up inside an evil castle with only one way to get out of it - find all the pieces of the great ACG key that lets you unlock the main door.

Many problems lie on your way to freedom, however - not only is the castle pretty big and spread out over several floors, it is also littered with enemies that must be avoided or dispensed of. For some doors, you need keys to open them.

This game pioneered in several ways - the mix of fast-paced action and exploration of the large castle with little "puzzles" was innovative at that time, and you got to choose a character class, each one with its own weapon and skills - each class had different secret routes and shortcuts through the castle.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>28B3AD66</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Atic Atac (1983)(Ultimate).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Atic Atac (1983)(Ultimate).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Atic Atac (1983)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44615" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Auf Wiedersehen Monty (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Auf Wiedersehen Monty</name>
		<desc>In Monty On the Run the intrepid coal thief Monty Mole fled to the rocky island of Gibraltar. However, the Intermole agency is on to him, and his only hope of escape is to trek across Europe, collecting enough cash to buy the Greek island of Montoss and live there in luxury.

This is Monty's third game, and the structure is similar to the previous two. It's platform and ladders based, with 80 screens each representing some area of Europe - the Eiffel Tower and the Leaning Tower of Pisa are among the identifiable landmarks. 

There are different ways of travelling through the levels - some bouncy platforms coupled with a new super-leap move allow for big progress to be made, while Monty can also suspend from the ceilings and dodge his way across. Monty can now fall without being hurt, although landing on water can cause multiple lives to be lost in quick succession.

There are many items to collect  - the most important are Eurocheques for money and airplane tickets. Once on a plane you must fight off the encroaching Intermole planes for extra points.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D78472BA</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Auf Wiedersehen Monty (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Auf Wiedersehen Monty (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Auf Wiedersehen Monty (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="134251" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Avalon (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Avalon</name>
		<desc>In 408 AD the Roman Empire is crumbling and the Romans have mostly left Britannia. you play Maroc the mage, a "Lore Seeker", who has set out to defeat Avelach, Lord of Chaos. You control Maroc's astral projection which can cast spells to achieve various parts of the quest, the objective is to advance in sixteen ranks by exploring the world and collecting spells and ultimately destroy the Lord of Chaos.

Maroc starts outside a castle where a spell descends upon him and projects his astral projection inside it. The projection can only act or move through the use of spells.The two basic spells are movement and servant spells. The move spell allows the projection to move around and the servant spell summons a spirit that can move about and collect objects or other spells for Maroc. Only up to four objects can be carried around at a time and there are around 220 locations on eight levels. Enemies will attack the projection and drain it's energy which can be replenished with a spell, if depleted the projection is destroyed and the game reverts to Maroc outside the castle, ready for another go.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graftgold Ltd, Steve Turner</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson Consultants</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>83FCC7F6</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Avalon (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Avalon (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44624" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Back to Skool (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Back to Skool</name>
		<desc>In this sequel to popular Skool Daze you once again you must try and save your own neck!

Having managed to steal your report during the last few skooldaze of term, you've spent the whole holiday forging teachers' signatures and handwriting to make yourself look like the brightest, sweetest natured, most helpful little soul ever to carry a satchel.... Now all you've got to do is get it back into the Headmasters's safe!

Back to Skool follows the same gameplay style as its predecessor, but this time the school is bigger (there's a girl's section to explore) and there's a larger cast of characters. There's also more to do this time around, with more objectives to complete before you can finish the game.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Serma Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>03542F69</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Back to Skool (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Back to Skool (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Back to Skool (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44647" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Batty (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Batty</name>
		<desc>Batty is influenced by Arkanoid's method of reviving the Breakout phenomenon. You control a paddle at the bottom of the screen, with the top half of the screen containing an arrangement of bricks, most of which can be destroyed. You must move the paddle left and right so as to make contact with a ball, and thus deflect it (using the walls at the sides strategically) into the bricks, some of which require multiple hits to destroy. Wipe the destructible bricks out, and you move on to the next level; fail to keep the ball in play and you lose one of your 5 lives.

Some destroyed bricks release power-up tokens, which must be 'caught' with the bat as they fall. Functions include multi-ball, a larger paddle, and the ability to 'catch' and relaunch the ball each time, which makes it a lot easier to gain access to precise bricks or areas.

Batty also has enemies flying around and dropping bombs towards you - the bombs cause your bat to stick for a second, perhaps costing a life. Many levels contain magnets at the top of the screen, which make the ball's path harder to predict. The two player mode gives each player access to half the playfield, so co-operation is required.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Elite Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Dennis Publishing</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>97DE1163</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Batty (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Batty (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Batty (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="135292" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bobby Bearing (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Bobby Bearing</name>
		<desc>Bobby Bearing is a young steel ball who lives in the land Technofear, carefully avoiding the dangerous Metaplanes. One day his evil cousin comes along and lures him and his four brothers directly into said Metaplanes and leaves them for good. So Bobby's quest of the day is to find his way home and rescue his brothers.

The Metaplanes are a big maze of isometric screens without scrolling. The main challenge is to find orientation in this maze with various dead ends and junctions; there are also lifts, magnets, air ducts and hidden switches to complicate matters. There are also enemies and traps to avoid, e.g. evil marbles, crushing blocks of stone or hard to navigate places with opportunities to fall off the screen.

When Bobby finds one of his brothers, Bobby has to roll him to the exit. There are no lives or energy bars to be found in this game: it simply has to be completed before time runs out. Dying or getting stunned by an enemy results in a time penalty. Similarly the player can easily restart a screen with a time penalty if he has manoeuvred himself into an unwinnable situation.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Robert Figgins, Trevor Figgins</developer>
		<publisher>The Edge Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B01C3C11</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Bobby Bearing (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bobby Bearing (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bobby Bearing (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44702" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomb Jack II (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Bomb Jack II</name>
		<desc>Having saved the world in the first game, Bomb Jack is out to collect as much gold as possible, which is lying on a number of ledges. These vary between open and shut - the open ones offer more points, and an extra life is on offer for collecting 10 in a row, so if possible the route should take in the open ones in order.

Gameplay differs from the original, in that Bombjack's movement is no longer free and self-propelled. Instead, he moves flick-style between ledges, so long as one is directly within one of the 4 compass directions. Baddies can be pushed off ledges, but this uses up some of Jack's limited energy.
</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Elite Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F6F26B15</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Bomb Jack II (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bomb Jack II (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bomb Jack II (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44701" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bomb Jack (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Bomb Jack</name>
		<desc>In Bomb Jack, the player controls Jack, who must collect all the bombs in order to complete the current round and go onto the next one. This sounds easy, right? Wrong! Making Jack's task difficult are numerous enemies such as birds, mummies, turtles, and orbs.

In each round, collecting a number of bombs results in a bonus coin appearing, and collecting this coin will make the player's score increase 2 to 4 times. More often than not, the "power ball" appears, and when you collect this, you can defeat enemies and have more time to collect all the bombs. There is also the "E" coin, which gives Jack one additional life, but rarely does this coin appear.

The more you progress through the game, the more difficult it becomes, as enemies travel more quickly to get you.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tehkan Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>1E8FE3EA</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Bomb Jack (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bomb Jack (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bomb Jack (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44714" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Boulder Dash II - Rockford's Riot (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Boulder Dash II: Rockford's Revenge</name>
		<desc>In part two of the "Boulder Dash" series, game design hasn't changed compared to part one, so you still have to mine diamonds while avoiding falling rocks and cave monsters of all sorts. As in part one, later levels become more difficult because many puzzle elements are added.
</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>First Star Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Prism Leisure Corporation Plc</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>50A64357</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Boulder Dash II - Rockford's Riot (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Boulder Dash II - Rockford's Riot (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Boulder Dash II - Rockford's Riot (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44713" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Boulder Dash III (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Boulder Dash III</name>
		<desc>The third part of the popular series, Boulder Dash III adds a sci-fi spin to the graphics (called MetalGrafik), with Rockford now wearing a spacesuit and running through a more futuristic setting.

Other than that, the 16 new scenarios are similar in gameplay to the levels of Boulder Dash I and II: Rockford still digs through a series of caves to retrieve diamonds. Once he has enough diamonds, a portal opens that takes him to the next stage. Obstacles in the caves include boulders, monsters which will kill Rockford upon touching them (but which can be eradicated by crushing them with falling boulders - some of the monsters then release a number of diamonds), and green slime that spreads through the entire cave and blocks pathways. Additionally, every level has a time limit. Several puzzle elements add variety to the game, such as walls which will turn falling boulders into diamonds.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>First Star Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Prism Leisure Corporation Plc</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>E312BD77</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Boulder Dash III (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Boulder Dash III (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Boulder Dash III (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44711" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Boulder Dash (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Boulder Dash</name>
		<desc>You're Rockford and have to dig through monster infested caves in search of diamonds. In each level you must collect a certain number of these diamonds, in order to open a portal to the next stage. Enemies can be squashed by falling boulders, which are released when the ground below them is removed or they are pushed onto empty ground, but be careful because these can also squash you. In later levels, difficulty is increased by many puzzle elements and shorter time limits.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>First Star Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>K-Tel International (UK) Ltd</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>76C21AFA</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Boulder Dash (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Boulder Dash (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Boulder Dash (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44716" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bounder (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Bounder</name>
		<desc>In Bounder, the player controls a tennis ball that constantly bounces on the screen. 

The player has to move the ball around between two bounces so it lands on friendly areas like grass or the main hexagonal-patterned floor. If it lands  hazardous areas like spikes and sand, or hits the enemies which move around, one of the seven lives the player starts with is lost. There are beneficial squares though - arrows which keep the ball in the air longer or teleports which clear part of the game. 

The 174 screens are divided into 10 levels - at the end of each of these there's a bonus screen.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8B29473F</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Bounder (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bounder (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bounder (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44717" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bounty Bob Strikes Back (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Bounty Bob Strikes Back!</name>
		<desc>Bounty Bob Strikes Back! is the sequel to Miner 2049er and features similar gameplay. As Bounty Bob, your goal is to claim every inch of 25 challenging mines. To do this, you must walk over each segment of the framework in the mines. To reach each segment of framework, you will need to figure out a way to jump, climb, or use one of the many devices occasionally available to get there. To you help you get around (or sometimes hinder progress) are ladders, slides, suction tubes, cannons, transporters, and other devices. Wandering about the mines are many dangerous mutants. If you come in contact with one of these, you will lose a life. Scattered throughout each mine are special food items; collect one of these, and you will temporarily be able to eliminate the mutants by walking into them. You will need to figure out a unique strategy for each level in order to complete it, plus there is a time limit so claim all the territory quickly!
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Big Five Software</developer>
		<publisher>Big Five Software|U.S. Gold Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6EE587B9</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Bounty Bob Strikes Back (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bounty Bob Strikes Back (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bounty Bob Strikes Back (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44728" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Bubble Bobble (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Bubble Bobble</name>
		<desc>Bubble Bobble is the story of two humans, Bub and Bob who wander into the mysterious cave of monsters and magically turn into dinosaurs. The only way to transform back is to reach the end of the cave...

Bubble Bobble is a platform game, with each level being a single screen. The enemies must be cleared from a level to go to the next one. With one player controlling Bub and the other controlling Bob, the player can jump and collect items for points (such as fruit). The real power Bub and Bob have however is the ability to blow bubbles. These bubbles can be as platforms to leap on, or to trap enemies. Enemies trapped in a bubble must be popped by jumping into them, wherein they'll turn to fruit. Additionally, power-ups sometimes float by in bubbles. They include lightning, which flies out horizontally at enemies, and water, which drags the player and enemies straight down flowing over platforms. Taking too long to complete any level will summon Baron Von Blubba, who will float around the screen trying to destroy the player.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>21507440</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Bubble Bobble (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Bubble Bobble (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Bubble Bobble (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="160834" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Buggy Boy (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Buggy Boy</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<hash>713035F4</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Buggy Boy (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Buggy Boy (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Buggy Boy (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44760" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Carrier Command (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Carrier Command</name>
		<desc>Carrier Command was one of the first real-time strategy games.

You control an advanced cybernetic aircraft carrier complete with fighters, amphibious assault vehicles, laser defenses and a fleet of decoy drones.  Your mission is to build a series of resource, factory, and defensive bases spanning an island chain.  The only problem?  At the other end of the chain is an even more advanced carrier under control of a terrorist organization with the same mission.

As you move around the islands you must decide what facilities to build and where they will best support your advance.  Resource islands provide materials that factory islands can use to build weapons and vehicles to replace your combat losses but both will be quickly overrun if the enemy attacks them while you are not present.  You also have to ensure that your stockpiles of equipment are stored safely until you can find time to launch a resupply drone to bring them to your carrier.

From your carrier, you can take first person control of your attack aircraft and amphibious tanks and use them to assault enemy islands or even the enemy carrier itself if you're lucky enough to find it.  The weapon payloads on your vehicles are completely configurable based on your needs.  An island invasion may require launching a virus bomb that will take over the enemy command systems or just blasting the base with a wire guided surface to surface missile.

Ultimately, you have to find and destroy the enemy carrier but, doing so will require a solid supply infrastructure and a strategy for depriving your opponent of his.
</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realtime Games Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbird Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>EC684A17</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Carrier Command (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Carrier Command (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Carrier Command (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44781" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Chase H.Q. II - Special Criminal Investigations (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Chase H.Q. II: Special Criminal Investigation</name>
		<desc>Three girls have been reported missing including the mayor's daughter, and Chase Special Investigations has asked you to track down five vehicles, mentioned in the mission briefing, who are believed to be involved in the kidnapping. Using a heavy-designed machine with a V6 DOHC 3000CC Twin Turbo Engine, five sets of nitro-fuel boosts, and a gun attached to the steering wheel (which you can use to damage the target vehicle), your mission is to patrol the streets and find these vehicles.

The gameplay is similar to Chase H.Q., but there are a few differences. For example, cars travel in both directions instead of one, and some of them will catch up to your car and shoot at you. At least once in every stage a helicopter does a fly by and drops you some grenades you can use to further damage the target vehicle. A guy on a motorcycle will catch up to you and throw grenades at your car. And, most importantly, as mentioned earlier, you can shoot at the target vehicle rather than just bumping into it.

Have fun driving around, but remember, there is a strict time limit, so I wouldn't waste time or keep crashing into things if I were you.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>4440385C</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Chase H.Q. II - Special Criminal Investigations (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Chase H.Q. II - Special Criminal Investigations (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Chase H.Q. II - Special Criminal Investigations (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44796" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Chuckie Egg 2 (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Chuckie Egg II</name>
		<desc>Chuckie Egg II is a sequel to platformer game Chuckie Egg, but is very different from the original game.  Whereas the original game features eight levels of one screen each, this features many more screens arranged into a maze for you to explore.

In the game, Hen House Harry must build a giant chocolate egg, with the ingredients (cocoa, milk and sugar), that are found in the factory.  Eight of each must be included.  Also, the eight parts of a toy kit must be found, to place inside the egg.

In order to get all the items you must find your way around the factory, avoiding many types of enemy, and solving puzzles using various items that you can carry.  There are a number of ways to get around the factory, including the platforms of the original, but also ropes and pipes, among other things.

Despite the drastic changes from the original, the game still retains the sound effects from the original.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>A&amp;F Software</developer>
		<publisher>A&amp;F Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>FE5444D2</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Chuckie Egg 2 (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Chuckie Egg 2 (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Chuckie Egg 2 (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44795" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Chuckie Egg (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Chuckie Egg</name>
		<desc>In the game you play Hen House Harry who has to collect 12 (a dozen) eggs from each level, while avoiding the ducklings.  The levels each occupy a single screen, and are made up of platforms, ladders and lifts (or elevators), and are thus similar to those in classic platform game Donkey Kong.  Corn can also be collected, which stops the time limit from ticking down and also stops the bonus, collected when the level is completed, from decreasing.  The ducklings also eat the corn, however.

There are only 8 distinct levels.  The ninth level is a copy of level 1, the tenth is a copy of level 2, and so on.  However, on the second time around the ducklings that can use the platforms and ladders are replaced by the Mother Duck, who can fly around the level going through the platforms and ladders.  On the third time around, you have to face both the Mother Duck and the ducklings, and similarly on subsequent goes round, when there are more ducklings.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>A&amp;F Software</developer>
		<publisher>A&amp;F Software</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<hash>D6997A16</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Chuckie Egg (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Chuckie Egg (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Chuckie Egg (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="160779" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cobra Force (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Cobra Force</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Players Premier</publisher>
		<hash>0C00CB15</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Cobra Force (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cobra Force (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Cobra Force (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44812" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cobra (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Cobra</name>
		<desc>This Green Beret-style arcade game follows the plot of the film starring Sylvester Stallone. As Stallone's Cobra character you must rescue Ingrid Knutsen before the Night Slasher gets to her. There are 3 levels of gameplay, set in a city, the countryside and a factory. All have multiple ledges and platforms to negotiate.

Cobra starts without a weapon, but he is tough enough to attack with a precisely timed head-butt, although this method of killing is risky, as it will kill Cobra if mistimed. Fortunately there are weapons to pick up along the way, by picking up hamburgers. The weapons include daggers, pistols and machine guns, but all are time-limited
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>51399443</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Cobra (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cobra (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Cobra (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="135281" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Codename Mat II (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Codename Mat II</name>
		<desc>In this sequel to Codename: MAT (the original never appeared on the Commodore 64) you once again take the role of Mat, now the pilot of the Centurion II as he battles the Myons once more.

In the Terranya war it has been discovered that the planet Vesta is full of the most precious substance in the galaxy, Karillium, which with one drop can turn a desert into a jungle. The planet orbits around the star Calest deep in a Myon zone, but the Earth managed to invade and capture the planet with unmanned ships. With the planet full of Karillium mines powered by an energy grid which in turn is powered by Calest, the Myons have decided to destroy the energy grid which will shut down the mines and the miners will leave the planet. Under the rules of war, only one manned ship can defend a inhabited planet and Mat has been lucky enough to be chosen.

The game is viewed from a 1st person perspective as you look out from your cockpit into deep space, with your gun in front of you. Using a Quadrant chart, you can see rows of satellites that power the mines which also shows your locations as well any Myon ships. You are able to control your speed as well as direction and if you need to move larger distances then you can warp as long as you input your direction. As you progress through the game you will find the Myons damaging the satellites and these need repairing by two droids on your ship who can also repair your ship.

Your ship also contains various scanners as well as a manual or automatic targeting system. Once you come across a wave of Myon ships you must destroy them with either your laser or plasma while using the scanners for they position. Once a wave is destroyed then you can repair any damaged satellites or your ship if needed. To help protect yourself from attack your ship has shields with decrease when hits are taken. You cannot be destroyed though because when you are close to destruction you teleport away from the planet. The game is over if the power to the planet is stopped by a damaged row of satellites.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Derek Brewster</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1BB9D770</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Codename Mat II (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Codename Mat II (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Codename Mat II (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44814" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Codename Mat (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Codename: MAT</name>
		<desc>Mission: Alien Termination involves all the knowledge of science, space combat and military tactics being implanted into the strong, agile and future-proof body of a 13-year-old boy. You play Mat, at the helm of the USS Centurion prototype fighter, and have the task for saving the world.

The game's basic space combat component is fast and smooth, with raging battles resembling Star Raiders. However, in addition to this you must plan your course carefully, both during and between fights. You also have the option of taking on command duties, directing all the other ships in the force.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Micromega</developer>
		<publisher>Micromega</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B109DFDC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Codename Mat (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Codename Mat (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Codename Mat (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="160770" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Comando Quatro (Spain).z80</path>
		<name>Comando Quatro</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Zigurat</publisher>
		<hash>031F7D9C</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Comando Quatro (Spain).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Comando Quatro (Spain).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Comando Quatro (Spain).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44833" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Contact Sam Cruise (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Contact Sam Cruise</name>
		<desc>It's Whodunit time in this licensed arcade adventure starring Sam Cruise. As Sam you must collect the clues by walking over them, with the hope of finding the killer. Money is an issue as well, as more can be collected, but it will be needed as the game goes on.

The city is awash with Gangsters, and neither they nor the police are happy with your methods or motives. Gangster bullets should be avoided if possible, as you only have the medical kits to repair the damage from 8 shots - fortunately a plethora of evasive moves are offered including rolls and somersaults. The police can be evaded by wearing disguises.

Many buildings can be entered and explored for clues, but leaving the lights on can alert people to your presence. Telephone calls play a big part in the game - initially you only have the number for your office, but this is a potential goldmine of clues, and more numbers can be obtained in a manner similar to Hacker.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D0585FDF</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Contact Sam Cruise (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Contact Sam Cruise (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Contact Sam Cruise (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44834" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Continental Circus (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Continental Circus</name>
		<desc>The home conversions of Continental Circus lack the full-on 3D and special glasses of the arcade version, but retain the essential gameplay structure. The first race is in Brazil and features 100 cars, and requires you to finish in the top 80 in order to qualify for  next race. As you work through the 8 races the size of the field steadily decreases, but so does the worst acceptable finishing position to qualify.

The car has high and low gears, and is susceptible to damage from contact with another car. Once you hit a car or a piece of the trackside scenery you will be called into the pits - fail to make it back, or hit another car, and you will crash and lose several seconds.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Mastertronic</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>36EA70FC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Continental Circus (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Continental Circus (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Continental Circus (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44855" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cruising On Broadway (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Cruising on Broadway</name>
		<desc>Cruising is one of the simplest computer games possible, and one which probably has been independently invented more than one time. The concept is similar to games such as Cuthbert Goes Walkabout, in that your goal is to colour all lines on the screen while avoiding the nasties that might get in your way.

Unlike the aforementioned game, though, Cruising doesn't simply divide the screen into a grid. Instead, the lines make more intricate patterns, more so for each "grid" that you clear. Another feature is that you can make a cut in the grid so that the "chaser" can't follow you that way. Just make sure not to cut off your own escape route!
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jeff Naylor</developer>
		<publisher>Sunshine Books</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>33934C42</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Cruising On Broadway (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cruising On Broadway (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Cruising On Broadway (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44861" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cybernoid II - The Revenge (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Cybernoid II: The Revenge</name>
		<desc>The follow-up to Cybernoid: The Fighting Machine is again a flip-screen shoot 'em up. In control of the deadly Cybernoid craft, your job is to rescue the cargo which has been stolen by a wave of pirate ships.

Using the range of weapon systems correctly is again a key factor. These include sideways aiming guns, bouncing bombs, 'seeker' smart bombs, bombs which move around th edge of the screen before finding a target, and time-sensitive bombs which explode a few seconds after you drop them. Shot pirate ships release cargo, and you must collect at least 1500 points of this, but on many screens it is more prudent to make an escape ASAP, as some screens have more hazards than others, and not all aliens on each screen act in the same way.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hewson Consultants Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson Consultants Ltd</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D1269907</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Cybernoid II - The Revenge (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cybernoid II - The Revenge (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Cybernoid II - The Revenge (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44862" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cybernoid - The Fighting Machine (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Cybernoid: The Fighting Machine</name>
		<desc>There are three asteroids, hidden among thousands, where various minerals and precious gems were stored. It was believed the riches would be safe there, until the Zoggians discovered them! Now you have to fly an experimental spacefighter, the Cybernoid, into battle to recover the asteroids. The Cybernoid is equipped with standard laser blasters, missiles, and the ability to pick up other weapons along the way. 

Cybernoid is an arcade style action game for one player. You can choose from three different skill levels; easy, hard and lethal. On some versions two different sound modes are also available, a basic music and sound effects mode, and a super sound effects mode with no music. Each room you explore is equipped with a time bomb. The bomb will explode taking you with it should you take too long to get past all the obstacles on the screen. You start the game with nine ships, and more can be earned by collecting enough points during the game.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hewson Consultants Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson Consultants Ltd</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>5AAFF50E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Cybernoid - The Fighting Machine (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cybernoid - The Fighting Machine (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Cybernoid - The Fighting Machine (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44875" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dan Dare II - Mekon's Revenge (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Dan Dare II: Mekon's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Mekon, the arch-enemy of humanity with an insatiable lust for power, is back. Hes created the SuperTreens, a genetically engineered species bent on destruction, as well as a new spaceship. As Dan Dare, you must stop him.

You have gained access to Mekons spaceship, which is packed with SuperTreens. When you find each one you must disable each control box before the time limit, and then reach the next level. Mekon will be trying to reach and activate each one, with the help of his existing race of Treens. Although Dan has six lives, being caught in an blast triggered by the destruction of a level without appropriate shielding is Game Over. Extra lives are scored incrementally after 50,000 points, while energy recharges can be obtained around the game.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gang of Five</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Games</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>F4DE84FF</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dan Dare II - Mekon's Revenge (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dan Dare II - Mekon's Revenge (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dan Dare II - Mekon's Revenge (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44874" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dan Dare III - The Escape (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Dan Dare III: The Escape</name>
		<desc>In the third game in the Dan Dare series, Dan has been kidnapped by an evil alien race known as the Treens and taken to their scientific satellite orbiting Venus, but it doesn't take long for Dan to break free and goes down into their ship. While searching it, he eventually finds an escape shuttle sitting in the launch bay, only to discover that it is out of fuel. He returns to the satellite in an attempt to find some.

The fuel cans are scattered around the five levels of the ship, which Dan can get to by using the Mekon's teleporters. To get to them though, Dan needs to destroy any Treen that gets in his way using a variety of weapons, brought by using a computer terminal. Along the way, the Mekon leader can be seen sitting around, and destroying him will more often than not reward Dan with a pod that he needs to access the teleporter. Dan can use his jet-pack to navigate the satellite, but this will eventually run out of fuel.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Games</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>62E78B6B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dan Dare III - The Escape (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dan Dare III - The Escape (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dan Dare III - The Escape (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44876" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dan Dare - Pilot of the Future (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Dan Dare: Pilot of the Future</name>
		<desc>A licensed game based around the cult comic strip character, recreating his daring attempts to defeat Mekon and save the earth.

The Anastasia ship is attacked by the Treens as soon as Dan steps onto it, although fortunately he picks up a laser on board. From then on, he must act as fast as possible.

The main task is to find each of the 5 parts of a planetary-destruction mechanism to the control room, so that it can be safely diffused. He can only carry one at a time, and once he gets the back he must find the correct socket for each one. Lastly he must escape to the surface.

Contact with a Treen will see Dan kidnapped and placed in the prison area; he can get out easily enough, but will now be in a different place. Getting hit by gun blasts will weaken him gradually.
</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gang of Five</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Games</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C434F3EB</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dan Dare - Pilot of the Future (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dan Dare - Pilot of the Future (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dan Dare - Pilot of the Future (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44883" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dark Side (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Dark Side</name>
		<desc>In Driller, the Ketars attempted to blow up the moon Mitral, but you stopped them. Now, they have Energy Collection Devices collectively known as EGOs, and hope to stock them up to use towards the Zephyr One device, and direct its energy at the planet Evath, resulting in a catastrophic radiation overload. 

Your mission is to beam onto their base on the moon Tricuspid, and destroy the EGOs. Destroying one will buy you more of your limited time. The problem is, many are connected to at least 2 others, and those can immediately regenerate, so you must tackle them in an order in which those with only 1 connection are attacked first.

You are inside a space suit, propelled by a Jet Pack with limited fuel, and possess lasers and a shield. Shield energy is limited, but can be recharged through pentagons and rods. In a world viewed through the the Freescape 3D system, you roam the verdant planet of trees, buildings and underground tunnels.

Gameplay has more action than Driller. The Freescape world has a third dimension - due to the jetpack you can leave the ground and look down on the view. You can also rotate the angle and make quick U-turns. You must leave the ground to shoot the active part of an ECD, but the jetpack uses energy at a faster rate, so use this feature sparingly. You must avoid Plexors, which weaken your shield, and deflector devices, which can beam you into prison.
</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Major Developments</developer>
		<publisher>Incentive Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2EE86822</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dark Side (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dark Side (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dark Side (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44887" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Deactivators (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Deactivators</name>
		<desc>Deactivators is an arcade-puzzle maze game which puts you in control of a squad of bomb disposal droids. You must pick them up and quickly throw them out of the building to safety - failure to do this costs you a droid and a room (occasionally blocking off other essential rooms). The game's levels have grid-like arrangements with doors, trapdoors and poles, and increase in size as the game goes on. For both these reasons, mapping is essential.

Security droids are on patrol, but these can be tricked into falling down holes. A computer room is the hub of your activities - this allows you to use teleports and turn off force fields, via the appropriate circuit boards which are hidden throughout the levels. On later levels the gravity isn't constant and you will find rooms with distorted directional senses, increasing the precision required significantly.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tigress Marketing</developer>
		<publisher>Ariolasoft</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>318BFB52</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Deactivators (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Deactivators (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Deactivators (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="136099" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Doomdark's Revenge (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Doomdark's Revenge</name>
		<desc>The follow-up to the original Lords of Midnight game uses a similar game system to its predecessor, but the story is now much more complex. Luxor the Moonprince's son Morkin has been kidnapped by Shareth, daughter of Doomdark, the evil ruler deposed in the first game. The player initially takes control of Luxor, Rothron the Wise, and Morkin's lover Tarithel the Fey, although many more characters can be recruited as the game progresses, as they aim to banish Shareth and rescue Morkin. Shareth has brainwashed him, so he must also be turned back to Luxor's side.

The game is effectively turn-based; your characters move by day (with a limited amount of movement possible, with each move in one of the 8 compass directions) and Shareth's by night. You will find plains, mountains, forests, underground tunnels and mysterious temples on your journey. A dark mist follows much of the area, which causes your characters to deteriorate in mood and thus become less effective.

The characters are now split into five distinct tribes - Giant, Dwarf, Fey, Icemark and Barbarians, and recruiting new characters into your party isn't automatic - factors such as the game situation can make some refuse to join, turn on members of other races, or defect (as the Utarg did in the first game).

There are several different objectives and possible outcomes to the game. Bringing Morkin back to the Gates of Varenorn is the most basic one, but many other characters ought to be saved, Shareth can be killed completely (with practice!), and there are many Crowns of Icemark to be retrieved. As in the first game, control of the full party only remains while Luxor is alive - his death means total defeat.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mike Singleton</developer>
		<publisher>Beyond Software</publisher>
		<hash>E015629C</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Doomdark's Revenge (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Doomdark's Revenge (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Doomdark's Revenge (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44948" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dun Darach (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Dun Darach</name>
		<desc>Dun Darach may be the first ever videogame prequel to Tir Na Nog. As such, it features the warrior Cuchulainn of Muirmethne, in a war against the Conachta. When he and his colleague Loeg meet a beautiful woman named Skar in an inn, they do not suspect that she is a spy, and will kidnap Loeg to the secret city of Dun Darach (the 'Oak Fort' in Celtic). Cuchulainn will not stand for this, and sets off to Dun Darach to rescue him. This will involve secondary quests being completed along the way.

The game system is identical to that of Tir Na Nog a single road of the city is shown at a time, which can be walked along to the left or right. When you come to a junction, the view can be rotated by 90 degree to allow this path to be followed. Gameplay is also similar - sword fights must be won and word-based puzzles solved, although unlike Tir Na Nog you cannot die.

Trade and money management plays a bigger part than before - objects can be offered to, sold to and stolen from others, and you get obtain jobs for money. Watch out for Ryde the policeman - if he finds you with stolen goods, everything you are carrying will be taken. You must also speak to people and enter magic rooms to obtain key information.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gargoyle Games Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Gargoyle Games Ltd</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>DC859439</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Dun Darach (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dun Darach (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dun Darach (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44964" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Elite (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Elite</name>
		<desc>You have a ship with virtually no equipment. Take her and trade among the different star systems. You can be safe and trade on razor-thin margins among the safe systems, or take some risks and trade with anarchic systems while watching out for pirates. You can save on fuel costs by buying a fuel scoop and fly near the sun, but again, watch out for pirates! Or be a pirate yourself and raid other ships...  Don't get a bad rep as the police will come after you... Dock with space stations and do your trades (some may take contraband...) Upgrade your ship with your proceeds with better weapons,  shields, and other equipment. With 8 different galaxies, each with HUNDREDS of planets, there are plenty of room for exploration! Can you make your reputation all the way up to "elite"?
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Torus, Philip Mochan, Ricardo J.M. Pinto, Dominic M.N. Prior, Mark Wighton</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software Ltd</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>30640FCC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Elite (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Elite (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Elite (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44974" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Enduro Racer (1987)(Hit Squad)[Re-Release].tzx</path>
		<name>Enduro Racer</name>
		<desc>In this game you play the role of an endurance bike racer. The gameplay involves you racing against the clock to get to the finish line and jumping over ramps. At the end of each race you get points for how many cars or bikes you have overtaken with which you can upgrade your bike.
There are various different terrain for you to race on including desert beach and dirt tracks plus a number of things to slow you down or even knock you off of your bike all together. The main idea is to find the best route through each level to shave off valuable seconds in order to over take more cars and bikes.

The Japanese version of the game has more Tracks than the European and US versions have. Among  them is a snow track which is one of the hardest tracks in the game, because there is a lot of stones on the thin road.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>7E1B0ACD</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Enduro Racer (1987)(Hit Squad)[Re-Release].png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Enduro Racer (1987)(Hit Squad)[Re-Release].png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Enduro Racer (1987)(Hit Squad)[Re-Release].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="44994" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Exploding Fist+ (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Exploding Fist +</name>
		<desc>As with IK+, the main addition of this Way of the Exploding Fist follow-up is a third player during the bouts - unlike IK+ all 3 can be human-controlled. A similar range of moves is offered to the predecessor, including attacking and defensive moves, and the moves vary in their value in terms of the points they offer within the fight, and the points they add to your score.

You start off as a rookie; to reach the first of the 10 Dans you must win 2 bouts before either of your opponents. Each bout is win by scoring 6 points, or by having the top score after 60 seconds. Finish last in any bout and you are out.

After every two rounds, a bonus game is played, which sets you in a darkened alleyway shooting at a succession of ninja heads, scoring points for each until you miss one.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software Pty., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<hash>24692205</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Exploding Fist+ (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Exploding Fist+ (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Exploding Fist+ (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="136671" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Flying Shark (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Flying Shark</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graftgold Ltd, Dominic Robinson, John Cumming, Gavin Wade, Drew Northcott</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>8B5D0E1F</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Flying Shark (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Flying Shark (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Flying Shark (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="136674" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Football Frenzy (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Football Frenzy</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Alternative Software</publisher>
		<hash>C67FEAB8</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Football Frenzy (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Football Frenzy (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Football Frenzy (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45055" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Frankie Goes to Hollywood (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Frankie Goes to Hollywood</name>
		<desc>Playing a thoroughly drab, mundane and predictable character, your aim is to become interesting enough to reach the Pleasuredome. After discovering a gruesome murder, your interest in something greater than the routine of 80s Liverpool is awoken.

You explore the streets and houses in the search of a way out. The main basis of the game involves picking up objects and using them in the correct way - most objects have more than one potential use, and misusing them is the only way the game can be lost. There are several sub-games along the way, including shoot 'em ups, a maze and a jigsaw puzzle.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Denton Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1EB79FA9</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Frankie Goes to Hollywood (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Frankie Goes to Hollywood (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Frankie Goes to Hollywood (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45057" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fred (Europe).TZX</path>
		<name>Fred</name>
		<desc>You are Fred, an intrepid archaeologist, interested in visiting the pyramid of Tootiecarmoon looking for a new experience, and in search of treasures and great adventures.

The game consists of 6 levels, on which you must obtain treasures  and - of course - a map that allows you to leave the labyrinthine pyramid alive.

You must avoid dangerous acid drops, mummies, spiders, vampires, etc. In order to defend yourself from those disagreeable enemies you have at your disposition a gun (with limited bullets), but some enemies are immune to guns, and you must jump or avoid them.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Indescomp</developer>
		<publisher>Quicksilva Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>29330416</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Fred (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fred (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Fred (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45088" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gauntlet II (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Gauntlet II</name>
		<desc>Based on the arcade game, Gauntlet II is very similar to the original. Up to four players (a wizard, a warrior, an elf, and a valkyrie) make their way through various mazes, collect treasures and magic potions, and fend off assorted creatures and ghosts.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>1EB26D35</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Gauntlet II (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gauntlet II (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gauntlet II (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45089" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gauntlet III - The Final Quest (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Gauntlet III: The Final Quest</name>
		<desc>Like in the prequels you empty areas infested by all kinds of enemies while running for the exit. Like this was rather a straight forward thing in the first two games, it's not that easy to finish a level anymore. While you only had to run until you find the exit (and besides killing hordes of enemies you probably find some keys to unlock doors leading to deeper dungeons) you might have to solve a few "quests" to proceed to the next level in this installment.
These "quests" are very basic, for example you have to find object A, then bring it to B, advance to C and finally go to D to uncover the exit.
The big difference is the graphics. While you had a top down view in the first 2 games Gauntlet 3 has an isometric kind of view.
The old 4 characters (warrior, wizard, elf and valkyrie) are ready for action again and this time they get backup by 4 new characters which include the Lizard, Neptune, Stoneman and the Iceman.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tengen Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>0A823009</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Gauntlet III - The Final Quest (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gauntlet III - The Final Quest (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gauntlet III - The Final Quest (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45087" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gauntlet (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Gauntlet</name>
		<desc>Gauntlet, the original arcade smash hit, is a fighting game where you choose a character and let rip into the hordes of enemies that assault you on you way to the end of the level. One or two players must make their way through 100 levels of mayhem and magic. 

It featured a choice of four characters to play with, each with different weapons. Thor the Warrior, has a  bludgeoning battle axe, Thyra the Valkyrie, has a close range sword, Questor the Elf has his long range bow, and Merlin the Wizard has magical bolts.

Ghosts, goblins and even the life draining Death are your enemies. Enemies stream out of generators, so destroy these before tackling the rest. 

Keys are needed to open the many doors within the levels, and in some situations a door will contain only bonus items, not a progressive route.  Scattered magic potions act like smart bombs and clear the screen of all enemies. Beware of poison though, this reduces your energy level.
Treasure is abundant throughout the levels and adds to your score.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>B62A7966</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Gauntlet (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gauntlet (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gauntlet (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45090" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gauntlet - The Deeper Dungeons (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Gauntlet: The Deeper Dungeons</name>
		<desc>This is an expansion pack for the original Gauntlet. It has 512 new action packed dungeons. Unfortunately there is no other new content besides the dungeons.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>A45FC702</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Gauntlet - The Deeper Dungeons (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gauntlet - The Deeper Dungeons (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gauntlet - The Deeper Dungeons (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45117" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Golden Axe (1988)(Sega)[h].tzx</path>
		<name>Golden Axe</name>
		<desc>Sega's classic arcade beat-'em-up game, Golden Axe puts in the shoes of one of three heroes, each with his own reason for trying to overthrow the evil rule of Death-Adder, who - along with his forces of darkness - kidnapped and imprisoned the King and his daughter and stole the legendary Golden Axe.

This is a horizontal fighting game, where you basically take one of the three characters (a warrior, a dwarf or an amazon) and bash everything which stands between you and Death Adder himself.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Games</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>1DC25B27</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Golden Axe (1988)(Sega)[h].png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Golden Axe (1988)(Sega)[h].png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Golden Axe (1988)(Sega)[h].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="132750" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Green Beret (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Green Beret</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jonathan M. Smith, F. David Thorpe</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>75F28A0A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Green Beret (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Green Beret (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Green Beret (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45156" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gyron - Arena (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Gyron Arena</name>
		<desc>Gyron Arena was created for the final play offs of the Gyron competition,  and released at a budget price,  gameplay is identical. The cassette inlay introduction gives some good background info on the game;

"On a cold grey morning in the middle of London thirty people gathered in a very ordinary office block. These people, in the age range 14 to 60, had one thing in common. They had completed one of the most difficult computer games ever devised; GYRON NECROPOLIS, and were brought together to compete in the grand final play off. Their task? Complete the GYRON ARENA game in the shortest possible time. The prize? A brand new Porsche 924 motor car or £12,500 cash. Further competitions were held in Spain and Denmark simultaneously with London to give foreign finalists the chance to claim the prize. The winner came from the Spanish heat, who finished the game in a blistering 18 minutes! Here is your opportunity to play the ARENA game used in the final ... Bet you can't beat 18 minutes!"
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Torus, Philip Mochan, Ricardo J.M. Pinto, Dominic M.N. Prior, Mark Wighton</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>90F7AF2C</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Gyron - Arena (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gyron - Arena (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gyron - Arena (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45157" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gyroscope (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Gyroscope</name>
		<desc>Releasing a game which resembles a well-known arcade game before any official license can be released was always a challenge for publishers, and in this case Melbourne House released a game similar to Marble Madness. Controlling a gyroscope, you most navigate your way down a sloping track full of hazards. The viewpoint is in fixed isometric 3D, with hazards including buildings, ramps and drops. The gyroscope accelerates quickly and takes time to slow down, so it is easy to go into a screen too fast.

Failing to keep the gyroscope spinning freely as it navigates these costs you one of your seven lives. You are also playing within a time limit - losing a life sees you return to the start of a level without regaining lost time, but running out of time sees you lose a life, but be able to continue from where you were left with a new set of time (so, as with Chase HQ, completing tricky levels can take 2 or 3 lives at first). 

You get time bonuses for completing a screen, points bonuses for completing one of the seven four-screen levels, and an extra life for reaching 1000 points.
At the end of level 7, you will get 1000 points for each remaining lives, doubling your current amount of lives. You will then start again at level 1 but mirrored by the vertical axis (you are now climbing from the bottom of screen to the top).
After level 14 (level 7 mirror), you will again win 1000 points for each remaining lives and then the game loop on level 1 (not mirrored).
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Catalyst Coders</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>38C5C99B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Gyroscope (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gyroscope (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gyroscope (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45175" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Head over Heels (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Head Over Heels</name>
		<desc>Two distinct characters called Mr Head and Mr Heels are  played in this arcade adventure. They are separated at the shoulders but capable of joining together to maximize their abilities in some situations (but reduce them in others, so they can be split again).

The game is presented from an isometric perspective, and presents the characters with a number of puzzles involving switches, jumps and climbs. The levels are 3 dimensional, and the characters must collect crowns as they progress. Objects can be picked up and manipulated as necessary.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software, S.A.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2922AB3E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Head over Heels (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Head over Heels (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Head over Heels (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45187" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hero Quest (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Hero Quest</name>
		<desc>The famous fantasy-themed board game was converted into an isometric-viewed role playing game in which the evil Wizard Morcar must be defeated. You take control of a wizard, a dwarf, a barbarian and an elf, each with different strengths and weaknesses, who each start the 14 missions from opposite sides of the board.

Strict turn-based movement rules apply, as actions other than movement can only be carried out before or after the move, the size of which is limited by a dice roll. These moves are carried out using an icon-based system. Characters can fight the many monsters which lurk, or cast spells to vanquish them. There are magic potions to uncover, but also hidden traps, so mapping is advised. Treasure can be collected, and traded at the shop after each level.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>221B Software Development</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>33C59A10</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Hero Quest (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hero Quest (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hero Quest (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45192" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Highway Encounter (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Highway Encounter</name>
		<desc>In this isometric 3D action-strategy game, the player uses a Vorton droid to push a bomb to the end of the highway into an alien base. There are 30 screens, most of them filled with hazards trying to block (like barrels) or destroy (mines and aliens) your bomb. 

The perspective and guidance concept are not the game's only original features; there are 4 more bombs with you, representing your extra lives - pushing you forward on your mission. If these other Vortons are destroyed, one of your extra lives is lost without the player being able to use it.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vortex Software</developer>
		<publisher>Vortex Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>DAF6D441</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Highway Encounter (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Highway Encounter (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Highway Encounter (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45200" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Horace Goes Skiing (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Horace Goes Skiing</name>
		<desc>A more accurate title for this would be "Horace Goes Skiing, but only if he can brave a Frogger clone first", as you start the game by having to reach the ski shop to get skis, and then get back across to reach the slopes. The road is full of cars and bikes, contact with each of which costs $10 in ambulance fees out of your starting $40, and the skis themselves cost $10.

The actual skiing section has a pseudo-3D view, similar to a roving camera mounted above the course. Your task is to cut between the red and blue sets of flags, without hitting any of the trees on the course. Light contact with these will allow you to carry on; heavy contact breaks your skis and sends you back to the first section of the game (which you also return to after completing each of the courses).
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psion Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sinclair Research Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>85BB5278</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Horace Goes Skiing (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Horace Goes Skiing (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Horace Goes Skiing (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="135906" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hudson Hawk (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Hudson Hawk</name>
		<desc>Hudson Hawk, a cat burglar, has a mission: steal three of Da Vinci's works of art, which include a rocking horse known as "The Sforza", his sketchbook that he called "The Codex", and a precious crystal. The mission will take him through a mansion, castles, rooftops, subways, and the Vatican. Of course, getting all these items will not be as easy as it sounds. Not only does Hawk face security guards, guard dogs, and others, but he must also avoid setting off alarms. To help him, Hawk can either punch enemies, or throw a ball at them.
</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Special FX Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7AEE8426</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Hudson Hawk (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hudson Hawk (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hudson Hawk (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="137814" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hyperaction (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Hyperaction</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Silversoft</publisher>
		<hash>FC64AAD0</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Hyperaction (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hyperaction (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hyperaction (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45231" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./I, Ball II - Quest for the Past (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>I Ball II</name>
		<desc>After rescuing their people and surviving (in the first game), the Ball race wish to discover something about their history and heritage. You have been sent down mines, to explore 50 screens, on each of which you must collect a key and reach the exit. You also have to pick up a sacred artifact on every 5th level.

Your character is very bouncy, requiring small movements in order to keep control. You can shoot at the surrounding enemies and collect weapons, although the initial one only shoots horizontally. There are many pickups on offer, including extra lives, bounciness boosts and opposition-slowers.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Timothy Closs</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>38CBFF73</hash>
		<image>./mixart/I, Ball II - Quest for the Past (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/I, Ball II - Quest for the Past (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/I, Ball II - Quest for the Past (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45256" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./International Karate+ (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>International Karate +</name>
		<desc>International Karate + (IK+) is a simple side-on beat 'em up. 3 characters appear on the screen - either 1 player and 2 AI, or 2 player and 1 AI - and proceed to kick seven bells out of each other via various karate moves.

Each of the moves scores a different number of points and if you come last in a particular round you are eliminated.

There are some sub-games too, involving your karate-master holding a shield and defending himself against bouncing balls from both directions, and kicking bombs off the screen before they explode.

All in the pursuit of that elusive black belt...
</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>System 3 Software, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>System 3 Software, Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>287DAF9D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/International Karate+ (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/International Karate+ (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/International Karate+ (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45272" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jack the Nipper II - In Coconut Capers (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Jack the Nipper... II in Coconut Capers</name>
		<desc>Naughty toddler Jack finds himself in Africa, with the aim of progressing through 192 screens of platform action. He starts with nine lives but no weapons, although a supply of coconuts to lob is close at hand. 

The jungle is full of snakes, rhinos, birds and all manner of other creatures, all of which must be avoided or killed - remember that their attack paths are pre-programmed, and the trajectory of your coconuts is quite limited. Travelling through the levels involves, amongst other things, ladders, mine carts, trees, ropes and logs.

As well as simply completing the game and amassing as many points as possible, you can aim to be as naughty as possible, which is gauged by a 'Naughty-O-Meter' next to the score, with numerous objects available for that purpose (one can be carried at a time, alongside one weapon).
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>5816309D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Jack the Nipper II - In Coconut Capers (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jack the Nipper II - In Coconut Capers (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Jack the Nipper II - In Coconut Capers (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45271" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jack the Nipper (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Jack the Nipper</name>
		<desc>Jack the Nipper is a platform game that contains 50 screens packed with action.

Jack is an evil and wicked toddler. You play Jack and you have to cause as much trouble without being penalized for it. To see how naughty you've been there is a naughtyometer at the bottom of the screen.

To cause some mayhem Jack must jump on things, pick up objects and drop those at places where they cause the most trouble to grown-ups.

The various objects can be found all over town and at Jack's home.
The game starts at Jack's home but Jack can walk out the door and go into town to, for example, blow up the police station, kill all flowers or free prisoners. Try to get a credit card and do some serious shopping!

The first thing you should look for is you peashooter and fire peas at various objects or persons. Toot your horn to frustrate grown-ups or animals.

The naughtier your the higher your naughtyometer goes up!
The game comes to an end as the naughtyometer reaches 100%.
Cause as much trouble as you can... but don't get spanked for it by grown-ups!
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8931634B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Jack the Nipper (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jack the Nipper (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Jack the Nipper (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45282" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jet Set Willy II - The Final Frontier (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Jet Set Willy II: The Final Frontier</name>
		<desc>This platform game is the sequel of Jet Set Willy. Again has each room its own hazards, such as spikes, revolving razors and ropes. The route through the house must be navigated carefully, due to the multiple entrances to some rooms - this is perhaps the first action game where mapping is an advantage. Another innovation, to the chagrin of players everywhere, is manual protection - a sheet of colour-coded numbers.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Projects Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Software Projects Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>14771687</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Jet Set Willy II - The Final Frontier (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jet Set Willy II - The Final Frontier (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Jet Set Willy II - The Final Frontier (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="164372" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jet Set Willy (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Jet Set Willy</name>
		<desc>Cult hero Matthew Smith followed up Manic Miner with a seminal platform game. Having struck it lucky in the first game, Willy now owns a lavish mansion with over 60 rooms linked in a 3D plane, and must tidy it all before his housekeeper will let him sleep.

Each room has its own hazards, such as spikes, revolving razors and ropes. The route through the house must be navigated carefully, due to the multiple entrances to some rooms - this is perhaps the first action game where mapping is an advantage. Another innovation, to the chagrin of players everywhere, is manual protection - a sheet of colour-coded numbers.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20140101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Projects Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Spud</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3CBA9764</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Jet Set Willy (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jet Set Willy (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Jet Set Willy (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45280" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jetpac (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Jetpac</name>
		<desc>Jetman has crash-landed on a distant planet, with ledges suspended in mid-air and populated by various nasties, and he must escape and find his way home. Your first task is to retrieve each of the three parts of his spaceship, in order, and carry them over the base part. After this, you must collect enough fuel to be able to fly away, again by picking it up and dropping it over the ship (you don't have to actually make contact with the ship in doing this). Once you've filled the ship up, you can fly on to the next level, in which you must again refuel.

Each level contains various bad guys, with different attack patterns; you have a lazer to shoot them for points, and must avoid contact with them. Diamonds can be collected for bonus points, and you get an extra life after every 10,000 points.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ultimate Play the Game</developer>
		<publisher>Ultimate Play the Game</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>DB33DE35</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Jetpac (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jetpac (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Jetpac (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="155537" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jet Set Willy III (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>JetSet Willy III</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>MB</publisher>
		<hash>B6FDCE1D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Jet Set Willy III (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Jet Set Willy III (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45295" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Jumping Jack (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Jumping Jack</name>
		<desc>Reaching the tops of 20 screens is the aim of Jack's life. The ledges go right across the screen, with gaps emerging at random intervals, through which Jack must aim. He can move along each ledge, and must avoid holes which open, as they can cause him to drop further. Later levels add aliens, snakes and all manner of other hazards, as well as an increasing number of holes. The control combination is unusual, and only comfortable on earlier Spectrum models - the game has no joystick mode.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagine</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>DAEE81A8</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Jumping Jack (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jumping Jack (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Jumping Jack (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="137954" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Knight Force (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Knight Force</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D302F317</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Knight Force (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Knight Force (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Knight Force (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45316" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Knight Lore (1984)(Ultimate).tzx</path>
		<name>Knight Lore</name>
		<desc>Our hero must reach Melkhior, a somewhat eccentric wizard who is the only one who can save him. As with most Ultimate titles of the day, reaching him is a long and treacherous challenge, involving both puzzle-solving and action, meaning that each screen requires thorough planning and precise navigation. 

The game uses the isometric viewpoint in a manner similar to the later Head Over Heels, using monochrome but detailed graphics and techniques to avoid flickering sprites. The game lasts for 40 days and nights - at night your character turns into a werewolf. Ultimate's individual style of eschewing straightforward instuctions in favour of feature lists and riddles is put to good use here, with the story detailed in a rhyming poem of sorts.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C10F7C90</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Knight Lore (1984)(Ultimate).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Knight Lore (1984)(Ultimate).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Knight Lore (1984)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45350" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Laser Squad - Remix (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Laser Squad</name>
		<desc>Laser Squad is by the same designer as Microprose's classic X-Com: UFO Defense. It brings to the table an immersive gameplay environment as well as many innovative ideas that weren't available in any other game of the time.

In Laser Squad you control a group of "marine"-like soldiers (and the occasional cyborg). Before taking them into battle, you must buy them weapons and armour with a predetermined amount of credits, taking into account the individual abilities of your squad. Unlike X-COM, the soldiers do not gain experience over time.

There are 3 missions in turn - in The Assassins you must face down Sterner Regnix and his guards, Moonbase assault challenges you to destroy the OmniCorp database, and Rescue From the Mines eschews violence in favour of a rescue mission. These are viewed from above and progress in turns. Laser Squad also features a 2-player "hotseat"-type gaming option.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Target Games Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Blade Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>E04E625B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Laser Squad - Remix (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Laser Squad - Remix (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Laser Squad - Remix (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45364" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lemmings (1991)(Psygnosis).z80</path>
		<name>Lemmings</name>
		<desc>Your task is to rescue the Lemmings across 120 levels of fast-paced puzzling. These creatures simply walk blindly through the world in the hope of reaching safety at the end of the level - unfortunately these levels include steep drops, gaps in the ground, barriers and rivers amongst other hazards.

You are in control not of any individual Lemming, but of a cross-hair, which can be moved over any of the Lemmings. Along the bottom are a selection of functions which can be assigned to a Lemming, including climbing, floating and bashing. You must click to select the appropriate function, then click on the Lemming to activate it. Each level has a different range of skills on offer, a different amount of Lemmings, and a different percentage target in order to progress.
</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>2C00C2FF</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Lemmings (1991)(Psygnosis).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Lemmings (1991)(Psygnosis).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lemmings (1991)(Psygnosis).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45368" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Light Force (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Lightforce</name>
		<desc>The Regulus system has been attacked by alien forces, and you are the only Terran fighter in place to clear the area and rescue the captured hostages.

The game is a vertically-scrolling shoot 'em up with 5 levels. The first of these involves clearing their defences to reach the alien sector, then you face the jungle, ice and desert planets, before reaching the final alien compound. The game's enemies have a variety of attack patterns and formations, as well as varied and colourful appearance.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Carter Follis Software Associates</developer>
		<publisher>FTL - Faster Than Light</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7974B7E7</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Light Force (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Light Force (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Light Force (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45377" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lode Runner (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Lode Runner</name>
		<desc>The Bungeling Empire has stolen a huge cache of gold from its rightful owners, and your mission is to infiltrate its treasury and recapture it. This entails progressing through 150 screens of platforms, ladders and ropes.

The Empire has sent robotic guards down to protect the gold, and contact with any of these will cost you a life. Your method of escaping them is to press fire to dig a hole in their line of movement, thus causing them to fall in briefly, allowing you to move across the gap safely. Once all the gold has been collected, a ladder allowing you to move onto the next screen is added. Completing these screens often requires forward planning and precision.

This was one of the earliest games to include a level editor, allowing the creation of new level designs with no programming skill.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Brøderbund Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Software Projects Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6212CC95</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Lode Runner (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Lode Runner (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lode Runner (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45389" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lotus Esprit Turbo Challenge (1990)(Gremlin Graphics).tzx</path>
		<name>Lotus Esprit Turbo Challenge</name>
		<desc>The first in a series of 3 racing games endorsed by the legendary car company, which is now a part of Proton.

The game features a total of 32 fictitious racetracks from around the world, split into 3 difficulty levels. There are 19 computer opponents (15 on the 8-bit versions) and you have to finish in the top 10 (top 8 on the 8-bits) to progress. The higher you finish in one race, the lower down the grid you start for the next race. The opposition drivers have pun names based on the F1 drivers of the day - examples include Ricardo Pastry and Crashhard Banger.

You can choose between sound effects or one of a variety of music pieces. The game features a simultaneous 2-player mode, but the 1-player mode only uses half the screen, a simple animation filling the other half. In most races you will have to make a pitstop for fuel in order to reach the finish. The tracks include features such as oil slicks, roadworks, boulders and rivers - contact with these (or the other cars) will slow you, but there is no car damage model.
</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magnetic Fields (Software Design) Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>ABA23852</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Lotus Esprit Turbo Challenge (1990)(Gremlin Graphics).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Lotus Esprit Turbo Challenge (1990)(Gremlin Graphics).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lotus Esprit Turbo Challenge (1990)(Gremlin Graphics).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45391" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lunar Jetman (1983)(Ultimate).tzx</path>
		<name>Lunar Jetman</name>
		<desc>Unfortunately, it seems like the crudely assembled multi-stage rocket that Jetman created in his first video-game outing (Jetpac) could have been put together a little better. With the rocket disintegrating about him in warp space, Jetman manages to crash land on a previously undiscovered planet, inhabited by hundreds of aliens intent of the total destruction of Earth. Oh no! Save us, Jetman!

Lunar Jetman has a graphical feel to it that is very similar to the original Jetpac game, but the gameplay is quite a bit different. Jetman's jetpac this time only has limited fuel, and that can prove hazardous when those pesky aliens come looking for him. Fortunately, Jetman also has a lunar rover at his disposal. Inside this he can replenish his jetpac's fuel supply as well as travel unmolested about the planet's surface. Unfortunately, the lunar rover can only travel across flat land, so the player must find and set down bridging units to allow the rover to traverse over any craters blocking the way.

Blocking the way to what, you ask? Well, each level has an alien base somewhere. Jetman must locate a bomb (which can be carried on the back of the rover), take it to the base and destroy it before the level's timer runs out. Taking too long results in missiles being launched to destroy the Earth and Jetman himself.

The game contains multiple levels, each obviously more hazardous and tricky than the last, and the player continues playing, racking up points until he runs out of lives.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ultimate - Play The Game</developer>
		<publisher>Ultimate - Play The Game</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>C0C6D93B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Lunar Jetman (1983)(Ultimate).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Lunar Jetman (1983)(Ultimate).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lunar Jetman (1983)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45414" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Manic Miner (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Manic Miner</name>
		<desc>You play the role of Miner Willy, a bold explorer and adventurer. He discovers a network of underground caverns used by an advanced but now extinct civilization, and realizes that the mines contain lucrative metal ores. Through 20 caverns, you must collect all treasures before all time (air) runs out, watching out for the nasty guardians, the obstacles, dead falls, quicksands and all elements to be found in a classic platform game.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Matthew Smith</developer>
		<publisher>Software Projects</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B28AD584</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Manic Miner (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Manic Miner (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Manic Miner (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="155037" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Match Day II (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Match Day II</name>
		<desc>The original Match Day was the first serious football game to hit the Spectrum, and this sequel emerged over 2 years later. League and Cup tournaments for up to 8 teams (any or all of which can be human-controlled) are offered alongside one-off Friendly matches with a handicap option - passcodes are given to allow you to restore these to the same state another day.

Matches are seven-a-side, with variable lengths from 10 to 30 minutes. All kicks except set pieces are variable in strength using a Kick-o-meter which is displayed on screen. One revolutionary feature of the game was the Diamond Deflection System, which mathematically calculated the angle and pace of any rebounds.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>2A924355</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Match Day II (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Match Day II (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Match Day II (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="129871" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Match Day (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Match Day</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jon Ritman, Chris Clarke, Guy Stevens</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>FA16964E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Match Day (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Match Day (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Match Day (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="123620" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Match Point (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Match Point</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psion Software Ltd, Steve Kelly</developer>
		<publisher>Sinclair Research</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>A865BE98</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Match Point (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Match Point (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Match Point (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45436" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Maziacs (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Maziacs</name>
		<desc>Maziacs is a maze game. The maze in Maziacs has no edges but has around 100 locations and a new maze is generated at each game start. The aim of Maziacs is to find the treasure and take it to the point the game started.

All scattered over the maze are prisoners, food, swords and treasures for you to collect but you are chased by monsters that will attack you.

A sword can only kill one Maziac, a hostile and horrible monster and it's only possible to carry one item at the time. Without a sword, you can still fight Maziacs, but your chances of victory are much lower. 

You need to collect food or you will die of starvation.

To find the treasure you should ask the prisoners who can show you the way, but only for a short distance. The route will turn yellow for a short time.

The prisoners will also tell you the way back to your starting point.
As you can only carry one item at the time it is best to kill as many Maziacs on your way to the treasure.
</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>dk'tronics</developer>
		<publisher>dk'tronics</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>5C1D23C9</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Maziacs (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Maziacs (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Maziacs (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45448" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mercenary - Escape from Targ (Europe).TZX</path>
		<name>Mercenary: Escape from Targ - The Second City</name>
		<desc>Mercenary: The Second City is an expansion disk for Mercenary, which features the same gameplay and controls.

Following the successes over Targ's Central City, the controller of the BENSON computer relaxes and enjoys himself. Soon however, he grows bored and starts looking around for new challenges on the still hazardous Planet Targ. Rumors about the Palyar Commander's brother-in-law living in the southern hemisphere suggest that this may be a good challenge. In this Second City, the battle between Palyars and Mechanoids still rages... and nothing is as it seems.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Novagen Software Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Novagen Software Ltd</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>57937303</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Mercenary - Escape from Targ (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mercenary - Escape from Targ (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mercenary - Escape from Targ (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45467" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mined-Out (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Mined-Out</name>
		<desc>The semi-amusingly-named Mined-Out involves guiding a character across a screen covered with mines. He can move in any of the four main directions. At each point he is told how many of these four squares have mines in, but not the exact locations of the mines, making completion a precarious challenge. There are 8 skill levels, each with progressively more and more mines. After each level you are showed an 'action replay' of your path, as well as a full diagram of where each mine was.
</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quicksilva Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Microparadise Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3E577060</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Mined-Out (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mined-Out (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mined-Out (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45477" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Monty Python's Flying Circus (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Monty Python's Flying Circus</name>
		<desc>Monty Python's Flying Circus is an arcade style game based on the UK television series of the same name. Players control one of the "Mr. Gumbies" and maneuver him through multiple screens, throwing fish at flying feet and similarly surreal enemies. Periodically the game cuts away to a non-sequitur aside, such as a lesson on "the larch," or a quick game of breakout.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Games</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>7C95C097</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Monty Python's Flying Circus (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Monty Python's Flying Circus (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Monty Python's Flying Circus (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="130298" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Moon Strike (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Moon Strike</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Mirrorsoft</publisher>
		<hash>69EDD7B7</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Moon Strike (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Moon Strike (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="133068" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mr. Freeze (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Mr. Freeze</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>David T. Clark</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6733A8F8</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Mr. Freeze (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mr. Freeze (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mr. Freeze (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45507" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Myth - History in the Making (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Myth: History in the Making</name>
		<desc>In this platform game, you are a mere mortal who has been called by the Gods to defeat several mythological creatures that have been turned bad by the evil Dameron.

Myth: History in the Making is a platform game with a lot of fighting. The levels of this game deal with different mythologies, from ancient Greece to the Vikings, over to Valhalla (where none other than the hammer-wielding Thor awaits you), and more.

Apart from jumping from platform to platform, you'll also fight the enemies and bosses in your path with a variety of weapons - in the beginning you have only fists to defend yourself, but later you'll find more powerful weapons, such as swords and axes. There are many various types of enemies, different on every level. Typically, enemies keep appearing and coming at you from all sides, no matter how many of them you kill - so you have to keep moving. 

Some obstacles in the game require not only brute force, but also a bit of thinking and puzzle-solving (and guesswork) to get past.
</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>System 3 Software, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>System 3 Software, Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>697F0108</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Myth - History in the Making (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Myth - History in the Making (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Myth - History in the Making (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45517" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Nemesis the Warlock (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Nemesis the Warlock</name>
		<desc>2000AD hero Nemesis must defeat the evil Torquemada, the Grand Master of Termight, and the hordes of Terminators he has dispatched. The game is set on a succession of 30 single-screen levels comprising of networks of platforms. You are armed with a gun (with limited ammunition) and a sword, and must kill a set amount of Terminators on each level. Terminators follow a set pattern, so you can work out which ledges they will reach next. Dead Terminators remain on the screen - when you are not doing well, Torquemata can sometimes turn these into vicious scythe-wielding zombies.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Creative Reality</developer>
		<publisher>Martech Games</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>335B2145</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Nemesis the Warlock (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nemesis the Warlock (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Nemesis the Warlock (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="138891" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Nemesis (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Nemesis</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cyclone, Stuart J. Ruecroft</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>B07D5B31</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Nemesis (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nemesis (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Nemesis (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45525" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Nigel Mansell's Grand Prix (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Nigel Mansell's Grand Prix</name>
		<desc>Nigel Mansell's first licensed computer game recreates all 16 Formula 1 circuits of the time, viewed from behind the car but with a full cockpit-type view below. This is important because the game is very much a simulation rather than an action game.

Before each race you have to do three qualifying laps, and only make the grid if you are fast enough to meet the pre-defined qualifying limit. The races can be between 5 and 20 laps, or at full length if you prefer - fortunately a half-finished season can be saved to cassette or disk. 

F1 cars of this era have turbo boosts, and this is available in the game to provide a quick blast of extra speed, which is useful for overtaking but can cause the turbo or the engine itself to be overstressed, as well as using fuel more quickly (pitstops are for tires but not fuel, again in keeping with the era's real Formula 1 rules).
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DJL Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Martech Games</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9F9C63AC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Nigel Mansell's Grand Prix (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Nigel Mansell's Grand Prix (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Nigel Mansell's Grand Prix (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45543" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./North &amp; South (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>North &amp; South</name>
		<desc>Based on the Belgian comic book, "Les Tuniques Bleues", this strategy game allows you to replay the American Civil War from both the North and the South sides.

In the strategy part of the game, you can move your troops on a map of the US. If two opposing armies enter the same state, the battle is played out in an action sequence. Additional action sequences must be accomplished when capturing an enemy fort or train.

The game also offers a two-player-mode.
</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>9BEEB0A6</hash>
		<image>./mixart/North &amp; South (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/North &amp; South (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/North &amp; South (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45562" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Operation Thunderbolt (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Operation Thunderbolt</name>
		<desc>Operation Thunderbolt is the exciting sequel to Operation Wolf. An airliner is hijacked by terrorists en-route from Paris to Boston, who threaten to kill all hostages on board if their mates aren't released from jail. Instead of reaching its destination, the airliner makes a landing in Kalubya, Africa, and all the hostages are hidden in various locations. The authorities have asked the hero from Operation Wolf to rescue the hostages, but only this time, the hero brings his friend along for the ride.

There are eight missions to complete in Operation Thunderbolt, and each one has you shooting down soldiers, choppers, and tanks. The gameplay varies every one or two missions. In some missions, you are driving a jeep or controlling a boat, while in others, you are walking while you're shooting. You have a limited supply of ammo, and a limited supply of rocket bombs, but you can always stock up by shooting down crates falling from the sky, or by killing a cat or dog that get in the line of fire. Also from crates, you can get special items like bulletproof vests, rocket bombs, and different weapons.

You also have a life bar to worry about. If you're shot at by soldiers, or if rocket bombs or grenades are thrown at you, you 'll lose energy, and once you're energy is depleted,  you lose one of your three lives. You can lose a lot of energy by killing hostages on purpose,  and you can't easily avoid killing them if you decide to use rocket bombs to wipe out enemies. The eighth mission, the mission that involves you fighting terrorists on a plane,  proves to be difficult because a woman in a blue dress stands up and gets in the line of fire, and you have to very careful when you're going to use rocket bombs.

There are two endings to this game, and which ending you can watch will depend on the number of hostages you've saved, and whether or not you shot the pilot instead of the mission eight boss.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>3D45AAA3</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Operation Thunderbolt (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Operation Thunderbolt (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Operation Thunderbolt (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45563" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Operation Wolf (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Operation Wolf</name>
		<desc>You have been recruited for Operation Wolf, a desperate attempt to rescue prisoners from the enemy. Through a series of missions, you'll engage a variety of enemies, from soldiers to ninjas, patrol boats to helicopters, and more. Can you carry the day?

Operation Wolf is an arcade conversion of the game by Taito. It is essentially a bitmapped "rail-shooter", where you basically hold the gun and shoot just about everything that moves, while conserving your ammo and grenades. Shoot ammo/grenades and healing items on the screen to "pick them up". Your primary machine gun can kill everything if you hit it enough times, but you can also use the grenade launcher for really deadly targets like helicopters or armored cars. You can collect a machine gun which will allow you to shoot faster for a few seconds. 

You'll be pummelled by a LOT of enemies. Some will be shooting, others will be tossing grenades, knifes, and more. Some are armored and requires more than a few hits, others dodges. You can shoot grenades and knifes out of the air if you aim well enough. There are also civilians running around which can be shot, but it's not beneficial. 

Bosses appear at the end of some levels, and each has a specific weakness you need to exploit.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>CB6D70B8</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Operation Wolf (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Operation Wolf (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Operation Wolf (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45577" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pac-Mania (Europe).TZX</path>
		<name>Pac-Mania</name>
		<desc>Pac-Mania is a variation on the game Pac-Man. You need to guide Pac-Man around a maze and eat all of the dots on the board in order to proceed on to the next round. Numerous, multi-colored ghosts also roam the maze trying to stop you. If you eat one of the power pellets in the maze, the ghosts will temporarily turn blue and run from you. Pac-man can earn bonus points by eating the ghosts when they are in this state. The maze is now in 3-D and is larger than screen which will scroll to follow the action. To help get out of tight spots, Pac-Man now has the ability to jump. But be careful, because some of the ghosts have learned this trick as well and you could end up in a mid air collision!
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Grandslam Entertainments Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1CFD94B3</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Pac-Mania (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pac-Mania (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pac-Mania (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45579" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pang (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Pang</name>
		<desc>Pang is a platform game which consists of 50 levels in total. It can be played with one or two players on the same screen, and the other player can join anytime within the game. 

Your goal is to destroy the balloons which bounce around the playfield. To accomplish this, you can shoot hooks which travel upwards, and blow up any balloon they touch. Depending on their size, they either split on two smaller ones, or evaporate if they're at their minimum size. Apart from balloons, some levels also have barriers that have to be destroyed with your hooks, since they often block your access to balloons. There are also some barriers which cannot ever be destroyed. Your character has the ability to climb ladders, but cannot jump. 

You can also pick up power-ups such as: the ability to fire two shots at once, the hook that attaches to the ceiling and waits 'til something bumps into it, a gun which has a high rate of fire but cannot destroy barriers. Beside extra weapons, you can also pick certain things like clock (halting time for a small period), dynamite (reducing all balls to minimum size, thus making you able to reach more points), life, and such.
</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mitchell Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>EBD8FD7A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Pang (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pang (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pang (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45597" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pheenix (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Pheenix</name>
		<desc>Pheenix is a classic shooter, similar to Space Invaders: In five different screens, you have to shoot birds whose droppings prove harmful for your spaceship. Luckily, you can activate a shield that will protect your vessel for a short time (you can't shoot during that time either though).

While the five different screens are similar, each one is unique in its way: In the third screen, you first see eggs flying around before the birds hatch and start unloading on you. And in the fifth screen, you have to destroy the enemy mothership.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Martin W. Ward</developer>
		<publisher>Megadodo</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B2860028</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Pheenix (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pheenix (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pheenix (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45622" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Popeye 2 (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Popeye 2</name>
		<desc>Strange happenings are afoot once again in Sweethaven and only Popeye can make it right. In Popeye 2, our spinach lovin' hero must once again rescue Olive Oyl and make mincemeat of Bluto while looking after Swee'Pea, feeding Wimpy and keeping an eye on Jeep.

Popeye has four different levels to traverse through. His initial adventure takes him to a construction site where bouncing springs, falling girders and open welding flames impede his progress. Rolling barrels, and bombs which must be touched to be put out also stand to cause harm. In every level scattered hamburgers must be collected in order for Popeye to get past Wimpy who is often hanging out somewhere near the top of every vertically scrolling platform level. There are also feats of strength that Popeye must perform by beating up a punching robot-type thing with the aid of Spinach. Once past all these obstacles Popeye can move on to the next level.

The second level takes Popeye into the urban jungle where he must climb the side of the Biff Spinach building and avoid the same obstacles as in the previous levels. In the third level falling girders are replaced with giant bananas as Popeye finds himself in a jungle. Coconut throwing monkeys hang from ledges and snoozing tigers and snakes decorate the trees. The fourth and final level of the game finds Popeye climbing the masts of the S.S. Trev and the S.S. Andy as he makes his way to a final confrontation with Bluto and rescue Olive Oyl.

Popeye is able to jump around and occasionally when the situation calls for it punch his way through this vertical platformer. Bonus points are rewarded for finding Swee'Pea and Jeep. He can take multiple hits before he takes a curtain call but thankfully is unharmed by long drops. The player should beware as Popeye has only one life to get through the four levels of this adventure.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bizarre Developments</developer>
		<publisher>Alternative Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B53C7DA1</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Popeye 2 (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Popeye 2 (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Popeye 2 (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45621" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Popeye (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Popeye</name>
		<desc>The object of the game is to collect hearts and deliver them to Olive Oyle to keep her 'lovemeter' topped up. Points are scored for hearts delivered.
Bluto, UFO's, witches etc try to stop you. Some hearts are behind locked doors so you've got to find the right key to open the door and get them while others can be grabbed simply by jumping up to get them.
Somewhere there's a fruit machine for which you need to collect 'spin' items.

The game boasts a 'clever multidimensional effect' which allows Popeye to go behind the scenery and go through doors.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>dk'tronics</developer>
		<publisher>dk'tronics</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>FA134EA5</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Popeye (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Popeye (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Popeye (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45665" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pyjamarama (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Pyjamarama</name>
		<desc>Wally Week has become trapped inside one of his own nightmares, and is in danger of failing to wake up from it in time for work. Only you can save him from the inevitable sack, by finding the key that can be used to bring your alarm clock to life.

The world inside his head is large and varied, with escalators, lifts and locked doors used to navigate it. Only two objects can be carried at a time, but some must be used in tandem, and others only become active when you walk over them while carrying one or two items they require to become active. 

As this is a nightmare world, not everything is as it seems - everything is enlarged, and axes, punching hands and ghosts are all out to get you. Your energy is measured by a 'Snooze Energy' meter depicted by a glass of milk - once this drops to minimum, one of your 3 lives is lost.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mikro-Gen Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Mikro-Gen Ltd</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>334588A4</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Pyjamarama (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pyjamarama (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pyjamarama (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="161751" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rainbow Islands - The Story of Bubble Bobble 2 (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Rainbow Islands</name>
		<desc>Sequel to Bubble Bobble, Rainbow Islands sees Bub and Bob (in 2 player mode), who are now curiously small boys rather than dinosaurs, attempting to rid the Rainbow Islands of bad guys.

Using the power to cast rainbows, trapping anything underneath, the boys must ascend vertically 4 levels each island, with a big, bad boss at the end of each.

By trapping beasts under your rainbows, then jumping on them to break them you can collect seven different colored gems, and there are also power-ups for extra speed and rainbows.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A5A1B19E</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Rainbow Islands - The Story of Bubble Bobble 2 (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rainbow Islands - The Story of Bubble Bobble 2 (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Rainbow Islands - The Story of Bubble Bobble 2 (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45698" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rastan (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Rastan</name>
		<desc>Rastan features five levels or hacking and slashing gameplay with a boss at the end of each level. Numerous enemies assault you on your journey such as flying demons, chimeras, valkyries, piranhas, skeleton undead and more. Fight through to the end and save the land of Lograth from certain doom.

The game features different weapons such axes, maces and fire swords, each with its own attributes like extended range or attack power. Armour can also be picked up in the forms shields, cloaks and armour, reducing the damage from enemy attacks. Other items include rings (increase the speed of your weapon) and jewelery for bonus points.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>4C4CF0AF</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Rastan (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rastan (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Rastan (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="139643" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rebelstar - 1 Player (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Rebel Star - 2 Players</name>
		<desc>A turn-based, tactical squad combat game for one or two players, from the creator of the later X-COM series.

Moonbase Delta may look like an unassuming mining colony, but in fact, it is the secret location of the ISAAC super-computer, used by the Empire to break the Rebels' secret codes. The Rebelstar Raiders' mission is to break in, get past the patrolling robot guards and destroy the computer. It won't be easy.

Your Raiders each have a specific number of action points per move, which can be allocated to movement, firing and object manipulation. Keys, medical kits and repair droids are among the available objects. Shots can be precise, point-blank (less points used, but less prospect of success), wide-range, or opportunist.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Firebird Software</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>07A9D9A0</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Rebelstar - 1 Player (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rebelstar - 1 Player (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="164982" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rebelstar 2 - 1 Player (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Rebelstar II: Alien Encounter</name>
		<desc>A turn-based, tactical squad combat game from Julian Gollop, creator of the X-COM series.

An alien race is threatening the galaxy. It is up to the Rebelstar Raiders to infiltrate the aliens' home base on the planet Thray 6. They have to get in, steal some alien eggs for research purposes, then get out - fast. There is only a limited time until the rescue ship must leave the planet, and the Raiders had better be on board.

Rebelstar II features a dangerous scenario on a hostile world. Slash through jungles, wade through deadly swamps and enter the alien base, where the Queen sits, guarding her eggs.
</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Target Games Ltd, Julian Gollop, Ian Terry</developer>
		<publisher>Silverbird</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>636E5844</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Rebelstar 2 - 1 Player (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rebelstar 2 - 1 Player (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45714" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Renegade (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Renegade</name>
		<desc>This is the conversion of Taito's scrolling beat 'em up, which later produced unofficial sequels Target: Renegade and Renegade III: The Final Chapter.  The game is set on the mean streets of Brooklyn, which you must venture through to meet your girlfriend, and then rescue her from her kidnappers. This is split into five levels, taking you through the subway and the docks as well as some inhospitable streets. A wide range of aggressive moves are on offer, including headbutts, kicks, punches and flying kicks. Much of the game's violence is depicted in a fairly tongue-in-cheek style, with an element of attempted humour along the way.
</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>51AE57AE</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Renegade (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Renegade (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Renegade (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45719" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rescue (Mastertronic) (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Rescue</name>
		<desc>Aliens are attacking the research station. As the security chief you have to guide the scientists to the rescue ship, along with their experiments, when they each wake up and start running around. Rescue as many as you can, because one of them has the answer to winning the whole war, but you don't know which. And don't forget to collect fuel for the trip.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Icon Design Ltd, Ste L. Cork, Mark O'Neill, Tiny Williams</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3A8A9782</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Rescue (Mastertronic) (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rescue (Mastertronic) (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Rescue (Mastertronic) (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45742" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Robocop 2 (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>RoboCop 2</name>
		<desc>RoboCop 2 is a mission-based platform game. Missions have various objectives, such as destroying nukes or killing all the enemies. If you didn't destroy/kill enough, you'll be transported to a training mission, which is a first-person perspective shoot 'em up. Should you also fail the training, you must go to the beginning of the previous mission. Successfully completed mission or enough points scored by training allow you to proceed to the next stage. Unlike in the first RoboCop, there's no time limit, and you are able to jump.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E51FC385</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Robocop 2 (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Robocop 2 (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Robocop 2 (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45743" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Robocop 3 (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>RoboCop 3</name>
		<desc>RoboCop 3 is a side-scrolling platform shooter. You get missions (such as rescuing your colleagues who are being kept hostages), which are divided into several smaller levels. The levels usually consist of several platforms, and are heavily populated by enemies who shoot at you. You can gather special repair kits, which will be used to restore your health after you've completed a level. "RoboCop 3" is more of a shooter than its predecessors, having more and tougher enemies.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1DFE4A46</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Robocop 3 (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Robocop 3 (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Robocop 3 (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45741" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Robocop (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>RoboCop</name>
		<desc>Patrolman Alex Murphy was killed on the streets of Detroit. The major corporation there, Omni Consumer Products (OCP) saw an opportunity to sell a new kind of law enforcement officer to the troubled city. They took what was left of Murphy, encased it in titanium armor, wiped his memory and created RoboCop. Now it's up to RoboCop to clean the streets of Detroit and eliminate the one responsible for his murder, Clarence Boddicker. But it looks like Clarence might not be the kingpin of this town...

Based on the 1987 movie of the same name, RoboCop allows the player to control RoboCop. The majority of the game is a side scroller. RoboCop can punch unarmed citizens and shoot armed citizens. He can move left, right and duck but can not jump. Different weapons can be picked up from enemies, and power-ups to restore health and/or energy. Following levels, RoboCop will have to match a criminal's face to the proper mugshot and engage in a first-person shooting bonus round.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3DDD1476</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Robocop (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Robocop (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Robocop (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45746" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Robotron 2084 (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Robotron: 2084</name>
		<desc>This is a port of the arcade game of the same name.

You are a mutant human, who by some freak of nature has the ability to shoot energy pulses from his body in eight different directions! Your job is simple: save humanity from their own creation -- the ROBOTRONS! The gameplay is pretty unique for the time. You can move and fire in any of eight directions. You get thrown in a room with various evil baddies strewn about, you've got to kill all the robots while at the same time finding some way to grab humans and avoid death.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Williams Electronic Games, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Atarisoft</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B1927007</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Robotron 2084 (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Robotron 2084 (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Robotron 2084 (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45755" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rod-Land (Europe).TZX</path>
		<name>Rodland</name>
		<desc>Taking a rather literal view of the term 'slap-stick humour', Rodland features two fairies called Tam and Rit, whose mission is to rescue their mum who's been captured and taken to a castle. 

There are 40 screens to clear, all full of baddies, who are disposed of by grabbing them with a stick, and flipping them from side to side to inflict damage. The hits needn't all be inflicted at the same time, as it's possible to release them to move them out of the way.

When killed, each bad guy releases some kind of extra, ranging from points bonuses to various devices which can be used to kill other enemies.

Each level also contains a certain amount of fruit. If you can collect all of this (with some bad guys still alive - you move on immediately once they're gone) you enter a bonus game, in which each enemy's death results in one of the letters E,X,T,R and A being released - collect them all for an invaluable extra life.

In the Game Boy version the difficulty lies slightly lower because the player can use his wand even when climbing ladders.
</desc>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Storm</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>8F1A934A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Rod-Land (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rod-Land (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Rod-Land (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45764" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./R-Type (Europe).TZX</path>
		<name>R-Type</name>
		<desc>R-Type is a side scrolling shoot 'em up best known for its extremely tough and strategic gameplay.  You control the R-9 spaceship as it launches a last-ditch effort to repel the evil Bydo empire.

The R-9 comes equipped as standard with a small gun which can only take down the smallest of enemies without firing several shots. By holding down the fire button, it can be loaded up so as to release a large burst of energy, eliminating all but the strongest enemies in its path. From time to time, pods will come flying in your direction. Upon being shot, they release an upgrade. The first one will invariably be the one called "The Force", which is a weapons pod that clings either to the front or the back of your ship, absorbing any enemy bullets or acting as a bumper with which you can fly head-on into them. You can also use it as an offensive weapon by firing it and pulling it back in. Mastering the Force is vital to surviving in R-Type, since it must be used both as protection against bullet clusters, as a remote controlled cannon, and in order to clear the screen from obstacles. Other upgrades give you target-seeking missiles or a bigger main gun. Different gun types, differentiated by their colour, serve different purposes. The blue one sends laser beams bouncing across the screen (good for tunnels), the red one fires straight ahead, and the yellow one follows any walls it may encounter (good for artillery emplacements).

The stages of R-Type are made in an organic style, certainly inspired by H. R. Giger's artwork for the Alien movies. When it came out, it was considered trend-setting since it broke off from the stereotypical sci-fi mould of other shoot'em'ups. In part, the levels themselves are your enemy, which is exemplified by the fourth, where spider-like creatures weave webs that cover the screen and block your path, or levels with intricate tunnel systems. Still, the levels are best handled with a combination of strategy and reflexes, without the memorisation that is required of R-Type's contemporary rival, Gradius.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Electric Dreams Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9442E177</hash>
		<image>./mixart/R-Type (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/R-Type (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/R-Type (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="161654" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Saboteur II - Avenging Angel (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Saboteur II</name>
		<desc>The ninja hero of the original Saboteur game has been killed, and his sister Nina is out to avenge this injustice. She has an array of kung-fu moves on offer, and must put them to use through 700 screens of action. The game design is very similar to the original, right down to the unusual background graphical style. The sections of the game are on multiple levels, separated mainly by ladders, and with lots of weapons and ammunition to pick up along the way. To beat the game you'll have to collect tapes and collect a 14-part computer code.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Durell Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Durell</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>FABA784F</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Saboteur II - Avenging Angel (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Saboteur II - Avenging Angel (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Saboteur II - Avenging Angel (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45774" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Saboteur (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Saboteur</name>
		<desc>Saboteur combines platform, beat 'em up and adventure elements, setting you as a lone samurai trying to infiltrate an enemy complex. You are capable of all manner of ninja-style moves including kicks and punches, as well as using weaponry. You must travel through an underground complex linked mainly by platforms and ladders, before triggering a bomb and escaping the complex. Your energy recharges if you stay still, so finding areas free of guards (kill these for money) and dogs (avoid them; killing them gains you nothing) is useful, especially as you only have one life. There's plenty of object manipulation involved, although only one item can ever be carried at a time.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Durell Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Durell Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>4C8381D8</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Saboteur (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Saboteur (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Saboteur (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45776" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sabre Wulf (1984)(Ultimate).tzx</path>
		<name>Sabre Wulf</name>
		<desc>The ACG amulet (a reference to Ultimate's formal name of Ashby Computers and Graphics), has been split into four pieces, which are located in different parts of a jungle, and you're the intrepid explorer sent to locate them.

The game takes place on a thoroughly huge map, and the viewed area often includes section which overlap and can't be reached directly, due to the huge shrubs and trees which are used as borders.

The gameplay has many similarities to Ultimate's earlier Atic Atac title (even though they charged almost twice as much for it). It combines shooting (creatures such as spiders and hippos are among the many ferocious delights on show), and puzzle solving, largely involving manoeuvring objects. Once you run out of lives, the game tells you the percentage completed; chances are you'll be surprised that hours of exploration only cover half of it.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>0EAEC7CE</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Sabre Wulf (1984)(Ultimate).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sabre Wulf (1984)(Ultimate).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sabre Wulf (1984)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45841" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sim City (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Sim City</name>
		<desc>SimCity sets you as the mayor of a new municipality, with the responsibility of building and maintaining a place where citizens can move to and work and be happy. The first task is to place essentials such as housing, transport links, schools, factories and shops. There are 50 types of these, allowing for homes of all standards and different types of businesses. Make sure to consider which sites are effective for which tasks. Some power sources pollute, others don't but are more expensive. Taxes must be raised to ensure an income, and then portions allocated to public services such as policing and roads. Earthquakes, floods and fires are all emergency situations that must be dealt to contain any damage.

Successful mayoring will cause the small village to grow into a town, then a city and finally a metropolis. As the city's size grows so do it's needs. Commercial buildings may suddenly find that they need an airport to expand trade, or housing may find itself changing rapidly as vast amounts of people come and leave.

The game also includes 8 pre-defined time-limited scenarios, with specific challenges and targets. The environment varies in each game (especially if you have the Terrain Editor add on), and this should affect your choices.
</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maxis Software Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software, S.A.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>114F9CCC</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Sim City (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sim City (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sim City (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45848" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Sir Lancelot (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Sir Lancelot</name>
		<desc>In this Manic Miner variant Sir Lancelot is exploring a castle in the hope of finding treasures. He must navigate his way through 24 platform screens (in a predefined order on the Spectrum but in any order on the Amstrad), collecting every object on each one to reveal the exit within a time limit. 

There are enemies on fixed attack paths to avoid - Lancelot has no weapon but can jump, and survive any length of fall. Avoiding contact is thus a case of jumping out of their way, and using lower ledges to strategically time his moves. There are sections you can freely climb but not descend, so timing and forward planning are important. Contact with any of these costs one of your four lives, and resets the screen to its starting position.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Studio B Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>9EFDB792</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Sir Lancelot (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sir Lancelot (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Sir Lancelot (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45854" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Skool Daze (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Skool Daze</name>
		<desc>This highly original game concept sets you as Eric, a typical scamp of a schoolboy whose school report is due, and it is so bad that his parents can't be allowed to see it. This means retrieving it from the headmaster's safe, by obtaining every piece of the pass-code from the teachers, by hitting each of the shields with your catapult.

All this has to be done around all the rigors of a typical school day. you must go to class when the bell goes, or else it's detention, and the other kids will often play around to block you. The game's Artificial Intelligence means that events continue to unfold around you in the other rooms and corridors.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1FE8DEA5</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Skool Daze (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Skool Daze (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Skool Daze (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45866" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Smash TV (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Smash T.V.</name>
		<desc>The year is 1999. The world's most popular television show is Smash T.V., an ultra-violent contest between two armed-to-the-teeth combatants, set loose in a series of deadly arenas that are filled to bursting with hordes of mindless beasts and killer robots. The aim of the game is to blast everything in sight and try to grab more cash and prizes than the other guy. Toaster ovens, VCRs, fancy cars and luxury holidays are there for the taking... for anyone who can survive long enough to enjoy them.

Smash T.V. is an insane shoot-em-up from the brain of Eugene Jarvis, creator of Robotron: 2084. It retains that game's frantic style of play and two-joystick control method, but adds plenty of gore, violence, a hint of satire and that all-important two player mode.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Williams Electronic Games, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>5339B763</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Smash TV (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Smash TV (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Smash TV (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45890" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Space Crusade (1992)(Gremlin Graphics).tzx</path>
		<name>Space Crusade</name>
		<desc>Space Crusade is a science fiction strategy game converted from the Games Workshop/Milton Bradley boardgame, in which you control a commander and four marines who are sent on different missions aboard hostile alien starships. Your commander starts off as a sergeant, but he can work his way through the ranks. The game allows three players, each commanding one marine chapter each. The alien team is `played` by the computer. 

The game is a literal conversion of the board game in the same vein as Gremlin's earlier Hero Quest. It can be best described as a turn-based board game in which the player must fulfill the primary and secondary objectives to complete the mission, which usually involves elimination of entire alien force on board or destruction of mothership etc. This game features unique 3D close-ups during the battle scenes, a feature which was later adopted by games like the X-Com series.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics</publisher>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<hash>35FB768A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Space Crusade (1992)(Gremlin Graphics).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Space Crusade (1992)(Gremlin Graphics).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Space Crusade (1992)(Gremlin Graphics).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45910" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Spellbound (Mastertronic) (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Spellbound</name>
		<desc>Magic Knight's second game (after Finders Keepers) sees him travelling through time to rescue 8 people including his tutor Gimbal, who have become locked in time thanks to a faulty spell.

The game invented a whole new control system, essentially pioneering the use of icons and windows in adventure games. You control a pointing finger, which can be moved onto each of the menus to reveal sub-menus, which contain the main options for object manipulation. 

All objects can be examined in detail, which produces a visual display of them, and possible clues as to their usage. You must look after your character's health and energy levels - carrying too many objects will progressively weaken him. You must also look after and direct the trapped characters once you locate them.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mastertronic</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic Added Dimension</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E3154424</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Spellbound (Mastertronic) (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Spellbound (Mastertronic) (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Spellbound (Mastertronic) (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45920" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Splat! (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Splat!</name>
		<desc>A spider must be guided safely through a maze, eating all the patches of grass. The screen scrolls in four directions, and the walls of the level are in a different pattern on each level, and must always be avoided for fear of losing a life. The main thing making life harder is that the level is always scrolling in random directions, and contact with the wall at the edge of the screen costs you a life. As a result, careful planning is required to ensure that you don't get trapped into a corner. There are seven levels of increasing difficulty to get through.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Incentive Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Incentive Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B180A781</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Splat! (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Splat! (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Splat! (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45929" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Spy vs Spy III - Arctic Antics (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Spy vs. Spy III: Arctic Antics</name>
		<desc>The third and final installment (after Spy vs. Spy and Spy vs. Spy: The Island Caper) sees the spies on an arctic island. Once again they're doing their thing - wandering round the island searching for items and setting traps to kill each other (or more frequently themselves).
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>First Star Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Databyte</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>73C74C8B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Spy vs Spy III - Arctic Antics (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Spy vs Spy III - Arctic Antics (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Spy vs Spy III - Arctic Antics (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45928" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Spy vs Spy (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Spy vs. Spy</name>
		<desc>M.A.D. magazines comic strip of the same name comes to life in this game which was designed for one or two players. The innovative split-screen shows both spies at the same time. Play with a friend or against the machine.

The black crow and the white crow are out to beat each other before the time bell rings. Find the needed objects by digging through drawers, closets and furniture in the house. Foil your opponent by setting creative booby traps in the various rooms (a bomb in a dresser drawer, for instance).

Fights ensue when both spies enter the same room.  Find hidden weapons in the rooms to help with those fights, since one of you will die if you run into each other.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>First Star Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Beyond - Challenging Software</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>4B15597B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Spy vs Spy (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Spy vs Spy (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Spy vs Spy (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="161440" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Spy vs Spy II - The Island Caper (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Spy vs. Spy: The Island Caper</name>
		<desc>A follow-up to the first Spy vs Spy game now sees the spies stranded on a desert island. This time, instead of the four items which allow you to leave for the airport, the spies must try to collect 3 pieces of a missile.

There are new traps and a single gun to take part in combat, rather than the big sticks of the previous game.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>First Star Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Databyte</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>78063623</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Spy vs Spy II - The Island Caper (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Spy vs Spy II - The Island Caper (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Spy vs Spy II - The Island Caper (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45950" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Star Wars (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Star Wars</name>
		<desc>You take on the role of Luke Skywalker, aiming to destroy the Death Star. In the first phase you have to pass swarms of TIE Fighters, including dogfighting the one piloted by Darth Vader himself. In the second phase the station's surface is protected by laser towers, third involves attacking its weakest spot - the unprotected exhaust port - with proton torpedos. Your X-Wing starts with six shields, but more can be awarded for good performance. Complete the game and it loops back around at ever-increasing difficulty.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Domark Software, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>826F811A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45952" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Star Wars III - Return of the Jedi (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Star Wars: Return of the Jedi</name>
		<desc>The arcade game from Atari based on the third Star Wars movie features three action sequences inspired by the film. 

First, you control Princess Leia on a speeder bike racing through the forests on Endor. You have to evade trees and deal with enemy troopers by shooting at them or luring them into Ewok traps.

In the second sequence, you control Chewbacca who has captured an Imperial AT-ST Walker, evading tree traps and shooting at enemy walkers. In this sequence, the perspective sometimes switches to the Millennium Falcon which you must guide through a fleet of enemy Star Destroyers and TIE Fighters.

In the final sequence, the Millennium Falcon enters the Death Star and has to make its way to the reactor, surviving more TIE Fighters and laser turrets. Once the reactor is destroyed, you have to get out again before the explosion engulfs the ship.

After the Death Star has been destroyed, the game restarts at the first sequence, but with a higher difficulty.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Domark Software, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B6C903B1</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars III - Return of the Jedi (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars III - Return of the Jedi (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars III - Return of the Jedi (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45954" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Star Wars II - The Empire Strikes Back (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back</name>
		<desc>The arcade game from Atari Games based on the second Star Wars movie features four action sequences inspired by the film. The graphical style is similar to the first Star Wars game, using vector graphics with a first-person perspective.

The first sequence takes place on the ice planet Hoth, where the player must destroy Imperial probe droids. The droids send transmissions to the Empire that can also be targeted and destroyed. Once enough transmissions have been sent, the Empire attacks.

In the second sequence, the player has to fend off Imperial walkers, either by shooting a limited number of tow cables at their feet or by targeting a small area at their head with lasers. But sooner or later, the Rebel base's power generator will be destroyed and the evacuation begins.

In the third sequence, the Millennium Falcon has to destroy TIE Fighters in space.

In the fourth and final sequence, the Falcon must navigate through an asteroid field, avoiding collisions.

Once the four sections have been completed, the game restarts at a higher difficulty level.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Domark Software, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>DA1C78E4</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars II - The Empire Strikes Back (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars II - The Empire Strikes Back (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars II - The Empire Strikes Back (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45944" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Starquake (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Starquake</name>
		<desc>As BLOB, the Bio-Logically Operated Being, you are sent into an unstable planet and charged with the task of preventing it from exploding. This involves collecting various items (the exact combination is different every time you load the game) and taking them to the planet's core.

The game is an arcade adventure viewed from the side, with 512 screens arranged in a 16x32 pattern. A teleport system exists, so once you find the codes you can get quick access to different parts of the game.

The creatures to avoid are intelligent, getting tougher to predict as you get closer to the centre, but you are armed with a gun and can also try to avoid them. BLOB has a set of platforms which can be used to allow limited vertical movement, but these disappear after a few seconds each use.
</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bubble Bus Software</developer>
		<publisher>Zafiro</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>8043260A</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Starquake (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Starquake (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Starquake (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45948" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Starstrike II (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Starstrike II</name>
		<desc>In Realtime's previous Starstrike game (not to be confused with Star Strike), the evil Outsiders attacked the Federation and had to be forced back. This time, the boot's on the other foot, as the Federation have sent their Starstrike II vehicles in to take them out. Armed with sophisticated computers, lasers and shields, all it needs is a good pilot, such as yourself.

Twenty-two planets fall under Outsiders control, and each has grid-based defenses which must be taken out, complete with all their command computers and production droids. The planets are split into five groups, each of which can be chosen at the start of the game. 

The combat is intense, and aims to create the likely feel of space combat, with lots of ducking and weaving to set up shots. The game features filled-in graphics, unlike the Elite-esque wireframes of the first game.
</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realtime Games Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Realtime Games Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>18262188</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Starstrike II (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Starstrike II (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Starstrike II (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="129891" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Stunt Car Racer (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Stunt Car Racer</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Geoff Crammond, Pete Cooke</developer>
		<publisher>Micro Style</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>F4D058DE</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Stunt Car Racer (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Stunt Car Racer (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Stunt Car Racer (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45990" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Super Hang-On (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Super Hang-On</name>
		<desc>This is a conversion of Sega's popular motorcycle racing arcade game.  In this game you race a motorcycle around the world, completing each section of track within a time limit. There are other bikes on the road, but beating this is not important, so they can be thought of as moving obstacles. Each continent is a different difficulty level: Africa is beginner, Asia is junior, the Americas are senior, and Europe is expert.  

This is a very simple and straightforward game, viewed from behind the bike in 2D (so the screen does not tilt with the bike). The right/left controls are steering, and up/down are gear changes. Your cycle is always moving, and your speed strictly depends on the gear you are in, although contact or running off the road slows the bike down.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Electric Dreams Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>FD445A8B</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Super Hang-On (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Hang-On (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Super Hang-On (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46014" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Switchblade (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Switchblade</name>
		<desc>The Fireblade, sacred symbol of the ancient Switchblade clan, has been smashed into 16 pieces by the evil Havoc - but they say that a Hiro can save it, and as Hiro, you must retrieve the 16 pieces and restore your people's pride.

The gameplay is platform and ladders based, set both inside and outside. The layout of the territories becomes visible as you progress, and they can contain bonus weapons and secret rooms. Unlike the sequel you start without weaponry, and this is gained directly, rather than you collecting coins and trading them at shop sections. Holding down fire progressively builds up your fighting power.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>CAE096C8</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Switchblade (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Switchblade (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Switchblade (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46024" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tapper (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Tapper</name>
		<desc>Tapper is an action game where you're a beer tapper (barman) and have to serve beer to demanding customers. There are four customers, each has its own lane lengthier than the previous one, whom you have to keep at bay. If they reach the end of the lane without receiving their beer, you're a goner; if you miss one and accidentally spill beer needlessly you lose a life and should one of them throw you back the mug and you fail to catch it, you lose a life as well.

Occasionally a bizarre icon will appear on one of the lines and, should you grab it, will invoke a "cabarette"-style show which will keep some of the customers occupied.

The Xbox 360 version includes bonus rounds, as well as co-op and versus multiplayer modes, also online, along with achievements.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bally Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>FFB98D87</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Tapper (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tapper (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Tapper (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46026" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Renegade II - Target Renegade (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Target: Renegade</name>
		<desc>Mr. Big is back in town, and this time he's captured your brother! He's being held at Big's Pig Pen which is located on the upper side of town. The problem is, every gang in the city is out looking for you. It is now up to you to beat the odds and rescue your brother. You start the game armed only with your fists, and along the way there are some additional weapons to be found such as baseball bats or garbage cans. Gameplay is an arcade style side scrolling action game for one player.
</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagine</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software, S.A.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>01941B89</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Renegade II - Target Renegade (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Renegade II - Target Renegade (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Renegade II - Target Renegade (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46031" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Technician Ted (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Technician Ted</name>
		<desc>Ted is an enthusiastic worker at a computer chip factory, which takes the form of dozens of hazardous platform screens, most of which lead to more than 2 other rooms, through holes in the floor and ceiling as well as a lift. Each room is littered with moving sprites as well as lava pits and dangerous drops, all of which will drain the energy from Ted's single life.

Ted has 21 tasks to complete in this 8 1/2 hour-day, but it is largely up to him to find out what they are, and which order to do them in. The full day includes trips to the canteen, photocopier, power generator and the boss' office - logic will give you clues as to when these are to be accomplished.

He knows that solving one problem can change the nature of another, due to the program's advanced Event Processing. In each room, two flashing boxes must be hit, sometimes within a time limit, and Ted knows the location of the first few of these. On the technical side the game promises a full uninterrupted soundtrack and super-smooth animation.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hewson Consultants Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson Consultants Ltd</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>B2F8FB89</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Technician Ted (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Technician Ted (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Technician Ted (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46048" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tetris (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Tetris</name>
		<desc>The original commercially-licensed version of Alexey Pajitnov's classic Tetris puzzle game.  Geometric shapes fall from the top of a playfield to rest on the bottom; fit the pieces together, and the line they form disappears.  If the pieces don't form lines and eventually stack up to the top of the playfield, the game is over.  Difficulty increases by dropping the pieces faster and faster over time.

Tetris is a verifiable classic game, translated to well over 200 electronic and computer platforms.  It takes 2 minutes to learn, but a lifetime to master.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Spectrum Holobyte, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Mirrorsoft Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>18C7D714</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Tetris (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tetris (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Tetris (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45137" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Great Escape, The (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>The Great Escape</name>
		<desc>The Great Escape is an isometric action-adventure game.

Gather round, kids, and listen to grandpa tell of his time as a prisoner of war in Germany. Was back in 1942. Those were rough times, lads. Rough times. Been shot down in my plane. Darn shame it was, it being a good plane and all. Next I know, theres this group of German soldiers standing round me, and off we go to a P.O.W. camp. Big thing, that, plenty of guards all around with a keen eye on your every move, and full of unfortunate souls like myself. Just that they do naught but sit all day and sob and generally be no great help when it comes to doing the Great Escape. But not me, no sir! I showed them Germans, I did, and I was out of their fashionable high security he who comes here, stays here camp in no time. You wanna hear that story? Bet you do!

Controlling a prisoner of war in a German camp, your goal is to break out undetected. There are numerous ways to freedom back doors, cracked fences, even underground tunnels. However, you have to plan your escape while obeying the strict rules of the camp. 

Number one: Daily program. You have to attend two roll calls a day, one meal, one exercise, and stay in bed at night. Failure to appear at any of these events will result in the alarm being rung. When you do not touch the controls, your protagonist will move automatically, going to all important events. You have to detect and use gaps in the time-table to explore the camp. 

Rule number two: guard rooms are off limits. If a soldier catches you in a room that is forbidden, you will be placed in solitary confinement. Of course, you have to enter restricted parts of the camp to find items crucial for your escape. The moral flag will turn from green to red to indicate that you are in an area where you shouldnt be. 

Rule no three: no prisoner may carry forbidden objects. When you are caught in a suspicious situation, you will be stripped of all items that you found so far. To avoid that, you have to deposit objects in a safe place. You need to find keys to open locked doors, uniforms for camouflage, flashlights to see in dark tunnels, and many more. 

Rule number four: guard commands are to be obeyed at all times. The German soldiers patrol on fixed routes and have a line of sight. You have to learn the guards routes and sneak past their backs to avoid detection when breaking out. If you are caught, your morale will decrease. If your morale reaches zero, your will to escape is broken.
</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Denton Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>5C0D7AD5</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Great Escape, The (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Great Escape, The (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Great Escape, The (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="162487" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hobbit, The (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>The Hobbit</name>
		<desc>Relive Tolkien's The Hobbit as Bilbo Baggins.  A piece of  Interactive fiction (with graphics to illustrate locations), you follow the plot of Tolkien's book (before the Lord of the Rings trilogy), starting with an encounter with Gandalf and Thorin.

The implementation is rich enough that you can play entirely without pictures if you wish.  Also, gameplay happens in realtime, uncommon for interactive fiction.
</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software Pty., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>69D34042</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Hobbit, The (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hobbit, The (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hobbit, The (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45520" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Neverending Story II, The (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>The Neverending Story II</name>
		<desc>The Neverending Story II is a bizarre platform game which is largely based on the movie. The concept is simple: you're Bastian, and are called forth once again by the Childlike Empress to save Fantasia, the Land of Dreams.

The game itself is indeed a platformer where you have to outrun giants (as in the movie) or push them over ledges. With every level you will be awarded with another advancement in the plot, usually a few pages written on a "book".
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Linel</developer>
		<publisher>Linel Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>319C069D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Neverending Story II, The (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Neverending Story II, The (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Neverending Story II, The (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45521" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Neverending Story, The (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>The Neverending Story</name>
		<desc>The Neverending Story is a text adventure based on the movie by Wolfgang Petersen (rather than the novel by Michael Ende).

The world of Fantasia is about to be destroyed by the "All-consuming Nothing", it needs someone from the "Real World" to believe in it again in order to be saved from falling into oblivion.

The player takes control of the young hero Atreyu who is the only one who can find the savior of Fantasia. The game uses different pictures to show the player's current location as well as the items he is holding, which companions are with him and any events that might be taking place. The game's parser has been deliberately kept simple (it has a vocabulary of about 40 words) in order to allow more room for the game data.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>AEC8248D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Neverending Story, The (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Neverending Story, The (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Neverending Story, The (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="45523" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./New Zealand Story, The (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>The New Zealand Story</name>
		<desc>One day, a kiwi tribe was having fun and games outside the zoo, only to be kidnapped by the evil-minded Leopard Seal, who plans to sell them at the black market. Fortunately, during the kidnapping process, Tiki, leader of the tribe, managed to escape the sack, and her job is to rescue Phee-Phee and the other kiwis scattered around New Zealand, and are held in cages in various locations that include Auckland, Rotorua, Waitomo Caves, Strait Cook, and Mt. Cook. 

If Tiki doesn't rescue a kiwi in a limited amount of time, the devil will appear and try to kill her. When Tiki reaches the outskirts of each city, except Strait Cook, there is a boss waiting to meet Tiki, and kill her by using their own choice of weapons. Also making the rescue mission difficult are several nasties that attempt to throw their own weapons, like bombs and arrows, at her. To defeat these enemies, Tiki shoots at them using her crossbow and arrows. More often than not, when Tiki shoots at enemies, they will leave behind pieces of fruit that she can pick up for points. However, it is likely that Tiki may get other weapons or the letters E, X, T, E, N, and D. Collecting all these letters will result in an extra life, and as for the weapons, they include laser shots, bombs, and fireballs. 

In some levels, a few areas are located further up than just left or right, and the only way that Tiki can go up is by snatching something off the enemy that gives her the ability to fly up. Other areas are underwater, and when Tiki goes underwater, her oxygen  meter decreases, so she has to rise up to the surface again to restore her oxygen levels. Apart from her own weapons, Tiki is able to squirt water at enemies if she gets to the top of the water.
</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>32ED2B0D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/New Zealand Story, The (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/New Zealand Story, The (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/New Zealand Story, The (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="159653" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Train, The - Escape to Normandy (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>The Train: Escape to Normandy</name>
		<desc>In the months before France is liberated by the Allies in World War 2, Germany tries to take Paris' collection of classic paintings. As Resistance member Pierre LeFeu, helped by wounded former engineer Le Duc, must prevent this happening, but taking the paintings by train to Normandy and Allied control.

Once in control of the train, you must set the throttle level, ensure that there is enough coal in the furnace, control the speed, and ensure that steam is released when necessary. Use the provided map, and the communications network once released, to plan the strategic side of your mission. Each station has coal and water supplies which may be needed to keep the train running.

You must raid railway stations in order to get track switches into the right position. Both this and the initial capture of the train involve aiming at the enemy, current indicated point, and ducking before their bullets can hit you. Taking control of bridges is similar - you control a cannon and must take aim.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artech Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>018DEF66</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Train, The - Escape to Normandy (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Train, The - Escape to Normandy (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Train, The - Escape to Normandy (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="138283" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wild Bunch, The (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>The Wild Bunch</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kevin Smith</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>A4BD0FE0</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Wild Bunch, The (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wild Bunch, The (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wild Bunch, The (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="138731" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Think! (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Think!</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The RamJam Corporation, Tony Barber, Simon Dunstan, Don Hughes, Tigress Marketing Ltd, David Bishop, Chris Palmer</developer>
		<publisher>Ariolasoft UK</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>948DF554</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Think! (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Think! (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Think! (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46058" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Three Weeks in Paradise (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Three Weeks in Paradise</name>
		<desc>This place would indeed be paradise, were it not for the fact that the Can Nibbles inhabit it. Herbert and Wilma Week are trapped by them, so Wally has become the third Week in paradise in his attempt at rescuing them.

This is an arcade adventure resembling the other Wally Week games, although it represents David Perry's design debut. There are many animals to avoid including stinging bees and butterflies, but the toughest foe is the Indian chief, best avoided with a well-timed jump. There are multi-stage puzzles to solve on each screen, and a limit of carrying 2 objects at a time.

The setting is largely jungle, but there are forests, beaches and huts amongst other things to explore as well. Movement between screens is generally from left to right, but you will go into the screen via signposted sections, and occasionally travel vertically as well.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mikro-Gen Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Mikro-Gen Ltd</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>453C0948</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Three Weeks in Paradise (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Three Weeks in Paradise (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Three Weeks in Paradise (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46062" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Thrust II (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Thrust II</name>
		<desc>The physics-based gameplay of the original Thrust is back and the controls of your craft are basically the same - swivel left and right, and thrust. While the essence of the game remains very similar there are some differences second time round. 

The Federal Resistance has captured an artificial planet of great strategic importance in the war against the Galactic Empire. However, the purification of the planet's atmosphere is not yet complete.

You must search the planet for 16 orbs, the majority of which lie below the surface, these are required for the construction of an atmospheric processor. This will involve descending into the maze-like tunnels of the planet, avoiding (or destroying) a variety of androids in your path and returning to the surface with the orbs in tow. 

Only one orb can be picked up at a time and they must be put in place at a designated site on the surface. Once an orb is picked up a timer begins counting down; if it's not in place in time the entire planet is destroyed! If your craft (or an orb that has been picked up) collides with the walls or the androids that patrol the passageways then it is instantly destroyed, a shield (life) is lost and play is resumed from a nearby location. Weapon pickups destroy all enemies on the screen of a specific type but can only be used for a limited time. 

Instead of the individual levels in the original game, there is only one game world in Thrust II and the orbs are scattered about in different places; they are also of varying masses and affect the handling of your craft differently.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Simon Clarke, Andrew Rogers, Jeremy C. Smith, J.C.G.</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>D0A8CCA4</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Thrust II (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Thrust II (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Thrust II (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46061" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Thrust (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Thrust</name>
		<desc>Thrust took a unique game style by bringing realistic physics and inertia-based movement into arcade games, directly influencing titles like Oids, not to mention the same author's Exile from Audiogenic. The action is viewed from the side, with the graphics drawn in vectors, in keeping with the mathematical nature of everything that unfolds.

As a Resistance fighter, the player must fly into enemy lines in order to steal Klystron Pods to power more advanced starships, using your tractor beam to take them. A network of mounted guns are aiming to shoot the player down  these can be disabled by shooting their power source, but eventually this will explode, forcing the player to flee. Some of the later levels feature reverse gravity, which is where things really get difficult.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>David Lowe, Simon Clarke</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>80DA936C</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Thrust (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Thrust (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Thrust (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46079" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./T.L.L. - Tornado Low Level (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>TLL: Tornado Low Level</name>
		<desc>TLL sets you as a skilled pilot who must take on a tough mission - shooting out six discs representing enemy strongholds in build-up areas. This must be done by lowering your altitude as you approach each one, making it crucial to avoid trees and buildings which are closer to ground level.

The action is viewed from above using a psuedo-3D display, and scrolls vertically in a manner similar to SWIV. At the side of the screen your altitude and fuel level are displayed, as well as an all-important mini-map. You will frequently have to refuel, which is done by touching down on the carrier. You don't have direct control over the plane's speed, a fact which takes the game out of the realms of simulation somewhat.
</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vortex Software</developer>
		<publisher>Vortex Software</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>4B72107D</hash>
		<image>./mixart/T.L.L. - Tornado Low Level (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/T.L.L. - Tornado Low Level (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/T.L.L. - Tornado Low Level (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46089" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Total Recall (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Total Recall</name>
		<desc>Based on the movie of the same name, Total Recall puts you in charge of Douglas Quaid, who must find a way to Mars in order to find the answers to his two questions: why is he being hunted, and who is hunting him. In order to do this, Quaid must go through level after level of beating up bad guys that get in his way.

Some of the levels differ in gameplay, and range between action and driving scenes. The action scenes mainly require you to collect some items before leaving the level. You have only one chance to complete the current level, which means that if your energy is lost, the game ends. Energy is lost if you are attacked by an obstacle, or if you are shot at by an enemy. You can gain more energy by either collecting some pills or a heart, depending on the platform.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>EEAD81EB</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Total Recall (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Total Recall (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Total Recall (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="143010" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Trashman (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Trashman</name>
		<desc>While few young people aspire to the role of a Dustman, New Generation Software felt they would enjoy pretending to be one on this innovative arcade game.

Each section presents you with a road of houses, drawn from forced-perspective 3D, with flick-scrolling as you move up the road. Each house's dustbin must be collected, emptied and replaced within the time limit, which is indicated by the Bonus timer at the top of the screen. If this reaches zero, you receive the first of 3 warnings -  a third sees you out of a job.

Setting foot on the grass causes the onus to drop more quickly, and there are additional hazards to avoid, including the local cars, which appear to be driven by maniacs, and cyclists and barking dogs, which can both injure you and cause your movement to slow.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>New Generation Software</developer>
		<publisher>Microbyte</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>312D41D7</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Trashman (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Trashman (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Trashman (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46115" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Turbo Esprit (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Turbo Esprit</name>
		<desc>Turbo Esprit puts you in control of a Lotus Esprit cop car, with the challenge of breaking up a drugs gang and protecting the innocent.

A map is built into the car, which can instantly show the positions of the baron's cars - this is crucial because you can't interrupt them before the initial deal is done, as this will simply make them leave and try again another time.

The game's environment is large and varied, with traffic lights, junctions and zebra crossings accurately implemented, and pedestrians to avoid. The roads are multi-laned, and at the end of each road you can turn across, which makes the game's perspective shift in a flick-screen manner. One unusual feature for the time is a saveable high-score table.
</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Durell Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software, S.A.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>1D71C727</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Turbo Esprit (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Turbo Esprit (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Turbo Esprit (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46118" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Turbo the Tortoise (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Turbo the Tortoise</name>
		<desc>After Doctor Mulliner and his assistant Beckett make a mistake using Cybernetic technology prototypes, Mulliners pet tortoise Wal is given super powers. The only way a working machine can be built is for this tortoise to travel through time and collect the required parts from six time periods (Prehistoric, Ice Age, Egyptian, Mediaeval, 20th Century and the Future).

Taking the role of Turbo the Tortoise, the player must travel through six side-scrolling platform levels, each of them well-guarded by enemies. Limited weaponry can be collected, although jumping on the heads of these foes will also kill them. Turbo must allow for moving platforms, switches, fragile platforms and water hazards. Enhancements and extra lives are in hard-to-reach places, often only accessible by using enemy heads as launch pads.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Impact</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>E71792A7</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Turbo the Tortoise (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Turbo the Tortoise (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Turbo the Tortoise (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46121" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Turrican II - The Final Fight (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Turrican II: The Final Fight</name>
		<desc>Turrican II: The Final Fight is a platformer/shooter as typically seen on consoles, but designed for home computers from the ground up.

Its plot is - naturally - very simple: an evil mega-robot called The Machine attacks the United Planets Ship Avalon 1, slaughtering all who resist. All - except Bren McGuire, who manages to escape and slips into the experimental Turrican bionic armor. As Turrican, he strives to show The Machine who's the boss.

Unlike other games of its type, this game contains three levels of horizontal shooter action in the spirit of R-Type or the developers' own Katakis. Six large worlds are to be explored, where you are basically free to go everywhere you want, since there is no automatic scrolling and the levels are packed with hidden extra lives and weapons. All those levels are very different: the first one in the rock desert is pretty colorful with parallaxing rainbow background and happy music, while the following worlds get darker and darker.

Turrican can get some different weapons for his arm cannon:

1. The bounce weapon which rebounds from surfaces into smaller bouncing balls when powered up;
The laser, which can shoots beams as large as Turrican himself when maxed out;
 the multiple shot beam, which can shoot up to five beams covering approximately a 90 degree angle.

 
The Turrican suit weaponry is not limited to the arm cannon however:

1. He also can fire a continuous beam, activated by holding the fire button. This beam can be rotated around Turrican, so it is possible to blast things below him in this way;
Additionally, he can fire power lines by pressing the space bar, resulting in two energy bars as high as the screen going from the Turrican suit to the left and right of the screen, severely damaging enemies in the process;
If the space bar is pressed when the hero is crouching, the Turrican will morph into a shuriken shape. In this state, it will roll to the left or the right, damaging enemies while being invincible and small bombs can be dropped by pressing the fire button;
Finally, the most powerful attack, which can only be used one time per life, can be delivered by pressing the fire button and the space bar at the same time. The Turrican suit will morph into a shuriken shape and fly around the screen for several seconds, while firing shots of the different weapons in multiple directions.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Factor 5 GmbH</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbow Arts Software GmbH</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>79ED029F</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Turrican II - The Final Fight (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Turrican II - The Final Fight (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Turrican II - The Final Fight (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46175" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wheelie (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Wheelie</name>
		<desc>In Wheelie you ride a Zedexaki bike (a combination of the famous Kawasaki brand and the ZX in ZX Spectrum), but this is no ordinary racing game. You are trapped in Nightmare Park, and must find an escape before you can race the Ghost Rider.

The park is made up of four linked levels of road, which you can move up and down at by finding a ramp headed in that direction and moving the joystick in that direction. Standard direction changes on each piece of road must also be navigated.

There are many creatures to avoid or jump over - mutant kangaroos and hedgehogs for starters. Standard hazards such as ramps and school buses are dealt with by pulling a wheelie - in this case, jumping at the last possible moment while at top speed
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>3B8EB9DE</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Wheelie (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wheelie (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wheelie (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="138284" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wild Streets (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Wild Streets - Remake</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>52D458BD</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Wild Streets (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wild Streets (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wild Streets (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46195" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wonder Boy (1987)(Activision).tzx</path>
		<name>Wonder Boy</name>
		<desc>Just when things were going great with Tom-Tom and his girlfriend Tanya, some thug of a woodland king had to kidnap her and hide her away, and Tom-Tom doesn't have a clue where. That's why he has to explore deep dark forests, cross endless oceans, climb treacherous slopes, survive endless volcanoes, and even walk through clouds. But Tom-Tom will never be totally alone. You see, when he goes through the exotic locations, he has to come face to face with its inhabitants, like bees, spiders, snakes, coal-kids, frogs, bats, snails, coyotes, and octopuses, to name a few. The hatchet is Tom-Tom's only line of defense against these menaces.

There are ten areas, each containing four rounds each, but the tenth area can't be accessed unless Tom-Tom collects all the dolls during his rescue mission. During his journey, he can break open different eggs that will reveal hatchets, skateboards, mushrooms, milk, and even guardian angels. You can ride the skateboard through each round, as long as you don't collide with an inhabitant. When you complete each round while still riding the skateboard, you'll start the next round still riding it. As you progress through each round, your vitality will start to get low, but it can be increased by getting milk, mushrooms, potato chips,or fruit that appear everywhere you go. As well as the normal eggs, there are also speckled eggs that must be avoided, otherwise the God of Death will be released, and once he follows you, you'll lose vitality much quickly. At the end of every fourth round, there is a king waiting to destroy you with his fireballs or lightning bolts.

There are also warp-gates, but you don't find them, they find you. You see, warp-gates appear in rounds 1-4 of each area. If you happen to get one fruit, a special item will appear. These special items include handbags, wrist watches, a pair of shoes, a teddy bear, and a bottle of perfume. Another girl will appear and take you up to the clouds where the object is to collect as many hearts as you can without falling down or getting the item again. Once you have collected all the hearts, you can get the item to return to the surface, and more often than not, you'll get further in the round.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<hash>BFB15A92</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Wonder Boy (1987)(Activision).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wonder Boy (1987)(Activision).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wonder Boy (1987)(Activision).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="46206" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Wriggler (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Wriggler</name>
		<desc>One of the few games to set you as a maggot, in Wriggler you must negotiate the four stages of the Maggot Marathon. This involves trekking through a garden, a shrubbery, an underground lair, and finally a mansion. 

Viewed form above the game is maze-based, with lots of Atic Atac style sections where you can see other parts of the level on the same screen, but can't access them because the design of the maze puts something in the way. Graphics are quite large and chunky - this is perhaps the closest anyone came to borrowing Rapscallion's unusual visual design.

You have an energy bar which decreases constantly, and contact with the ants, spiders and the rest of the sickly creatures reduces this further. Fortunately you can obtain apples, cherries, cups of tea (I suspect a generation of sadistic 10-year-olds started trying to ply worms with caffeine as a result of this) and other foodstuffs to recharge this. These can be eaten immediately or stored for later use, however you can only hold one object at a time. Many other items are needed to get past situations during the game, so be careful what you keep to avoid too much backtracking through the 256 screens.
</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Devonshire House</developer>
		<publisher>Romantic Robot UK</publisher>
		<players>1</players>
		<hash>6C65A021</hash>
		<image>./mixart/Wriggler (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wriggler (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Wriggler (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien (1984)(Argus Press Software).tzx</path>
		<name>Alien</name>
		<desc>"In space no-one can hear you scream."
That tagline from the movie is apt for this strategy adaptation that follows the plotline of the first movie in the franchise. The action starts after the chestburster scene which unleashes an alien organism into their enclosed spaceship.  The remaining crew members must attempt to destroy it while the traitorous android tries to protect the alien.  

There are 3 decks to search with 35 different rooms which are connected by ducts which the alien can use to sneak up on people.  You can herd the alien into an airlock to blast it out into space, or set the auto-destruct on the ship and flee in the shuttle with all remaining live crew members plus Jones the cat who must be found and put in a box.

The screen shows you a plan of the deck you are on, and the ducts in the immediate area.  There are trackers and sensors which can be used to pinpoint movement in other areas.  In ordering each crew member, you are given possible movements or other actions such as picking up weapons, entering the ducts or catching the cat. In certain situations, special options will appear such as starting the self-destruct system when in the command centre. The responses to orders are also affected by the personality of the crew member, and how much they have had to suffer. 

The screen also displays reports on the condition of the crew member youve selected, whether there is any damage to the room youre in and whether the duct grills are open (meaning the Alien has been through there). You also get the occasional message from the ship's computer Mother like when a crew member dies.  Sound effects create suspense. At times you hear the alien move around or doors and grills being opened as well as the blip from the tracker.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Alien (1984)(Argus Press Software).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Alien (1984)(Argus Press Software).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Alien (1984)(Argus Press Software).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Concept Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Argus Press</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3D Starstrike (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>3D Starstrike</name>
		<desc>The Outsiders have attacked the Earth Federation, laying waste to its defense fleets. In desperation, Federation Command sends the new Starstrike space fighters to attack the Outsiders's main bases (which are converted moons), hoping to exploit a fatal flaw in the design: a direct hit to the reactor at the center of the base might lead to its destruction.

Both regarding graphics and gameplay, 3D Starstrike is essentially a clone of Atari's Star Wars. Using wireframe graphics with a first-person perspective, the player controls the Starstrike fighter in several distinct phases: the first phase is the approach to the enemy base, where Outsider space fighters must be destroyed. The second phase takes place close to the surface of the base, where enemy bunkers and laser towers await. The third phase is a trench run, where gun turrets await at the side of the trench, and catwalks blocking the way must be dogded. The run culminates in the reactor room, where two reactor pods must be hit to destroy the base.

After a base is destroyed, the game continues with a new base in the next level, with later levels having a higher difficulty.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/3D Starstrike (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/3D Starstrike (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/3D Starstrike (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realtime Games Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Realtime Games Software Ltd.</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chase H.Q. (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Chase H.Q.</name>
		<desc>As an undercover agent of Chase Headquarters, your job is to patrol the streets and track down five criminals. You are given a mission briefing before you start which gives information on the suspect and what car they drive. Then you drive across the city without crashing into other cars, and catch up with the criminal's car. To arrest the suspects, you must keep bumping into their car until it is no longer functional. And you have to do this under a strict time limit. You can't afford to crash into cars or buildings or you waste time getting on the road again. 

However, once you've caught up with your suspect, you are given more time. Your car is also equipped with turbo boosts, which you can use to gain extra speed if you are way behind the criminal. Each arrest is based on a "suspicion".
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Chase H.Q. (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Chase H.Q. (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Chase H.Q. (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Arkanoid (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Arkanoid</name>
		<desc>The original Breakout concept involves controlling a bat at the bottom of the screen and using it to catch and direct a ball so as to hit all the bricks which are arranged at the top of the screen. It was unpopular for over a decade, before Taito revived it with some new ideas in this arcade game.

The game's plot redefines the bat as a Vaus spaceship, the ball as an energy bolt, and the bricks form a mysterious wall stopping the ship from progressing to safety.

By the mid-80s, power-ups were popular in most types of arcade games, and Arkanoid features them. They are caught by positioning the bat below them as they fall (meaning that you risk missing the ball if you go for them at the wrong time). The power-ups include lasers (which are mounted to each side of the ship and allow you to shoot out the blocks), a catching device (so as to be able to fire the ball off at a different angle every time you hit it) and one that slows the ball.... sorry, bolt.... down. Needless to say, the game inspired tonnes of clones, few of which added anything else.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Arkanoid (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Arkanoid (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Arkanoid (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Renegade III - The Final Chapter (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Renegade III: The Final Chapter</name>
		<desc>Renegade 3 was the third and last in the Imagine's series, based on the original coin-op by Taito. The hero's girlfriend has been beamed into the future, while the man himself has been sent back into prehistory. This sets the scene for a sideways scrolling arena combat game, where the player fights in various time periods. The settings varied from Egyptian and medieval, to a futuristic level. As such, gone are the attacks of street gangs from the first two iterations of the series, replaced by assailants such as knights in armor and robots. In each level you have six minutes to reach the finish, as this is all the time the time-travel portal is available for. There are many surface hazards to avoid, as well as multi-layered Green Beret-style areas. You can kick and punch at different heights, allowing you to deal with each of the diverse foes.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Renegade III - The Final Chapter (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Renegade III - The Final Chapter (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Renegade III - The Final Chapter (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine Software</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Block Dizzy (1991)(Banzai Programming).z80</path>
		<name>Block-Dizzy</name>
		<image>./mixart/Block Dizzy (1991)(Banzai Programming).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Block Dizzy (1991)(Banzai Programming).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Block Dizzy (1991)(Banzai Programming).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Your Sinclair</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gyroscope 2 (1987)(Melbourne House).tzx</path>
		<name>Gyroscope II</name>
		<image>./mixart/Gyroscope 2 (1987)(Melbourne House).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Gyroscope 2 (1987)(Melbourne House).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gyroscope 2 (1987)(Melbourne House).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MAC, SLA</developer>
		<publisher>Color Magic</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hacker (1985)(Activision).tzx</path>
		<name>Hacker</name>
		<desc>Hacker is an adventure/trading game based on what was then a unique idea. You're starting into the adventure as a real hacker would do, lacking information of what is to come, only driven by your ambition. Consequently, the game opens with a plain text screen, prompting you for the login password. To break into the system is the first puzzle you've got to solve.

Once in, you'll soon find out that you've accidentally stumbled upon a conspiracy of global impact. From then on, you'll maneuver a robotic drone around the globe through a tunnel system deep in the earth. In major cities, you may surface and talk to contact persons, who'll trade items for cash. When delivered to the correct city, you can exchange these items for a piece of evidence. If all evidence is collected, you're to inform the FBI. As if figuring out the correct routes and trades wasn't hard enough, frequent system malfunctions and security checks test your skill as well...
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Hacker (1985)(Activision).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Hacker (1985)(Activision).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hacker (1985)(Activision).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hacker 2 - The Doomsday Papers (1987)(Activision).tzx</path>
		<name>Hacker II: The Doomsday Papers</name>
		<desc>Hacker II: The Doomsday Papers is a real-time strategy game.
It is the sequel to Hacker 

Once again you hack into a computer system, just to end up saving the world. Hacker II: The Doomsday Papers opens with the console to the "Actisource" computer hotline system (a nice self-ironic pun - although nobody knows why a serious hacker might want to crack a help service for computer games...). However, your quiet little hack is soon disturbed: The government wants you for a secret mission. It, again,  involves a robot drone and you're the one at the remote control. Although this time, it's not the whole globe that's your playground, but a high security facility in Russia, where the plans for global domination are hidden.

In fact, all you've got to do is to guide your drone to the vault on a 2D map of the building. However, there are two major obstacles: Patrolling guards and security cameras. To avoid detection, you've got to trick the observers. By tapping the surveillance system you can see what cameras are currently active and which rooms they monitor. Your task is to bypass the video signal of the right cameras with a taped recording of an empty room, so that your drone is hidden from the view. You control four monitors, which you may freely switch to show the security monitor, the radar map, VCR output or one of the 38 cameras -- thus keeping an eye on guard movement while simultaneously controlling your drone and synchronizing recordings to cameras. Whew, sounds like a lot of work? It is.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Hacker 2 - The Doomsday Papers (1987)(Activision).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Hacker 2 - The Doomsday Papers (1987)(Activision).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hacker 2 - The Doomsday Papers (1987)(Activision).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Midnight Resistance (1990)(Ocean Software).tzx</path>
		<name>Midnight Resistance</name>
		<desc>The Midnight Resistance fighters are up against the awesome powers of mad scientist King Crimson and his Crimson Corps. Crimson has kidnapped your scientist grandfather and five more of your relatives, and aims to put his advanced plans to evil use.

Take control of a Resistance fighter in this scrolling shoot 'em up consisting of nine platform-based levels, each ending with a Boss to defeat. Your enemies appear on foot and in vehicles, and Crimson has also planted machine gun bays en route. 

Dead enemies release keys, which can be traded in at shop points for weapons. These weapons include machine guns and flamethrowers, for which ammunition must be bought - weapons are discarded when you have no suitable ammo. The control system is unusual - you can shoot in different directions and crawl along low ledges.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Midnight Resistance (1990)(Ocean Software).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Midnight Resistance (1990)(Ocean Software).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Midnight Resistance (1990)(Ocean Software).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Raiders II (1987)(Electric Dreams Software).tzx</path>
		<name>Star Raiders II</name>
		<desc>The Zylons have returned to attack the Celos IV star system. In this 3D shoot-'em-up, the player takes control of the Liberty Star and must warp to threatened planets to battle the Zylon Fly Fighters and Destroyers. The Zylon Squadrons can also be attacked while in transit, and friendly Space Stations allow refueling. To achieve victory, the Zylon Attack Bases on their own planets must be destroyed. The game ends if the Liberty Star runs out of fuel, or if all cities are destroyed by Zylons.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Raiders II (1987)(Electric Dreams Software).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Raiders II (1987)(Electric Dreams Software).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Raiders II (1987)(Electric Dreams Software).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Electric Dreams Software</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hijack (1986)(Electric Dreams Software).tzx</path>
		<name>Hijack</name>
		<desc>You are the head of the US Governments Hijack Division, and you are called into action when a group of terrorists hijack a vehicle. You have three potential ways to foil them  get enough money to bribe them, use political influence to over-rule them, or bring in military force. To achieve any of these tasks, you will need to work with the President, FBI and CIA agents, Military and Political Advisers, and other staff including the Secretary to keep you in contact with them. You have a time limit, which the President can attempt to extend with the hijackers if you request this.

You control your characters left-right movement through the buildings directly, including entering lifts to switch rooms, but moving the controller up or down moves a cursor along rows of icons at the top and bottom of the screen. The screen also has graphs to indicate your current political, military and financial situations.

Most important of these are the chances to interact with other staff members, provided they are in the room. There are at least two requests you can make to each of them  The President can be asked for more support, an FBI Agent can question staff to ensure that there is no inside information. CIA Agents can give information about the hijackers, with 3 levels of detail, the more advanced ones taking longer. Press releases must be issued to ensure good publicity (and thus keep the President on your side) and funds raised to help with a financial solution.

Your final target is to go to the scene of the hijack and negotiate with the terrorists. You can bring your key advisers with you, to increase the chance of a correct outcome.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Hijack (1986)(Electric Dreams Software).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Hijack (1986)(Electric Dreams Software).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hijack (1986)(Electric Dreams Software).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electric Dreams Software|Paradise Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electric Dreams Software</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scramble Spirits (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Scramble Spirits</name>
		<desc>Sega's take on the 1943 style of vertically scrolling shoot 'em ups was set in the future. Your fighter plane is aged and under-powered, yet you must face down large planes,  tanks and ground targets to achieve victory. Each level ends with a close-viewed section of particular intensity before finally facing a boss. Smart bombs are occasionally found lying around, and can destroy everything on the screen, although you can't use them on the bosses. A simultaneous 2-player mode is provided.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Scramble Spirits (Europe).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Scramble Spirits (Europe).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Scramble Spirits (Europe).mp4</video>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Grandslam Entertainments Ltd.</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turrican (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Turrican</name>
		<desc>Three-headed demon Morgul has been influencing people's dreams to create nightmares, but more recently these nightmares have become real. Only Turrican can save them in this fast paced side scrolling shoot-em up. It features 5 worlds and 13 levels of challenging gameplay.

Gameplay is conceptually simple: just jump, shoot and explore. However, this game puts a lot of emphasis on finding and using the 10 different weapons Turrican can collect.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Turrican (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Turrican (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Turrican (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rainbow Arts Software GmbH</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbow Arts Software GmbH</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./+Start Fuse.sh</path>
		<name>+Start Fuse</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T000000</releasedate>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3D Starfighter (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>3D Starfighter</name>
		<desc>3D Starfighter is a 3D shoot-'em-up where you must using a set of cross hairs shoot the rapidly approaching enemy craft, before they career into you and drain your shields. Use your lasers sparingly, for they also drain your energy.

The player is in the role a special agent whose mission is to deliver the Complete Hostile Alien Obliteration System (CHAOS) weapon to the population of a distant planet overrun by hostile aliens. Clear each space zone of hostiles before you encounter the ultimate goal to destroy the enemy Battlestar.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/3D Starfighter (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/3D Starfighter (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/3D Starfighter (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Oliver Twins, Mervin James, James Wilson, Jon Paul Eldridge</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./I, Ball (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>I,Ball</name>
		<desc>Terry Ball (terrible, geddit?) has kidnapped Lover Ball, No Ball, Eddy Ball and Glow Ball, and I,Ball must rescue them through 16 stages. The gameplay is shoot 'em up based, with the 16 levels scrolling vertically. They are full of hazards ranging from step-like sequences of blocks and metallic edges, to Terry Ball's unleashed devices including microwave ovens and crabs. The initial weapons is quite puny, but collecting discs allows upgrades to be obtained, including multi-directional fire and turbo boosts. You have four lives, but must complete each level within a time limit.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/I, Ball (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/I, Ball (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/I, Ball (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Timothy Closs, Kevin Wallace</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sentinel, The (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>The Sentinel</name>
		<image>./mixart/Sentinel, The (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sentinel, The (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sentinel, The (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Astroball (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Astroball</name>
		<image>./mixart/Astroball (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Astroball (Europe).mp4</video>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Revelation Software (Balor Knight, Chris Pile, Jade Lucas)</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Reality</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road Racer (Europe).tzx</path>
		<name>Ivan "Iron Man" Stewart's Super Off Road</name>
		<desc>Enter the world of off-road racing as 4 vehicles will face each other, on a series of tracks which are based around flipped and reversed versions of a core selection. Fame, glory and bikini clad women await your victories and the taste of dirt awaits if you fail. Let a computer car beat you and you lose one of your 3 credits.

Successful races bring more money, which can be used to soup up their machine. Boosts to top speed, grip and acceleration can be purchased, and your nitro boost must be kept topped up. If you are desperate for upgrades, you can buy into your spare credits

Only your off-road driving abilities will be enough to pull you to first place in these races. Play alone or with up to 3 other players (depending on the version)  in this conversion of a classic arcade game.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road Racer (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road Racer (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road Racer (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Leland Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Games</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
