<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>PSP</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game id="78511" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Beowulf - The Game.cso</path>
		<name>Beowulf : The Game</name>
		<desc>Gamers live the life of Beowulf, the legendary Norse warrior with the strength of 30 men who is torn between the nobility and brutality within him. Arrogant, self-serving and lustful for gold and glory, Beowulf journeys to Denmark to destroy a bloodthirsty beast wreaking havoc on a frigid land. But evil persists, and Beowulf succumbs to its lure of even greater fame, quietly maneuvering to claim the Danish throne. As King, Beowulf must face the consequences of ambition, even as war descends on the realm.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Virtuos</developer>
		<publisher>Ubi Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<image>./mixart/Beowulf - The Game.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Beowulf - The Game.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Beowulf - The Game.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28155" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./BlazBlue Continuum Shift II (USA).cso</path>
		<name>BlazBlue : Continuum Shift II</name>
		<desc>BlazBlue: Continuum Shift II features the full 18 character cast of the original BlazBlue: Continuum Shift, including the three DLC characters, Makoto, Valkenhayn, and Platinum. Furthermore, BlazBlue: Continuum Shift II also features the new system mechanics and game balance revisions introduced by the original Arcade version and system version 1.03. With all of these new features, BlazBlue: Continuum Shift II is a brand new fighting game experience sure to meet the expectations of fans everywhere.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20110331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arc System Works</developer>
		<publisher>Arc System Works</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<image>./mixart/BlazBlue Continuum Shift II (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/BlazBlue Continuum Shift II (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/BlazBlue Continuum Shift II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28372" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crazy Taxi - Fare Wars (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Crazy Taxi : Fare Wars</name>
		<desc>Crazy Taxi: Fare Wars (known as: Crazy Taxi: Double Punch in Japan), is a PSP game, which is a port of both Crazy Taxi and Crazy Taxi 2. There is also a multiplayer aspect which was not available in the games' predecessors, where players compete against one another for customers and fare money. The game was developed by newly created Sniper Studios.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20070612T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sniper</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<image>./mixart/Crazy Taxi - Fare Wars (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Crazy Taxi - Fare Wars (USA).png</marquee>
	</game>
	<game id="28404" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Crush.cso</path>
		<name>Crush</name>
		<desc>Danny is troubled with insomnia.  Desperate for sleep and unable to get it, he finds himself a test subject in the mad Dr. Reubens' crowning achievement, C.R.U.S.H. (or Cognitive Regression Utilizing pSychiatric Heuristics, if you prefer).  C.R.U.S.H. puts the subject under hypnosis and allows them to explore their psyche and confront their own deep, dark secrets.  Crush is a platforming game with puzzle elements.  Initially, it looks like a third person platformer, but you'll soon discover the game's hook - as Danny, you can "crush" the landscape based on the camera direction, giving you a new perspective on a previously impassable situation.  Huge gaps become mere footsteps wide, or may even disappear.  Tall buildings can be squashed flat, allowing you to walk over previously impossible terrain.  By rotating the camera with the D-Pad, you can choose to crush the level sideways, similar to a 2D platformer like Super Mario Bros., or top-down, somewhat like Bomberman.  However, there are, of course, restrictions.  Not all blocks can be crossed when crushed.  In addition to this, some blocks that you can stand on in 3D simply don't exist in 2D.  And then there's creatures lurking based on Danny's fears: giant cockroaches roam around some levels, and need to be squashed before Danny can get past them.  Some blocks contain nightmarish limbs that swipe at Danny when he gets too close.  And some blocks (representing Danny's childhood fear of building blocks) even come to life and patrol the 3D levels.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20070525T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zoë Mode</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Crush.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Crush.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Crush.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="144116" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Cube.cso</path>
		<name>Cube</name>
		<desc>Cube is a puzzle game with action elements. The game is set in a cubic world with different stages and challenges. Players control a cube through tracks that act like 3D platforms and mazes. There are 135 levels based on nine themes in total. The different themes (called zones in the game) come with their own contraptions and a specific colour. Dangers include bombs, creatures, sinking surfaces, rotating blocks, blocks that blow the cube backwards and more. Sometimes these also need to be manipulated to create new paths (e.g. moving blocks and then luring a bomb to blow it up).</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<image>./mixart/Cube.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cube.png</marquee>
	</game>
	<game id="28214" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dead Head Fred.cso</path>
		<name>Dead Head Fred</name>
		<desc>Dead Head Fred is an action game that tells a "classic tale of murder, corruption, revenge and... interchangeable heads". The main character is Fred Neuman. He's a private detective in the town of Hope Falls. During his investigations, he gets too involved with the dealings of the mob, so he's lured into a trap and beheaded. Shortly after his murder, he's found by Dr. Friedrich Steiner, who resurrects his body, and places his brain and eyes into a jar. From here begins the journey of Fred for revenge.  Due to the experiment, Fred has the ability to take the heads of enemies (a total of 9 are available), each giving him a special upgradeable power, like smashing ability, ability to fire projectiles or flight.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20071123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>D3 Publisher</developer>
		<publisher>Vicious Cycle</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Dead Head Fred.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dead Head Fred.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dead Head Fred.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28475" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Death Jr II - Root of Evil.cso</path>
		<name>Death Jr.</name>
		<desc>Take on the role of the Grim Reapers teenage son Death Jr. after he unleashes an unspeakable horror from a box that Pandora herself couldn't open in a school field trip at the museum.  Death Jr. is a 3-D platform game in which you control Death Jr. a.k.a. DJ in an attempt to find his friends that have been taken by the evil necromancer Moloch. DJ's friend souls appear as puzzle pieces throughout the game in which you must find to bring them back.  Warp through 17 levels fighting demons and fiends using DJ's famed scythe along with other weapons like a shotgun, electric gun and even C4 Hamsters. Use DJ's scythe to not only maim and kill but to reach heights not accessible by jumping. Upgrade weapons and learn new moves (scythe combos) by collecting widgets scattered throughout the levels. The ability to destroy the environment is an advantage to DJ as the more successful hits with his scythe be it animate or inanimate his combo meter will rise allowing DJ's friend Pandora to assist in the fight.  Death Jr.'s camera is a free roaming camera that follows DJ around with the ability to snap to the position DJ is looking at the press of a button. You can also free look with the press of a button and lock on to enemies and strafe while shooting with a gun. At the end of each level you receive a report card that tells you your number of kills, how much destruction you caused, the total number of combo points, special items discovered and your final grade.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Backbone Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Death Jr II - Root of Evil.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Death Jr II - Root of Evil.png</marquee>
	</game>
	<game id="28196" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dungeon Explorer - Warrior Of The Ancient Arts.cso</path>
		<name>Dungeon Explorer - Warriors of Ancient Arts</name>
		<desc>Dungeon Explorer sur PSP est un hack'n slash dans lequel le joueur peut incarner 3 races différentes et choisir parmi 6 classes de personnages. Le jeu propose un mode multijoueur en local qui permet à 2 ou 3 joueurs de coopérer pour espérer remporter la victoire.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20080202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<image>./mixart/Dungeon Explorer - Warrior Of The Ancient Arts.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dungeon Explorer - Warrior Of The Ancient Arts.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dungeon Explorer - Warrior Of The Ancient Arts.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28697" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dungeon Maker - Hunting Ground.cso</path>
		<name>Dungeon Maker : Hunting Ground</name>
		<desc>Create your own dungeon, with simple or complex design. Lure monster and endanger the townspeople life into your new built dungeon. Thereafter, trick the townspeople into believing you are the hero and slay the monster, and be hailed as the Grand Architect in this hack-and-slash dungeon crawler.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20070702T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Global A Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Xseed Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Dungeon Maker - Hunting Ground.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dungeon Maker - Hunting Ground.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dungeon Maker - Hunting Ground.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28029" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dungeon Seige II - Throne of Agony.cso</path>
		<name>Dungeon Siege : Throne of Agony</name>
		<desc>Dungeon Siege : Throne Of Agony est un jeu de rôle et d'action sur PSP. Commencez par créer votre personnage, parmi les trois classes différentes : un guerrier, un mage et une sorte de voleur pouvant attaquer avec deux armes. Choisissez également un compagnon de route et partez défier les nombreux ennemis pour monter en niveau.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SuperVillain Studios</developer>
		<publisher>2K Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Dungeon Seige II - Throne of Agony.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dungeon Seige II - Throne of Agony.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dungeon Seige II - Throne of Agony.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28172" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dungeons and Dragons Tactics.cso</path>
		<name>Dungeons and Dragons : Tactics</name>
		<desc>Faithfully utilizing the Dungeons &amp; Dragons 3.5 rule-set, Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Tactics allows players to take a party of six adventurers into a wide variety of dangerous environments to experience deep and exciting turn-based action. All of the core races and classes are available to the player, including two Psionic classes, the Psion and the Psychic Warrior. Play with your friends wirelessly in both cooperative and adversarial game modes.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20070914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kuju Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/Dungeons and Dragons Tactics.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dungeons and Dragons Tactics.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Dungeons and Dragons Tactics.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28449" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Echochrome.cso</path>
		<name>Echochrome</name>
		<desc>echochrome is a puzzle game with a design inspired by the works of M.C. Escher. The gameplay is based around optical illusions, as the player must utilize five simple laws of perspective in order to join walkways, hide dangers and create path in order to reach the "echoes", checkpoints in the game. This implies that different actions are possible based on the camera perspective, which is changed when the player rotates the camera.  For the PSP there are two different versions. The UMD game offers 105 levels with three game modes for each: Solo mode (walk alone), Pair mode (control a white and black mannequin - when they meet each other they merge into a grey one and the puzzle is solved) and Others (solo mode with the additional of black enemies). The PlayStation store version is called echochrome Micro and only offers 56 levels with the three game modes.  All versions have a built-in editor. On the PS3 levels can be easily exchanged through the PlayStation Network. The system will also automatically download ten custom puzzles, rated highly by other users, to a maximum of 300. When the maximum amount has been reached, older ones are replaced.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20080704T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game-Simulation</genre>
		<image>./mixart/Echochrome.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Echochrome.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Echochrome.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28672" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Every Extend Extra.cso</path>
		<name>Every Extend Extra</name>
		<desc>Every Extend Extra is a remake of the popular freeware game Every Extend and in all main aspects of gameplay it sticks to its independent roots. The main difference between E3 and the original game is E3's music adaptation, just like the other Tetsuya Mizuguchi's synesthesia titles (Lumines and Rez). E3's main arcade mode allows the player to advance through different stages, each of them featuring different background, enemy designs, music, bosses and a varying pace of play.  As in the original game you too are unable to shoot. The only way of defense is to detonate your "ship" in the vicinity of the enemy. Enemies appear in randomized patterns, and the main goal is to detonate at the right moment and position, to set up a chain reaction of explosions and earning a combo bonus. Blowing oneself up takes away from your overall stock of lives, with a new life being issued at specific amounts of points.  The original game has been included with the PSP version as well.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Q Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Buena Vista Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game-Action</genre>
		<image>./mixart/Every Extend Extra.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Every Extend Extra.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Every Extend Extra.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28259" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Exit.cso</path>
		<name>Exit</name>
		<desc>Exit places you in the role of Mr. ESC, professional escape artist extraordinaire.As Mr. ESC, your job is to guide scores of people from precarious situations. In the midst of situations such as a burning apartment, you will guide and direct those people in an effort to take each and every person in each level out of harm's way. One hundred levels are available in the main quest, with an additional one hundred becoming available through wi-fi downloads.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game-Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Exit.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Exit.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Exit.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28262" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Fat Princess - Fistful of Cake (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Fat Princess : Fistful of Cake</name>
		<desc>Fast-paced and strategic, Fat Princess: Fistful of Cake pits two hordes of players against each other in a comic medieval battle on the PSP. The player's goal is to rescue a beloved princess from the enemy castle. There is a catch, though; the adversary has been feeding her magical cake to make her heavier to carry. Therefore, it will take much of the army working together to carry her across the battlefield. Team balance and strategy is crucial in Fat Princess: Fistful of Cake because players can switch between five different character classes, literally, at the drop of a hat. The name of the game is cooperation, whether it is flinging another player over the enemy's walls with a teeterboard, healing him while he charges into battle, or adding muscle to carry the hearty princess to safety. The comical, quirky, and loveable cast of characters in Fat Princess: Fistful of Cake has been developed specifically for optimization on the PSP. Now players can have their cake and take it on the go, too.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20090101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<image>./mixart/Fat Princess - Fistful of Cake (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fat Princess - Fistful of Cake (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Fat Princess - Fistful of Cake (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28486" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Free Runing.cso</path>
		<name>Free Running</name>
		<desc>Free Running is a third-person open-environment arcade game, based around the sport of Parkour.  Set across multiple high and low rise urban environments, Parkour participants (known as traceurs) navigate around and over various obstacles using only the natural abilities of the human body. By stringing together spectacular gymnastic style moves, the player builds up 'flow', and is awarded points according to their agility and grace.  In the single player story mode, the players creates a novice traceur, who is mentored by Parkour athletes from Urban Freeflow, and by the Parkour guru Sebastian Foucan.  In addition, there are numerous single and multiplayer challenge modes - races, collection events, style based challenges, timed events and more.  Successful completion of challenges unlocks new levels, videos, clothing, footwear and music tracks.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20070329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reef Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Rebellion</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Free Runing.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Free Runing.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Free Runing.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28119" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Gladiator Begins (EUR).cso</path>
		<name>Gladiator Begins</name>
		<desc>A sequel to Colosseum: Road to Freedom. You once again begin your journey as a gladiator. Your best chance at freedom is to earn enough money in the arena to purchase your liberty from the shackles of servitude.    The game features real-time combat against one or multiple opponents and allies, a wide variety of equipment to buy, sell or modify as well as several different fighting styles and a branching storyline with multiple endings.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20110101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Goshow</developer>
		<publisher>Acquire</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Gladiator Begins (EUR).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gladiator Begins (EUR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Gladiator Begins (EUR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28553" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Grip Shift.cso</path>
		<name>Gripshift</name>
		<desc>Gripshift is a driving game with a twist. It combines racing with puzzles and even some platform action.   The game is built around a tour mode where the player must complete the stages one by one. Clear these stages by driving fast to the finish or try to top the times required to obtain bronze, silver, and gold medals. There are also stars to collect and a hidden item on every stage to discover. All of the levels are afloat in the air, so if the player happens to drift off the course, the car drops into nothingness.  There are many multiplayer modes, including bonus games such as soccer, ice hockey and a Snake game played with cars. In the track editor, players can construct their own gravity-defying tracks and share them through a wireless connection.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sidhe Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<image>./mixart/Grip Shift.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grip Shift.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Grip Shift.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28102" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Guilty Gear Judgement (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Guilty Gear Judgment</name>
		<desc>Guilty Gear Judgment is a sidescrolling beat-'em-up. Which also comes bundled with the Guilty Gear X2 #Reload fighting game. Japanese version comes with Guilty Gear XX Slash instead of #Reload.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arc System Works</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up-Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Guilty Gear Judgement (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Guilty Gear Judgement (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Guilty Gear Judgement (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28969" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Hot Wheels Ultimate Racing.cso</path>
		<name>Hot Wheels Ultimate Racing</name>
		<desc>Ultimate Racing is the first game in the series of Hot Wheels licensees to appear on the PSP platform. Just like the other games, it is a straightforward racing game with a focus on arcade gameplay. The game offers three game modes:  Ultimate Challenge: win races to unlock new cars, tracks, challenges and performance upgrades.    Arcade Mode: quick play based on the unlocked content from the Ultimate Challenge mode.    Multiplayer Mode: quick races or checkpoint-based races for up to four players  In Ultimate Challenge, there are six main stages to choose from, with eleven tracks and twenty licensed cars in total. The game starts from a central warehouse where all unlocked cars are stored. These can be upgraded or customized in the garage. Next to the performance upgrades, players can tweak the colors of the body, glass, neon, wheels, and change the wheels and decals.    The Arcade Mode is further divided into different challenges: Quick Race, Survival Mode (complete a series of increasingly difficult races and avoid being kicked out), Collector (checkpoint-based races) and Time Trial.    Next to regular racing controls such as brakes and acceleration, players can also use NOS (boost) and Slow Motion (slow down time during difficult sections). The use is limited as it depletes a reserve. It can be refilled by passing by obstacles without hitting them or completing tricky jumps. Tracks, with themes such as Volcano, Jungle or Death Valley, are generally filled with obstacles, moving objects or animals. The focus is entirely on racing, there are no weapons or other offensive means and the cars can only be slowed down, unable to sustain damage.    There are three different camera settings and ghost cars are supported during time trials.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20070727T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raylight Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Zoo Digital</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
		<image>./mixart/Hot Wheels Ultimate Racing.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hot Wheels Ultimate Racing.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Hot Wheels Ultimate Racing.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28297" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Infected.cso</path>
		<name>Infected</name>
		<desc>Infected is a fast-paced third person comedy zombie shooter.  The focus is on a humorous plot and combo-based zombie killing.  It's Christmas time in New York and Zombies have come to ruin the festivities.  As New York Cop Agent Stevens, you find out that not only are you immune to the zombie virus, but your blood is actually so powerful, it will make a zombie explode.  The main focus of the gameplay is shooting holes in the zombies until they are weak enough for you to fire a vial of your own blood into them, causing an explosion.  Weaken enough zombies, fire a blood vial into one, and watch the chain reaction as exploding zombies send your anti-zombie blood onto other zombies.  The game was one of the first online PSP games, and featured a mode where defeating an opponent would give them your virus, and force their avatar online to look like your avatar.  If they in turn defeated someone, your virus would be passed onto them as well.  At any time you could look at a world map to see where on earth your strain of virus had travelled.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20061110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Majesco</developer>
		<publisher>Planet Moon</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<image>./mixart/Infected.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Infected.png</marquee>
	</game>
	<game id="27964" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Killzone Liberation.cso</path>
		<name>Killzone : Liberation</name>
		<desc>In Killzone: Liberation, two months after the events of "Killzone," (PS2) most of southern Vekta is still under Helghast control. The rules of war have been cast aside with the Helghast General, Metrac, employing brutal measures in order to seize the initiative and strengthen his position further. Returning as Templar, players will be sent on a mission to undertake a covert operation to save hostages captured by Metrac, while ISA troops continue the fight for liberty. Featuring an intelligent third person camera system, Killzone: Liberation allows players a more tactical surveillance viewpoint to view their action and read the enemy's behavior during gameplay. Set in an intense postmodern war reminiscent of the previous PS2 title, Killzone: Liberation features the unique graphical style to showcase pure grit and realism. During gameplay, players will have access to variety of weapons that are unique and innovative, inspired by modern military equipment.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20061108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Guerrilla</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2-6</players>
		<image>./mixart/Killzone Liberation.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Killzone Liberation.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Killzone Liberation.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28125" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Loco Roco (USA).cso</path>
		<name>LocoRoco</name>
		<desc>LocoRoco is an innovative 2D platform/action game available exclusively for the PSP. Featuring unique controls utilizing the "L" and "R" shoulder buttons, players are tasked with controlling via "tilting or bumping" the landscape of the LocoRoco in order to help them navigate through the level and keep them out of harm's way. With more than 40 stages, players control and guide the LocoRoco through vibrant, thriving and lush worlds filled with slippery slopes, swing ropes , and more. Featuring six different types of LocoRoco that include their own voices and actions, players will be enchanted by captivating music that communicates the joyous world of these LocoRoco. In addition, LocoRoco features the rewarding LocoHouse, three mini-games , and wireless features. The peaceful world of the LocoRoco are under attack by the not-so-nice Moja Corps. These evil outer space creatures want nothing but to capture the blissful LocoRoco and take them from their land of blowing flowers, lively creatures and pastel scenery. As the planet where the LocoRoco inhabit, players must tilt, roll and bounce the LocoRoco to safety.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game-Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Loco Roco (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Loco Roco (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Loco Roco (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28203" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lumines.cso</path>
		<name>Lumines</name>
		<desc>Bust blocks, solve puzzles, and play wirelessly with your friends. In Lumines, your objective is to clear the screen by connecting blocks of like colors together. A timeline wipes away your solid-color creations, which can also initiate combos and link moves. See if you have what it takes to advance through 24 levels, each with its own musical theme and sound effects. Lumines features four gameplay modes, including single-player and multiplayer.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Lumines.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Lumines.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lumines.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28153" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Metal Gear Acid (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Metal Gear Ac!d</name>
		<desc>The Metal Gear series comes to the PSP offering a new gameplay system and storyline. In Metal Gear Acid, you'll take on the role of Solid Snake, a top-secret agent who's an expert at infiltration. It's up to you to make calculated decisions to plan out your strategy and accomplish missions in a turn-based style of game. Strategic battle cards give you different abilities and stealth tactics that help you achieve mission objectives. Experience a deeper kind of tactical espionage in the palm of your hand.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Playing cards</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Metal Gear Acid (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Metal Gear Acid (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Metal Gear Acid (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28358" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Micro Machines V4.cso</path>
		<name>Micro Machines V4</name>
		<desc>Mixing miniature mayhem with maximum multiplayer racing, Micro Machines v4 features knockabout, breakneck racing in the fastest scale miniatures, complete with explosive weapon power-ups. Letting you loose with hundreds of vehicles, each with distinctive performance abilities, you'll be racing your inch-long miniature motors on the wildest tracks where everyday household objects appear immense in size and can become lethal hazards.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20060629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Supersonic Software</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/Micro Machines V4.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Micro Machines V4.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Micro Machines V4.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="27974" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./MX vs ATV Reflex.cso</path>
		<name>MX vs. ATV Reflex</name>
		<desc>MX vs. ATV Reflex is an off-road racing video game developed by Rainbow Studios and published by THQ. It is the third game in the MX vs. ATV series.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20100203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rainbow Studios</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<image>./mixart/MX vs ATV Reflex.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/MX vs ATV Reflex.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/MX vs ATV Reflex.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28759" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./PAC-MAN Championship Edition (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Pac-man Championship Edition</name>
		<desc>Pac-Man Championship Edition is similar in basic gameplay to the original 1980 Pac-Man: players have to eat dots, while avoiding the four ghosts that roam around the maze. Championship Edition, however, also brings many gameplay differences.    The game was designed by the creator of the classic original 1980 arcade game Pac-Man, and it was Iwatani's final game before his retirement.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Various</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/PAC-MAN Championship Edition (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/PAC-MAN Championship Edition (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/PAC-MAN Championship Edition (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28654" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Platypus (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Platypus</name>
		<desc>The big city of Collosatropolis has reached the limits of its expansion. The Collostropolan leaders have decided to solve the problem by invading the neighboring country of Mungola. Since Mungolans are simple, earthy types they don’t expect much of a struggle. Mungola’s defense force consists only of a single squadron of fighter planes – the F-27 Platypus.  Platypus is a side-scrolling shooter, where you use your little space craft to blast the enemy ships. Shooting some formations gives the player weapon upgrades for twenty seconds. All models in the game were designed in clay, photographed and then digitally coloured. There is 20 levels in four different worlds each with their own themes and enemies.  The PSP version includes minor changes. It adds worlds, ships, and enemies not in the original game, constructed from existing graphics, with new movement patterns. The weapon balancing and bonus scoring system have been changed. Enhancements include a save system, a new Survival mode and Wi-Fi multiplayer action for 2 players.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20080417T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mumbo Jumbo</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Platypus (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Platypus (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Platypus (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28275" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Power Stone Collection.cso</path>
		<name>Power Stone Collection</name>
		<desc>This is a compilation of enhanced versions of Power Stone and Power Stone 2. This collection includes bonuses like the Bomber Battle minigame, visual layout fixes, new weapons, extra characters in Power Stone 1, and new unlockables. Multiplayer is available for 2 players (PS1) or four players (PS2). Using a single UMD, you can send the trial version of Power Stone 2 for your friends to play.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20061020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Compilation-Action</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/Power Stone Collection.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Power Stone Collection.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Power Stone Collection.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="142882" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Prince of Persia - The Forgotten Sands (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Prince Of Persia : The Forgotten Sands</name>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20100520T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Prince of Persia - The Forgotten Sands (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Prince of Persia - The Forgotten Sands (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Prince of Persia - The Forgotten Sands (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28304" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Prinny Can I Really Be The Hero (EUR).cso</path>
		<name>Prinny : Can I Really Be the Hero</name>
		<desc>In Prinny: Can I Really Be The Hero? players are treated to a single player spin-off from the popular role-playing universe of Disgaea. Here players step into the unlucky shoes of a penguin called a Prinny and 999 of his comrades as you slash your way through various Netherworld areas in side-scrolling service to the Demon Lord Etna. Although the mission that you are saddled with, finding ingredients for the ultimate desert, is ridiculously comic, the action you face is not, so you're given 1,000 lives to work with and you can use everything you find on the battlefield to help you survive and succeed.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20090217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nippon Ichi Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nippon Ichi Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Prinny Can I Really Be The Hero (EUR).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Prinny Can I Really Be The Hero (EUR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Prinny Can I Really Be The Hero (EUR).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28438" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Rengoku II - The Stairway to HEAVEN.cso</path>
		<name>Rengoku II : The Stairway to H.E.A.V.E.N.</name>
		<desc>The first Rengoku was a surprise hit for many PSPÂ® gamers. Featuring a compelling story about a cyborg yearning to escape its life of never ending battle, Rengoku provided a new and exciting world to battle through on the PSPÂ®.     Now gamers will return to the world of Rengoku as they battle their way through the towering structure of Purgatory and the Seven Deadly Sins! Rengoku 2 builds upon the first game with improved level design for more strategy, smoother control, exciting new fighting mechanics that allow for attack combos, and deeper customization. With network support for up to four players via AD HOC, more levels, an explosive soundtrack by Hong Kong composer, Chan Kwong Wing, and character designs by legendary manga artist, Jun Suemi, Rengoku 2 is a deep and more challenging action experience.  -- Summary from Gamefaqs.com</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20061201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/Rengoku II - The Stairway to HEAVEN.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rengoku II - The Stairway to HEAVEN.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Rengoku II - The Stairway to HEAVEN.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28273" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Shinobido (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Shinobido : Les Légendes du Ninja</name>
		<desc>Gamuran has been defeated. By laying this elite warrior to rest, the Asuka Ninja have prevented war in Utakata. However, the threat of conflict is far from over. As the population of Utakata work night and day to rebuild their hometown, something in the shadow watches, ready to bring a new wave of terror to the fallen province. Team up for co-op missions of stealth and action in Shinobido: Tales of the Ninja, or take on your friends in Wireless battles via ad-hoc multiplayer combat.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20061026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Spike</developer>
		<publisher>Acquire</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Shinobido (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Shinobido (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Shinobido (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28109" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./SSX on Tour (USA).cso</path>
		<name>SSX : On Tour</name>
		<desc>Create your skier or snowboarder and get on the slopes in this version of the SSX franchise. With a different front end interface to previous versions, which looks like a mix between MTV and a doodle book, you select the challenge you want to take part in rather than boarding your way to the event as previous versions.  With improved controls making "Monster Jumps" (Uber Tricks) easier to perform, everyone can look like a professional without learning button combos. As before, if you perform the same trick over and over, you won't get the points to take your skier/snowboarder from a novice to what they have a labeled "black-diamond-dominating rockstar".  The game promises big jumps, fast pace and lots of coloured, detailed slopes.  The GameCube version delivers Mario, Luigi and Peaches on the slopes as special characters. Each has their own moves and is accompanied by Mario-style music.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports BIG</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/SSX on Tour (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/SSX on Tour (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/SSX on Tour (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28002" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Street Fighter Alpha 3 MAX (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha 3 Max</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter Alpha 3 MAX is a conversion of the 2D arcade fighter Street Fighter Alpha 3. Featuring a roster of 37 characters, including 3 (Maki, Yun, Eagle) never seen outside of the GBA version, and 1 brand-new character (Ingrid) to the game, all with their own storyline, you can spend a very long time learning the intricacies of all the fighters.  It includes all the novelties introduced in the Alpha series, including finite defenses, the ability to recover and isms to customize special attacks. To help avoid the typical repetitiveness of the game, all the modes available in the previous home versions of Alpha 3, such as Arcade Mode, Training Mode, Edit Mode, World Tour, Dramatic Battle and Survival modes are all available in this version, along with the brand-new 100-man kumite (survival) and tag-team battle modes.  The PSP version also has network games (Ad-Hoc only) for up to 8 players, with four additional modes: VS Mode, Team Mode, Variable Battle (take three players into battle of which you control two, and the computer one), and the Dramatic Battle with multiple fighters going at it simultaneously.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Action</genre>
		<players>8</players>
		<image>./mixart/Street Fighter Alpha 3 MAX (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Street Fighter Alpha 3 MAX (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Street Fighter Alpha 3 MAX (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28939" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./TNT Racers.cso</path>
		<name>Tnt Racers</name>
		<desc>TNT Racers is a racing video game for the Wii U, Wii, PlayStation 3, PlayStation Portable, and Xbox 360. The game was released on the consoles as downloadable games. The game was developed by dtp entertainment for the WiiWare and PSP games, while Keen Games developed the PS3 and Xbox Live Arcade versions. The game was released on December 1, 2010 for the PS3, February 9, 2011 for the Xbox 360, and March 31 for the Wii and PSP.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Keen Games</developer>
		<publisher>DTP Young Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<image>./mixart/TNT Racers.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/TNT Racers.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/TNT Racers.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="29154" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Traxxpad.cso</path>
		<name>Traxxpad</name>
		<desc>Traxxpad is a music application for Sony's PlayStation Portable developed by Definitive Studios and published by Eidos Interactive. It was released June 26, 2007. Traxxpad is a portable music studio featuring a sequencer, drum machine, and keyboard for the creation of music tracks. It features a library of over 1000 sound samples for use, and allows users to record their own samples using a microphone for the PSP.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20070626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Definitive Studios, LLC</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance-Various</genre>
		<image>./mixart/Traxxpad.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Traxxpad.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Traxxpad.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28419" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Tron Evolution (EUR).cso</path>
		<name>TRON : Evolution</name>
		<desc>Tron: Evolution is a third-person action-adventure, tie-in video game for the film Tron: Legacy by Propaganda Games, published by Disney Interactive. It was officially announced at the Spike Video Game Awards and was released for the Microsoft Windows, PlayStation 3, PlayStation Portable and Xbox 360 platforms on November 26, 2010 in Europe and December 7, 2010 in North America.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20110203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SuperVillain Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Disney</publisher>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/Tron Evolution (EUR).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tron Evolution (EUR).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/TRON - Evolution (USA) (PSN).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="103359" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Work Time Fun.cso</path>
		<name>WTF : Work Time Fun</name>
		<desc>Created specifically for the PSP system, WTF is a crazy collection of fun and addictive mini-games that drive the player to perform sometimes trivial, sometimes mind-bending, but always fun jobs in pursuit of the almighty dollar. The latest in a long line of unique Japanese games that have gained popularity in the United States, WTF delivers gamers compelling, bite-sized morsels of frenzied arcade-style action unlike anything ever seen on the PSP system.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20061017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCEJ</developer>
		<publisher>D3Publisher</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Work Time Fun.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Work Time Fun.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Work Time Fun.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Family Guy (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Family Guy</name>
		<desc>This game is based on the animated television series Family Guy. It was also released for the PlayStation 2 and the original Xbox.    The game is split into 22 levels for the three playable characters: Peter, Stewie or Brian. Peter and Stewie have eight levels, while Brian has six. Each character has his own unique style of play.    A key feature of the game are mini-games done in the same style as the cutaway gags that the show is famous for, usually lasting less than 10 seconds. The mini-games often repeat cutaway gags from the shows, such as Peter inexplicably burning his hand in a waffle iron. Successfully completing the mini-game offers a bonus: Brian becomes invisible for a short period, while Peter and Stewie receive power-ups for their respective abilities.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Family Guy (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Family Guy (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Family Guy (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T000000</releasedate>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghost in the Shell (JAP).cso</path>
		<name>Ghost in the Shell : Stand Alone Complex</name>
		<desc>Based on the series of the same name, Ghost in the Shell: Stand Alone Complex is a fast-action third-person shooter for up to four players. As "Major" Motoko Kusanagi, Batou, and Tachikoma, you can engage enemies in both multiplayer combat and single-player missions. In single-player mode, your missions involve hacking into machines and computers, controlling your enemies' minds from a distance, and using a variety of weapons to eliminate your enemies. Complete the Story mode to unlock more playable characters, costumes, and additional weapons.    The game serves as a sequel to the PS2 game of the same name.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ghost in the Shell (JAP).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ghost in the Shell (JAP).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Ghost in the Shell (JAP).mp4</video>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>G-Artists</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King Of Clubs.cso</path>
		<name>King of Clubs</name>
		<desc>King of Clubs is an innovative action-puzzle game, combining the challenge of the traditional ball-rolling puzzler with the classic tacky seaside pastime of mini-golf. As an evolution of the ball-rolling puzzle genre, each level has multiple solutions, and as further equipment is unlocked, new paths through each hole become viable. Building on the great tradition of sorry-looking mini-golf courses, the game is set in a dilapidated theme-park which takes decaying kitsch to new extremes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/King Of Clubs.png</image>
		<video>./snap/King Of Clubs.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/King Of Clubs.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080516T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oxygen</developer>
		<publisher>Oxygen</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Michael Jackson - The Experience (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Michael Jackson : The Experience</name>
		<desc>Michael Jackson: The Experience is a rhythm game that has players virtually dancing along with the King of Pop, on more than a dozen of his biggest hits. Players make their character dance by tapping the PSP directional buttons in time with the music, following on-screen cues. Routines are modeled after the artist's choreography, as seen in famous music videos and live performances, using a rotoscope-style animation technique to reproduce the actual poses and postures. As players master the routine for each song, it becomes unlocked in a jukebox mode that can be accessed at any time. The game has three difficulty settings, to challenge fans of all skill levels.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Michael Jackson - The Experience (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Michael Jackson - The Experience (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Michael Jackson - The Experience (USA).mp4</video>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20101125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Music and Dance-Various</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultimate Board Game Collection (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Ultimate Board Game Collection</name>
		<desc>Ultimate Board Game Collection includes a large group of tabletop and board games, some classic and some unique. It contains 24 games in all, arranged into categories, and supports up to 6 players:  All-Time Favorites: Backgammon, Checkers, Chess, Chinese Checkers, Reversi   Words &amp; Numbers: Anagrams, Dice, Kakuro, Sudoku, Word Cubes Puzzle Games: Concentration, Enigma, Jigsaws, Mahjong Family Favorites: 3-D Tic-Tac-Toe, Naval Battle, Parcheesi, Quattro, Snakes and Ladders Strategy Games: Dominoes, Go, Mancala, Gomoku, Shogi  This PSP version has more games than the Playstation 2 or Wii versions, and has some additional features. It allows players to play their own MP3 audio tracks off of a memory stick, and two of the games, Jigsaws and Concentration, have the option to upload custom images to jazz up the atmosphere. Also included are 27 unlockable trophies as goals to work for. The in-game tutorial provides help for any unfamiliar games.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ultimate Board Game Collection (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ultimate Board Game Collection (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ultimate Board Game Collection (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mere Mortals</developer>
		<publisher>Valcon Games LLC</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gun - Showdown.cso</path>
		<name>GUN Showdown</name>
		<desc>GUN Showdown puts players in the role of Colton White, a vengeful gunslinger making his way through the untamed West of the late-1800s where the lines between good and evil are blurred and greed, lust and brutality were a way of life. The game features all of the action contained in the console versions, as well as all-new side missions, quick-play modes, multiplayer modes and gameplay features that are unique to the PSP system.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Gun - Showdown.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Gun - Showdown.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gun - Showdown.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20061027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mercury Meltdown.cso</path>
		<name>Mercury Meltdown</name>
		<desc>Mercury Meltdown is the sequel to Archer Maclean's Mercury, a puzzle game where your job is to guide a blob of mercury, or several blobs, along various mazes, by tilting the game world, while hazard try to zap, attract, repulse, eat, or blow you up.  Mercury Meltdown features a new vibrant visual style, a lot of completely new stages, a free-look camera, ghost mercuries and replays for your best times that can be saved, and much more. The game's original realistic graphics have been turned into a more cartoon style. The mercury now has a black line around the outside of it.  The main change in the game is the ability to change the mercury into 3 more states. Besides normal state now you can turn the mercury into the "Fast" or "Slow" using a heater and a cooler, and using a solidifier you can make it unto "Solid" state, a round, non-breakable ball. The mercury can still be split using a splitter, needed to solve certain puzzles.  Unlike the original Mercury, the game is split into themed "Labs"  rather than “Worlds”. There are 10 Labs, with 16 initial stages: Astro, Bio, Chemical, Electro, Geo, Atom, Aero, Hydro, Micro, V.R. (Virtual Reality). The PS2 version adds two more: Chrono and Cryo, as well as twin analog control, support for the rumble feature, improved graphics and all the levels from the original Archer Maclean's Mercury. There are 168 stages in the PSP version and over 200 in the PS2 game. Unlike the previous game, there is no strict order to play the levels. Once a Lab has been unlocked, you can play all the stages included right away.  Attributes show how well you do in the games. The best performance is awarded with a golden cork, based on four conditions: a high score (a 1 sticker), all bonus items found (a star sticker), 100% mercury (a corked test-tube), and complete the level within the time limit. While playing, your progress is measured in faces that replace the time clock. The time limit cannot cause the game to end anymore, instead it just turns into a sad face and players can still complete the level. The mercury limits have also been removed, but 100% mercury is still needed to access some of the later stages.  The top right corner shows a color chart, to help with mixing colors in the game. This can also be done in the paintshop. This release adds multi-paintshops, triangle base pyramid shaped constructions with 3 different coloured gates on either side.  In addition to the main game, there are now five party games, which are unlocked by collecting the bonus stars in the main game:  1. Metrix: puzzle games where coloured blocks need to be fit inside a pre-defined grid.  2. Paint: move the mercury to paint the tray as much as possible against your opponent.  3. Race: guide mercury around speedy track with boost pads and avoid falling off.  4. Rodeo: tilt the playing area to keep the mercury on the field, while a fan tries to knock you off.  2. Shove: aim the mercury for the center spot of the target, just like curling.  All the party games can be played in multiplayer over Wi-Fi on the PSP. The tutorial is now separate from the main game, and there is an additional Playground mode where you can test the different items in the game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mercury Meltdown.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mercury Meltdown.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mercury Meltdown.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20060929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ignition Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Ignition Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game-Action-Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear Solid - Portable Ops Plus.cso</path>
		<name>Metal Gear Solid : Portable Ops Plus</name>
		<desc>Metal Gear Solid: Portable Ops Plus is a standalone addition to last year's award winning stealth action title of the same name. Focusing on a portable multiplayer experience, players will be able to enjoy more maps, more missions, and recruit a talented crew of war heroes for battling real opponents in online arenas.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Metal Gear Solid - Portable Ops Plus.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Metal Gear Solid - Portable Ops Plus.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Metal Gear Solid - Portable Ops Plus.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20071113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Kojima Productions</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2-6</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Naruto - Ultimate Ninja Heroes.cso</path>
		<name>Naruto : Ultimate Ninja Heroes</name>
		<desc>The latest edition of the series offers a furious fighting game experience with up to 3-on-3 team-based gameplay, intense single player action and a wireless multi-player versus mode for up to two users all within the Naruto Universe. With eight interactive stages and 20 playable characters to choose from, gamers can take the battle outside the perimeters of the home to become the ultimate Hokage. In a new addition to the franchise, gamers also have the ability to create and customize their own ninja dream squads to battle opponents or trade player's profiles via wireless connectivity.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Naruto - Ultimate Ninja Heroes.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Naruto - Ultimate Ninja Heroes.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Naruto - Ultimate Ninja Heroes.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20070913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CyberConnect2</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pilot Academy.cso</path>
		<name>Pilot Academy</name>
		<desc>Pilot Academy is a flight simulator on the PSP which encompasses all eras of flight, ranging from historic WWI fighter planes such as the famous Fokker Triplane (flown by the "Red Baron" Manfred von Richthofen) to modern military and civilian jet aircraft like the F-15, F-16 and Boeing 747. All aircraft names and designs are licensed.  In the initial lessons, the game teaches the player the basics of powered flight for both civilian and military purposes. The game uses all PSP buttons to deliver a flight simulation feel with the analog nub serving as a joystick. Controlling the flaps, air brakes, raising and lowering the landing gear as well as using the tail rudder are also possible. Military aircraft feature air-to-ground missiles, air-to-air-missiles, a machine gun and flares for self defense against missiles. The only thing missing from the simulation is a fuel gauge, but since most missions are rather short, this was probably a deliberate design choice.   After civilian and military flight lessons are completed, the player is free to choose from various missions and challenges. Completing a task successfully unlocks new aircraft in the player's hangar which can then be flown any time in free flight mode (but only on the tropical map). Distinctions are also awarded for completion of a mission based on time taken, aircraft integrity, completion of objectives and level of excitement/comfort of passengers (if any) and determine the level of proficiency of the player pilot.  Flights take place over different types of terrain including tropical, desert, snow covered mountains and canyons and in varying weather conditions like rain, snow and even in a storm. Some missions begin while already airborne, while others require the player to taxi onto the runway, takeoff and land after completing the objective.    Multiplayer supports up to four players dogfighting against each other or cooperatively with planes from any of the four military eras, e.g. a dogfight between a WWII propeller plane like the P-51 Mustang or the Spitfire versus an F-14 Tomcat or F-16 Falcon is possible.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pilot Academy.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pilot Academy.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pilot Academy.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20061103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rising Star Games</developer>
		<publisher>Kuju Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Burnout Legends (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Burnout Legends</name>
		<desc>First installation of the Burnout-series on handheld consoles combines the best features of the first three games: Burnout, Burnout 2: Point of Impact, and Burnout 3: Takedown.  Aggressive racing is still the centerpiece attraction of Burnout Legends and the player's task is not only to win the races but also crash opponent cars as much as possible.  Opponent takedowns, drifts, and other stunts award Burnout Points which in turn unlock new cars and other awards.  One player games can be played as single events or as a World Tour where the player needs to compete in different races and succeed in them in order to advance through five car classes (Compact, Muscle, Coupe, Sport, and Super).  In addition there is the Crash mode, where the goal is to create as much wreckage as possible by ploughing the player car into the traffic.  The different race types include Race, Time Attack, Road Rage, Pursuit, Face Off, Eliminator, Burning Lap, and Grand Prix.  Multiplayer game modes include Race, Road Rage, Pursuit, special Crash modes Double Impact and Party Crash (all these can can be played as single events or as a tournament), and Collector Challenge where the player has the opportunity to win other player's Collector cars.  PSP version game sharing feature allows others to play multiplayer events or single player demo without their own Burnout Legends UMD.  DS version Multi-Pak support allows two player games without additional game cards.  More than two player games require multiple game cards.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Burnout Legends (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Burnout Legends (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Burnout Legends (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20050913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>6</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fading Shadows.cso</path>
		<name>Fading Shadows</name>
		<desc>Fading Shadows is a unique puzzle game for the PSP where the player leads an orb through 40 different levels by controlling a beam of light. This beam acts like a magnet to attract the orb, and can be widened or narrowed for different effects. The orb can be changed into 3 different states: metal, wood and glass. In order to solve complex puzzles and overcome obstacles, the player must utilize all the different transformations of the orb and master control over the beam of light.  The game story revolves around a young boy named Erwyn, who has been captured and imprisoned by the evil Master Gardal. The boy's soul is pure and untainted, and if Gardal sacrifices Erwyn then Gardal may breach the gates of the Castle of Heaven - a fortress built to protect the world from dark forces. However, Erwyn's clairvoyant sister has sealed his soul within a protective orb, and it is her job to free the orb from captivity and guide it safely to the Castle of Heaven.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fading Shadows.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fading Shadows.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fading Shadows.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20080902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ivolgamus</developer>
		<publisher>Ivolgamus</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game-Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="142915" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Lord Of The Rings - Tactics (USA).cso</path>
		<name>The Lord of the Rings : Tactics</name>
		<desc>The Lord of the Rings: Tactics is a completely original strategy game set in Tolkien's Middle-Earth. Players experience the entire trilogy, from the earliest battle at Weathertop to the final conclusion at Minas Tirith and Mordor.    Unlike other tactics games, which are strictly straightforward turn-based affairs, The Lord of the Rings: Tactics innovates in its system. Players assign their moves simultaneously with the AI, and then all the actions unfold. In this way, players must guess their opponent's intentions and try to block them before they actually happen. This keeps the action moving much faster than a traditional tactics game.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<image>./mixart/Lord Of The Rings - Tactics (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Lord Of The Rings - Tactics (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Lord Of The Rings - Tactics (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Syndrome.cso</path>
		<name>Alien Syndrome</name>
		<desc>Alien Syndrome is a top down shooter inspired by Sega's original Alien Syndrome action game. The games story takes place thousands of years in the future; by this point in time mankind has explored many parts of the galaxy and established numerous colonies. One such colony, Seti-Alpha 5 (SAT5), has ceased communications for some reason and it is your job to head to SAT5 and investigate what went wrong. Upon arrival, you encounter the alien syndrome, a force which can mutate man and machine into deadly aliens. These events take place roughly 100 years after those in the original Alien Syndrome game.  When you begin the game you can select one of several characters as well as choose a character specialty (such as demolitions expert, firebug,  seal, tank, and sharpshooter). The specialty you select will determine your initial character stats; as you play through the game you earn levels which provide you points to allocate towards improving your stats. The character stats help determine your characters accuracy in ranged  or close attacks, speed, healing power, resistance to fire/radiation, armor strength, and so on.  Similar to the original game, the action is viewed top down. You'll need to explore the numerous corridors and rooms found on SAT5 and eliminate the numerous alien invaders found there. Mission objectives are often provided to you which need to be completed. Additional weapons, ammo, and other useful items can be found throughout the levels. Your character has a limited amount of energy, and if all energy is lost then you will need to begin again at the last checkpoint crossed.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Alien Syndrome.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Alien Syndrome.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Alien Syndrome.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20070624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Totally Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ridge Racer (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Ridge Racer</name>
		<desc>Ridge Racer is about speed and cool power sliding. The game features a nice selection of 24 tracks, 58 cars and music from all previous RR-games and in all aspects is faithful to the series' spirit. There are many game modes in the game, like a world tour-mode where player competes on the courses in order to earn new cars and tracks, Time Attack where one races around the tracks against time and also a multiplayer mode, which supports the ad-hoc, meaning that up to eight players can race against each other with only one game disc, with one player hosting, and others joining.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ridge Racer (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ridge Racer (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ridge Racer (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Hunter Portable 3rd (Japan).cso</path>
		<name>Monster Hunter Portable 3rd (Japan)</name>
		<desc>Monster Hunter Portable 3rd is a game in the Monster Hunter franchise for the PlayStation Portable system that was released in Japan on December 1, 2010. The game was released, as a part of the PlayStation Portable Remaster series, on PlayStation 3.The game introduces new regions, monsters, and a revised Felyne combat system. Monster Hunter Portable 3rd is not an update to Monster Hunter Freedom Unite or Monster Hunter Tri. Monster Hunter Portable 3rd is instead separate to the rest of the series, and most of the game has been entirely remade. However, it is also a successor to Monster Hunter Freedom Unite as the third game in the Portable series.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20100624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>RPG</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Monster Hunter Portable 3rd (Japan).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Monster Hunter Portable 3rd (Japan).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Monster Hunter Portable 3rd (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flatout - Head On (USA).cso</path>
		<name>FlatOut : Head On</name>
		<desc>FlatOut Head On boasts the most four-wheeled mayhem ever seen on PSP, with nine different game modes, including 36 carnage challenges, full career Championship, destruction derbies, multiplayer party mode and the bone-crunching Ragdoll stunt mode.    From rock-smashing dust ups in arid desert landscapes to down and dirty races through rubbish-strewn city streets, FlatOut's PSP debut is yet another gritty excursion into racing carnage.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Flatout - Head On (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Flatout - Head On (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Flatout - Head On (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20080320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Six By Nine</developer>
		<publisher>Empire Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="28064" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Aliens Vs Predator Requiem.cso</path>
		<name>Aliens vs. Predator : Requiem</name>
		<desc>Based on the second blockbuster film from 20th Century Fox opening December, 2007, Aliens vs. Predator, is an all-new third-person action game exclusively designed for the PSP (PlayStationPortable) system from the creators of the award-winning original Aliens vs. Predator for PC. You play as an elite, lone Predator, carrying an awesome arsenal of exotic weaponry, stealth tracking and vision mode equipment. Your mission: eradicate all traces of the horrifying Alien menace from the previously sleepy town of Gunnison, Colorado.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20071113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rebellion</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Aliens Vs Predator Requiem.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Aliens Vs Predator Requiem.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Aliens Vs Predator Requiem.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28229" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./ATV Offroad Fury Pro.cso</path>
		<name>ATV Offroad Fury Pro</name>
		<desc>ATV Offroad Fury Pro is an offroad racing game which was released alongside with ATV Offroad Fury 4. Besides the expected ATV (all-terrain vehicles) there are also a variety of other vehicles to race with, e.g. trucks or bikes, which is the foundation of the career mode: participating in a string of championships which are divided in vehicle type and difficulty. Upgrades and additional vehicles are purchased with credits which can be earned in a number of ways: besides price money for winning races, credits are also awarded for performing stunts. There are also three sponsors which offer free upgrades and/or credits for fulfilling their demands regarding performance and stunt rating, but they should be hired with caution because a big penalty is assigned for missed goals. The available types of races are Supercross, Rallycross, National, Freestyle, Circuit, Endurcross, Rally and Snowcross.    Besides a basic course editor and multiplayer for up to four players (which is also the maximum number of racers in single-player) there are also connectivity features with ATV Offroad Fury 4 which allow to exchange courses/vehicles and access a shared online community.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20061026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/ATV Offroad Fury Pro.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/ATV Offroad Fury Pro.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/ATV Offroad Fury Pro.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28025" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Marvel Ultimate Alliance.cso</path>
		<name>Marvel : Ultimate Alliance</name>
		<desc>Dr. Doom has united supervillains as the Masters of Evil. Now for the first time ever, over 20 Marvel superheroes including Spider-Man, Captain America, Wolverine, Ghost Rider, Blade and Silver Surfer have come together to stop Doom. Mix and match your choice of Marvel superheroes, in teams of four as you travel across the Marvel Universe to stop this threat. Certain teams such as The Fantastic Four and The New Avengers provide additional bonuses.  Some heroes must be unlocked first. The game also features RPG elements, such as leveling up. When a hero gains a level, they earn points you can use to upgrade their skills. You also collect Shield Coins, which can be spent on boosts for your hero team.   You explore various legendary Marvel locales, from Asgard, to Prince Namor's Atlantis, where you take on foes with punches, kicks and super powers. Super powers drain energy, however, so use them wisely. Combos can be achieved by combining super powers. Energy is restored by collecting blue orbs from fallen foes.   Boss battles are like the comics themselves: titanic battles that often not only test brawn but your brain as well. With over 20 playable heroes plus all the cameos, there are over 100 heroes and villains.  The game modes feature either single player, co-op, or online play. In general, Marvel Ultimate Alliance's gameplay can be considered an improved version of 2004's X-Men: Legends. The different versions are fairly identical. The PSP release has three more game modes, while Wii, PS3 and Xbox 360 have additional levels.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20061201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raven Software</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<image>./mixart/Marvel Ultimate Alliance.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Marvel Ultimate Alliance.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Marvel Ultimate Alliance.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28459" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./MTX Mototrax (USA).cso</path>
		<name>MTX Mototrax</name>
		<desc>MTX Mototrax is a motocross racing game that features motocross legends such as Travis Pastrana and Carey Hart. As players progress in the game's career mode, they will eventually be afforded the opportunity to challenge the mentioned pros in both Supercross and Motocross events as well as freestyle trick events. Winning these events will allow the player to earn cash and sponsorships that unlock additional gear and upgraded bikes.  The game also features a track editor that gives players the option of creating their own custom tracks. Multiplayer is also an available option. Players can compete against one another through ad hoc wireless play.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20070208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Bros</developer>
		<publisher>Left Field Productions</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving-Sports</genre>
		<image>./mixart/MTX Mototrax (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/MTX Mototrax (USA).png</marquee>
	</game>
	<game id="28202" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Pursuit Force - Extreme Justice.cso</path>
		<name>Pursuit Force : Extreme Justice</name>
		<desc>Extreme Justice is the sequel to Pursuit Force and this time the player has to take down five different gangs terrorizing Capital City. Not only gangs are the opponent, there is also the Viper Division, a rival squad of police out to capture them first and put the player out of business.    There are 12 vehicle types to use throughout the game such as helicopters, cars, jet skis, trucks, buses, bike and sidecar, and speed boats as well as new vehicles including hovercrafts. There are 30 types of weapons, ranging from handguns clear up to heavy artillery. Another new feature is the "Justice Bar" that helps regain strength and keeps the mission going. The game has 50 criminal cases and four new characters to play as.    It also features a multiplayer modes that can support up to four different players (PSP Wi-Fi Ad Hoc).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bigbig Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<image>./mixart/Pursuit Force - Extreme Justice.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pursuit Force - Extreme Justice.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Pursuit Force - Extreme Justice.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28237" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./R-Type Tactics.cso</path>
		<name>R-Type Tactics</name>
		<desc>In a desperate war against the mysterious alien race known as the Bydo, humanity sends wave after wave of fighters into Bydo space -- none of which are ever heard from again. Mankind's main hope now resides with a lone commander, sent to lead a small armada on a perilous mission into the heart of the Bydo Empire. Low on fuel and forced to scavenge resources and equipment from his surroundings, the commander must use all his cunning and wits if he hopes to succeed, let alone make it home alive.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20080506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rising Star Games</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./mixart/R-Type Tactics.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/R-Type Command (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/R-Type Command (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28306" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Socom US Navy Seals Fireteam Bravo 2.cso</path>
		<name>SOCOM : U.S. Navy SEALs, Fireteam Bravo 2</name>
		<desc>The Navy SEALs are invading the PSP for a second covert campaign, one that will take handheld owners through 14 non-linear missions with dynamically changing objectives. Commanders guide a two-man team across multiple terrain types as they strive to build "command equity" and "local influence" through successful stealth and tactical operations. By rescuing civilians, completing goals, and uncovering bonus objectives, players will earn points to spend on weapons or military support in the form of supply drops and air strikes. Black market equipment and intelligence can also be acquired from the local populace, improving the SEAL team's chances for success.    An entry in the SOCOM series wouldn't be complete without multiplayer options, and Fireteam Bravo 2 includes wireless support for up to 16 players in both Ad-hoc and Infrastructure modes. Three new game types are introduced in this sequel, including a capture-the-flag variant, and users are now able to create custom tournaments, ladders, and even clan challenges. Fireteam Bravo 2 also offers an improved friends list and instant messaging to help simplify the process of finding worthy teammates and opponents. As in the first PSP title, Fireteam Bravo 2 lets owners of the PS2 version link the two games to unlock special features in both SOCOM titles.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070620T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zipper Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-16</players>
		<image>./mixart/Socom US Navy Seals Fireteam Bravo 2.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Socom US Navy Seals Fireteam Bravo 2.png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Socom US Navy Seals Fireteam Bravo 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28267" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Toca Race Driver 3.cso</path>
		<name>Toca Race Driver 3 Challenge</name>
		<desc>DTM Race Driver 3 Challenge is the third game in the series and the first to appear on the PSP. The main change is the new game mode “World Challenge” in which players take part in mission-based challenges.  Tracks include the British GT championship, Australia’s V8 Supercars, Germany’s DTM events and American Race series.    Four players can compete across a wireless network connection by sharing one game. Twelve players can race against each other with full versions of the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20070217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<image>./mixart/Toca Race Driver 3.png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Toca Race Driver 3.png</marquee>
	</game>
	<game id="28164" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Untold Legends - Brotherhood of the Blade (EU).cso</path>
		<name>Untold Legends : Brotherhood of the Blade</name>
		<desc>Journey to a world beyond the realms of imagination and engage in battles to save Aven, a timeless city of safe haven and the last remaining stronghold of Good in a world of Evil. As a dark threat looms and a gathering of unknown forces grows stronger, heroes have been called and the Brotherhood of the Blade has been formed. It is up to you and your chosen brothers to unravel the mysteries of this looming peril. Untold Legends: Brotherhood of the Blade offers on-the-go action-RPG combat, intense multiplayer battles and a completely original adventure for you to uncover.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20050901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/Untold Legends - Brotherhood of the Blade (EU).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Untold Legends - Brotherhood of the Blade (EU).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Untold Legends - Brotherhood of the Blade (EU).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28530" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Xyanide - Resurrection (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (v1.01).cso</path>
		<name>Xyanide : Resurrection</name>
		<desc>Xyanide Resurrection est un shoot'em up sur Playstation Portable. En tant que shérif de l'espace, il vous faut nettoyer le vide spatial des légions d'Aguira, légions nées de la combinaison de magie impie et d'une étrange substance vivante connue sous le nom de Xyanide. Plusieurs modes de difficulté costauds et quinze niveaux différents sont au programme.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20070928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Playlogic International</developer>
		<publisher>Playlogic International</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Xyanide - Resurrection (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (v1.01).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Xyanide - Resurrection (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (v1.01).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Xyanide - Resurrection (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (v1.01).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="28419" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./TRON - Evolution (USA) (PSN).cso</path>
		<name>TRON : Evolution</name>
		<desc>Tron: Evolution is a third-person action-adventure, tie-in video game for the film Tron: Legacy by Propaganda Games, published by Disney Interactive. It was officially announced at the Spike Video Game Awards and was released for the Microsoft Windows, PlayStation 3, PlayStation Portable and Xbox 360 platforms on November 26, 2010 in Europe and December 7, 2010 in North America.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20110203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SuperVillain Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/TRON - Evolution (USA) (PSN).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/TRON - Evolution (USA) (PSN).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/TRON - Evolution (USA) (PSN).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aliens Vs Predator Requiem.cso</path>
		<name>Aliens vs. Predator : Requiem</name>
		<desc>Based on the second blockbuster film from 20th Century Fox opening December, 2007, Aliens vs. Predator, is an all-new third-person action game exclusively designed for the PSP (PlayStationPortable) system from the creators of the award-winning original Aliens vs. Predator for PC. You play as an elite, lone Predator, carrying an awesome arsenal of exotic weaponry, stealth tracking and vision mode equipment. Your mission: eradicate all traces of the horrifying Alien menace from the previously sleepy town of Gunnison, Colorado.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Aliens Vs Predator Requiem.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Aliens Vs Predator Requiem.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Aliens Vs Predator Requiem.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20071113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rebellion</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ape Escape on the Loose.cso</path>
		<name>Ape Escape : On the Loose</name>
		<desc>Based on the Ape Escape series, Ape Escape: On the Loose arrives on the PSP with multiplayer functionality and a variety of minigames. The new adventure begins when Specter--a monkey-turned-monster--and his army of monkeys travel back in time to change history and take over the world. Now it's up to you to pursue Specter and capture more than 200 monkeys in eight different worlds, which span more than 20 levels.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ape Escape on the Loose.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ape Escape on the Loose.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ape Escape on the Loose.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20060510T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ape Escape Academy.cso</path>
		<name>Ape Escape Academy</name>
		<desc>Ape Escape Academy sees you taking on the role of one of the cheeky monkeys from the Ape Escape series. Choose your chimp, then prepare to tackle various classes in Academy Mode. Each 'class' is actually a mini-game. Your goal is to complete as many mini-games as possible from the 9x9 grid, and score as many lines as you can (sort of like Noughts and Crosses). Mini-games range from mind-bending quizzes to wacky sports games, to the just plain silly, like protecting a roast banana from oncoming apes, or flying through the sky delivering parachutes to plummeting primates.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ape Escape Academy.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ape Escape Academy.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ape Escape Academy.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daxter.cso</path>
		<name>Daxter</name>
		<desc>Daxter stars for the first time on his own in this action-platformer that reveals how he became a hero and freed Jak at the beginning of Jak II. Finally able to explore past the secure boundaries of Haven City, Daxter inadvertently takes on a job as a pest exterminator, a task the Old Sage intuitively knew he was proficient at since the first Jak and Daxter. Armed with a fly swatter and soon afterwards a spray canister that allows him to not only stun bugs but to hover in the air, Daxter unravels to the player the introduction of the upcoming invasion that occurred in Jak II into Haven City. The invasion is led by the Metal Heads who are using bug-like variations called Metal Bugs to permeate the city. Later upgrades include a flame thrower attachment as well as a detonator weapon.  Daxter's path towards freeing Jak involves a series of platforming and combat challenges through a wide variety of environments ranging from a high speed transit system to a fish cannery, and all the way to the Krimson Guard fortress where Daxter has to sneak past the guards to eventually save Jak.  Daxter features a variety of vehicle levels, minigames typical of the Jak series, as well as a series of dream level sequences that take Daxter into a realm where he is the hero. The dream minigames spoof cinematic moments from The Matrix, Indiana Jones, Braveheart and Lord of the Rings. Wi-fi multiplayer mode of Bug combat is included, where players can use their trained collected bugs to fight each other.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Daxter.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Daxter.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Daxter.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20060420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ready At Dawn Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Death Jr (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Death Jr.</name>
		<desc>Take on the role of the Grim Reapers teenage son Death Jr. after he unleashes an unspeakable horror from a box that Pandora herself couldn't open in a school field trip at the museum.  Death Jr. is a 3-D platform game in which you control Death Jr. a.k.a. DJ in an attempt to find his friends that have been taken by the evil necromancer Moloch. DJ's friend souls appear as puzzle pieces throughout the game in which you must find to bring them back.  Warp through 17 levels fighting demons and fiends using DJ's famed scythe along with other weapons like a shotgun, electric gun and even C4 Hamsters. Use DJ's scythe to not only maim and kill but to reach heights not accessible by jumping. Upgrade weapons and learn new moves (scythe combos) by collecting widgets scattered throughout the levels. The ability to destroy the environment is an advantage to DJ as the more successful hits with his scythe be it animate or inanimate his combo meter will rise allowing DJ's friend Pandora to assist in the fight.  Death Jr.'s camera is a free roaming camera that follows DJ around with the ability to snap to the position DJ is looking at the press of a button. You can also free look with the press of a button and lock on to enemies and strafe while shooting with a gun. At the end of each level you receive a report card that tells you your number of kills, how much destruction you caused, the total number of combo points, special items discovered and your final grade.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Death Jr II - Root of Evil.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Death Jr II - Root of Evil.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Death Jr II - Root of Evil.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Backbone Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Def Jam Fight For NY - The Takeover.cso</path>
		<name>Def Jam : Fight for NY, The Takeover</name>
		<desc>Def Jam Fight for NY takes the battle for hip-hop domination into the fighting ring. More than 35 hip-hop artists and personalities--including Busta Rhymes, Carmen Electra, Lil' Kim, Ludacris, Method Man, Redman, Sean Paul, Slick Rick, and Snoop Dogg--face off in brutal wrestling matches. In the ring and on the streets, you'll join the battle as a New York City street fighter. The game challenges you to develop your own fighting style and seize control of the hip-hop underworld.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Def Jam Fight For NY - The Takeover.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Def Jam Fight For NY - The Takeover.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Def Jam Fight For NY - The Takeover.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20060829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AKI Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disgaea - Afternoon of Darkness (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Disgaea : Afternoon of Darkness</name>
		<desc>Disgaea is a tactical role playing game. Battle gameplay takes place on a map divided into a square grid. The player controls a squad of humanoid units and monsters, which each occupy a single square of the grid and do combat with a group of enemies. Depending on the character and attack selected, the player will be able to deal damage to a specific enemy unit or a designated region of the map. Combat ends when all enemy units or all of the player's units are destroyed.  Humanoid characters may lift and throw other units across the map in order to allow allies to move further or force enemies to keep their distance. This even allows the player to capture enemies by throwing them into the base panel; these enemies then become allies, and can be used on subsequent maps. The chance of capturing an enemy in this manner depends on several factors. Failure to capture the enemy will result in the death of all characters inside the base panel, and the enemy will survive.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Disgaea - Afternoon of Darkness (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Disgaea - Afternoon of Darkness (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Disgaea - Afternoon of Darkness (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20071030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Nippon Ichi Software</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Everybodys Golf 2.cso</path>
		<name>Everybody's Golf 2</name>
		<desc>Step out of the clubhouse and onto the open tee with Hot Shots Golf Open Tee 2. The classic, entertaining golf franchise returns to the PSP system with new quirky characters, beautiful courses and a huge variety of customizable options that enable you to take your golf game wherever you go.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Everybodys Golf 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Everybodys Golf 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Everybodys Golf 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20080528T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Clap Hanz</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon - Advanced Warfighter 2.cso</path>
		<name>Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter 2</name>
		<desc>Scott Mitchell, the leader of the ghosts, is sent south of the Panama border to eliminate guerrilla forces believed to be trafficking high-tech weapons to rebel forces.     â€¢ Exclusively developed for the PSPÂ®: Original story, setting, technology and gameplay for you to engage in.   â€¢ Advanced Warfighter: Master prototype weapons, use drone technology and call in naval artillery or air strike support.   â€¢ Co-op multiplayer: Play the entire campaign with a friend over wireless network.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon - Advanced Warfighter 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon - Advanced Warfighter 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon - Advanced Warfighter 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto : Chinatown Wars</name>
		<desc>LEFT FOR DEAD IN THE WORST PLACE IN AMERICA    Following his father's murder, Huang Lee has a simple mission: deliver an ancient sword to his Uncle Kenny to ensure his family retains control of the Triad gangs of Liberty City. Huang is a spoiled rich kid who expects everything to run smoothly, but his trip does not go exactly as planned. After being robbed and left to die, he will search for honor, riches and revenge in the most dangerous and morally bankrupt city in the world.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20091020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Games</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Liberty City Stories.cso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto : Liberty City Stories</name>
		<desc>There are a million stories in Liberty City. This one changes everything. Once a trusted wise guy in the Leone crime family, Toni Cipriani was forced into hiding after killing a made man. Now he's back and it's time for things to be put right. The streets of Liberty City are in turmoil. Warring mafiosi vie for control as the town begins to self-destruct under waves of political corruption, organized crime, drug trafficking and union strikes. No one can be trusted as Toni tries to clean up the mess of the city's chaotic underworld. Deranged hit men, morally depraved tycoons, cynical politicians and his own mother stand in his way as Toni tries to bring the city under Leone control. Forced to fight for his life in an odyssey that will shake Liberty City to its foundations, Toni must use any means necessary to secure his place in the leadership of the Leone family in a town up for grabs.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grand Theft Auto - Liberty City Stories.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Grand Theft Auto - Liberty City Stories.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grand Theft Auto - Liberty City Stories.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20051024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Take 2 Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<players>6</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Vice City Stories.cso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto : Vice City Stories</name>
		<desc>Vice City, 1984. Opportunity abounds in a city emerging from the swamps, its growth fueled by the violent power struggle in a lucrative drug trade. Construction is everywhere as a shining metropolis rises from foundations of crime and betrayal.  As a soldier, Vic Vance has always protected his dysfunctional family, his country, and himself. One bad decision later and that job is about to get much harder. Kicked out onto the streets of a city torn between glamor and gluttony, Vic is faced with a stark choice: build an empire or be crushed.  GTA: VCS is the PlayStation Portable follow-up to Rockstar's monumental handheld entry in the series, Grand Theft Auto: Liberty City Stories. As in Liberty City Stories, this game ventures back to the location of the second PS2 game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City Stories.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City Stories.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City Stories.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20061031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Games</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 3rd person-Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-6</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jeanne D'Arc.cso</path>
		<name>Jeanne d'Arc</name>
		<desc>It is the 15th century, the time of the Hundred Years' War between England and France. A young French girl from the village of Domremy trying to assist her father with his daily labors discovers a mysterious object: an armlet that binds magically on her wrist. Soon the village is being attacked and finding the first sword she can, she steps forth to encounter the enemy, some humanoid beasts. Taking strength from the armlet, hearing a mysterious voice and having for assistance her close friends, she manages to defeat them and embarks on a long quest to help her countrymen and vanquish the evil forces invading France.  Jeanne d'Arc is a turn-based strategy RPG game of the Japanese variety, that fuses medieval history with fantasy and the craziness of Japanese anime. This is a well known story retold through tactical battles one after another, while game dialog along with hand drawn cutscenes twist the story into different territories from the original.   It is a story of teen friendship and dedication, remorseless war, evil magic, unavoidable death, heartache abandonment and purifying hope. Jeanne joins the army and along with 14 other companions with different skills and personalities march to face England's Henry VI's troops. With her are other armlet wielders, able to use them and transform into fearsome warriors able to strike down evil at its core. The game features a map to move through locations where the battles which push the story forward happen along with free stages that add nothing more than fun, strong items and difficult bosses.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Jeanne D'Arc.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Jeanne D'Arc.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jeanne D'Arc.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20061122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Justice League Heroes (EU).cso</path>
		<name>Justice League Heroes</name>
		<desc>Military robots cause havoc in a high tech Metropolis research facility. In Finland, genetically-engineered creatures take over the top secret Deep Space Communications Array.  A team of super powered criminals, having never worked together before, seize a Nevada missile base.  And deep beneath the surface of Mars, dozens of alien warriors are released from their long imprisonment…  These seemingly unrelated events prove to be pieces of a sinister plan, and it will take Earth’s greatest superheroes to stop it: The Justice League!  Justice League Heroes is an action game, also for two players cooperatively, based on the popular DC Comics series.  Control DC’s most popular heroes: Superman, Batman, Wonder Woman, Green Lantern, Martian Manhunter, The Flash, Zatanna and a handful of unlockable characters like Aquaman, Green Arrow, Hawkgirl, Huntress, Hal Jordan, and Kyle Rayner. In addition, the PSP version features exclusive unlockable heroes: Supergirl and Black Canary.  Players battle through famous locations such as Metropolis, S.T.A.R. labs, and for the first time, the Justice League's Watchtower.  Many of DC’s greatest villains face against our heroes including Braniac, Killer Frost, Darkseid, and Doomsday.  Boss battles are furious and unique, with no two defeated the same way.  Superpowers are developed through experience orbs collected from a wide range of enemies such as The White Martians, Brainiac’s assassin droids, and alternate-dimensional creatures.  Some special orbs known as “boosts” can enhance superpowers.  The boosts range from enhanced damage, efficiency, attack range, luck, speed, and super power duration.  Multiple boosts can combine into a single, more powerful boost.  Players can allocate their orbs and boosts to customize heroes to best suit their playing style.  Special shield icons placed throughout the game can be collected and spent to unlock characters and alternate costumes which affect the heroes' abilities as well their appearances.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Justice League Heroes (EU).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Justice League Heroes (EU).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Justice League Heroes (EU).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Snowblind Studios, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Brothers</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lego Batman.cso</path>
		<name>LEGO Batman : The Video Game</name>
		<desc>Lego Batman: The Videogame is an action-adventure video game developed by Traveller's Tales, published by Warner Bros., and released in 2008 for the Xbox 360, PlayStation 2, PlayStation 3, PlayStation Portable, Nintendo DS, Mac OS X and Wii video gaming platforms. It is the first Lego Batman video game. The game is based on the comic book character Batman and the Lego Batman toy line, who also handled marketing and financial aspects of the game.    The game is similar to the Lego Star Wars series and Lego Indiana Jones: The Original Adventures, in that it is both a game based on a licensed property, and has environments, objects, and creatures made out of Lego. However, Lego Batman is the first to have an original story. The Mac OS X version of the game was released in April 2009 by Feral Interactive.[2] A standalone sequel titled Lego Batman 2: DC Super Heroes was released on June 19, 2012, and a follow-up titled Lego Batman 3: Beyond Gotham was released on November 11, 2014.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Lego Batman.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Lego Batman.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Lego Batman.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20081009T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Brothers</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lego Indiana.Jones.The.Original.Adventures.cso</path>
		<name>LEGO Indiana Jones : La Trilogie Originale</name>
		<image>./mixart/Lego Indiana.Jones.The.Original.Adventures.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Lego Indiana.Jones.The.Original.Adventures.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Lego Indiana.Jones.The.Original.Adventures.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>Travellers Tales</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lego Star Wars 2.cso</path>
		<name>LEGO Star Wars II : The Original Trilogy</name>
		<desc>Lego Star Wars II: The Original Trilogy is a multi-platform action-adventure video game developed by Traveller's Tales and published by LucasArts and TT Games. It was released on September 11, 2006. Part of the Lego Star Wars series, it is based on the Star Wars science fiction media franchise and Lego Group's Star Wars-themed toy line. It follows the events of the Star Wars films Star Wars, The Empire Strikes Back and Return of the Jedi. The game allows players to assume the roles of over 50 Lego versions of characters from the film series; customized characters can also be created. Camera movement was improved from its predecessorâ€”Lego Star Wars: The Video Game; and the concept of "vehicle levels" was explored more thoroughly. The game was revealed at American International Toy Fair 2006. Promotions for the game were set up at chain stores across the United States.    Lego Star Wars II was critically and commercially successful; it has sold over 8.2 million copies worldwide as of May 2009. Critics praised the game for its comedic and "adorable"[2][3] portrayal of the film series and for their preference of the original trilogy to the prequel trilogy. However, the game's low difficulty, and its Game Boy Advance and Nintendo DS versions in general, were received more poorly. The game received awards from the British Academy of Film and Television Arts and Spike TV, among others. A mobile phone adaptation was later developed by Universomo, published by THQ, and released on December 19, 2006. Lego Star Wars and Lego Star Wars II were compiled in Lego Star Wars: The Complete Saga, released on November 6, 2007. The OS X version of the game was released in April 2007 by Feral Interactive.[4]</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Lego Star Wars 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Lego Star Wars 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Lego Star Wars 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20061110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LEGO Star Wars III - The Clone Wars (EU).cso</path>
		<name>LEGO Star Wars III : The Clone Wars</name>
		<desc>Lego Star Wars III: The Clone Wars is a 2011 Lego game for the PlayStation 3, PlayStation Portable, Xbox 360, Wii, Nintendo DS, Microsoft Windows and Nintendo 3DS consoles, and based on The Clone Wars animated series, developed by Traveller's Tales and published by LucasArts and TT Games, released in March 2011[2] and is the latest game of the Lego Star Wars video game series. Lego Star Wars III features missions and characters from the Clone Wars television series, as well as favourite characters from the original Star Wars saga, in both single-player and multiplayer gameplay modes.[3][4][5] The Mac OS X version of the game has been released by Feral Interactive.[1]</desc>
		<image>./mixart/LEGO Star Wars III - The Clone Wars (EU).png</image>
		<video>./snap/LEGO Star Wars III - The Clone Wars (EU).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/LEGO Star Wars III - The Clone Wars (EU).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20110322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Travellers Tales</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Little Big Planet (USA).cso</path>
		<name>LittleBigPlanet</name>
		<desc>LittleBigPlanet's critically acclaimed - PLAY, CREATE, SHARE - experience, makes its way to the PSP system with a completely new Sackboy adventure. PLAY through 35+ levels and collect prize bubbles, costumes, and - CREATE - materials. CREATE your own levels and challenges with the easy to use POP-IT tool. Once complete, SHARE your creations in ad-hoc mode or post them to the community pool in infrastructure mode.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Little Big Planet (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Little Big Planet (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Little Big Planet (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20091117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCE Studio Cambridge</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Various-Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Moto GP.cso</path>
		<name>Moto GP</name>
		<desc>MotoGP is a motorcycle racing game based on the 2005 MotoGP season. It features all the riders from that 2005 season, but only eight of the seventeen circuits. There are two main modes of play, arcade and season. Arcade allows the player to select any rider and track to race on. Season mode allows the player to take part in a complete season with one 'real-life' rider, or alternatively to compete over multiple seasons with a fictional rider, with the ability to move teams at the end of the season depending on the performance during the season. Different levels of difficulty relating to the realism of the bikes handling and performance are offered to cater for both novice and more experienced players. All the usual setup options are available to tune the bikes for each track.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Moto GP.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Moto GP.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Moto GP.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20061025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Need For Speed Most Wanted USA.cso</path>
		<name>Need for Speed : Most Wanted 5-1-0</name>
		<desc>Need for Speed: Most Wanted (commonly abbreviated to as NFS: MW or just Most Wanted) is a racing video game developed by EA Black Box and published by Electronic Arts. It is the ninth installment in the Need for Speed series. The game features street racing-oriented game play, with certain customization options from the Need for Speed: Underground series. The game is succeeded by Need for Speed: Carbon, which serves as a sequel to Most Wanted.    Most Wanted has been released for Nintendo DS, Microsoft Windows, PlayStation 2, Xbox, GameCube, Game Boy Advance and is the first Need for Speed game released for the seventh generation console, the Xbox 360, as one of the system's launch titles. Another version of Most Wanted, titled Need for Speed: Most Wanted 5-1-0 has been released for the PlayStation Portable. In May 2012, the PlayStation 2 version was released on the online virtual market, PlayStation Store, for the PlayStation 3. On June 1, 2012, a reboot of the game, also called Need for Speed: Most Wanted, was announced by the British developing team Criterion Games and was released on October 30, 2012.    Need for Speed: Most Wanted received positive reviews and was a commercial success; it sold 16 million copies worldwide, making it the best-selling title in the series</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Need For Speed Most Wanted USA.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Need For Speed Most Wanted USA.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Need For Speed Most Wanted USA.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pac-Man World Rally (US).cso</path>
		<name>Pac-man Rally</name>
		<desc>A kart-race game with Pac-Man and other characters from previous Pac-Man games and other Namco franchises. For instance the PlayStation Portable version features Mr. Driller, Mappy and the Prince from Katamari Damacy .    The game is packed with not only the traditional Dots to consume and enemies to avoid, but also with power-ups and temporary advantages which players should use strategically to win the race and beat opponents. One example is a power slide to turn corners at full speed. Of course, enemies can also be bitten after eating a Power Pellet.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pac-Man World Rally (US).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pac-Man World Rally (US).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pac-Man World Rally (US).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20060822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Smart Bomb Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pixel Junk Monsters Deluxe (USA).cso</path>
		<name>PixelJunk Monsters Deluxe</name>
		<desc>In PixelJunk Monsters Deluxe, the player controls a defender-of-the-forest character in a lush 2D environment. The player's goal is to strategically defend the pathway to his home base from an onslaught of various threatening monsters. In between waves of monster attacks, the player scrambles to reinforce his defenses by collecting gold coins and jewels from fallen enemies to finance new towers and research deadlier weapons. The game features a new island with more than 10 stages, new enemies, music tracks and special bonus features. With two new unique towers available, players can enjoy all the original Monster stages with fresh new gameplay.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pixel Junk Monsters Deluxe (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pixel Junk Monsters Deluxe (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pixel Junk Monsters Deluxe (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20091029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Q-Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type Command (USA).cso</path>
		<name>R-Type Command</name>
		<desc>In a desperate war against the mysterious alien race known as the Bydo, humanity sends wave after wave of fighters into Bydo space -- none of which are ever heard from again. Mankind's main hope now resides with a lone commander, sent to lead a small armada on a perilous mission into the heart of the Bydo Empire. Low on fuel and forced to scavenge resources and equipment from his surroundings, the commander must use all his cunning and wits if he hopes to succeed, let alone make it home alive.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/R-Type Command (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/R-Type Command (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/R-Type Command (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20080506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rising Star Games</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rainbow Islands Evolution (USA) (En,Fr,Es).cso</path>
		<name>Rainbow Islands Evolution</name>
		<desc>Rainbow Islands Evolution is a game in the Bubble Bobble series for the PSP system. It is also known as New Rainbow Islands Hurdy Gurdy Daibouken in Japan. It is an enhanced remake of the arcade game Rainbow Islands.    Bub and Bob, the two main characters in the series, are against an evil recording company that seeks to pollute the Rainbow Islands' atmosphere by creating constant musical noise, therefore wilting the flora and mutating the fauna. In this game, Bub and Bob use a hurdy-gurdy (an old European musical instrument) as a weapon to create the rainbows.    The game follows the same vertical-scrolling system from the original, but it expands to a third dimension as there are platforms in the background which become accessible through the course of the game.    The game suffers from reviews stating that it had been overworked with new features, especially those that make this version of the game differ significantly from the original game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rainbow Islands Evolution (USA) (En,Fr,Es).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rainbow Islands Evolution (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rainbow Islands Evolution (USA) (En,Fr,Es).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20070208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rising Star Games</developer>
		<publisher>Marvelous Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rainbow Six Vegas.cso</path>
		<name>Rainbow Six Vegas</name>
		<desc>The stakes are high when the world's most elite counter-terrorism unit enters Las Vegas, where over 36.7 million men, women and children visit each year. "Sin City," the home of the famous Las Vegas Strip, flashy hotels, high-rolling casinos and world-famous celebrities, becomes the setting for a terrorist threat of global proportions. What happens when one of the world's most famous cities is held hostage by terrorists?</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rainbow Six Vegas.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rainbow Six Vegas.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rainbow Six Vegas.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20070612T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scarface.cso</path>
		<name>Scarface : Money. Power. Respect.</name>
		<desc>Scarface : Money. Power. Respect. sur PSP vous permet de remettre la main sur l'empire de la drogue du baron cubain. Combinez le jeu de stratégie au tour par tour et l'action en temps réel pour vous faire revivre l'ascension de Tony Montana. Dans un Miami réaliste, rivalisez avec vos ennemis pour la conquête du territoire et contrôlez l'action en temps réel lors des combats en pleine rue. Jusqu'à quatre joueurs peuvent s'affronter en wi-fi.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Scarface.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Scarface.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Scarface.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20061117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Universal </developer>
		<publisher>FarSight Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Rivals.cso</path>
		<name>Sonic Rivals</name>
		<desc>Sonic Rivals is a platforming/racing game and the first game in the series to feature on the PSP. It has typical Sonic gameplay, but with a twist - players race through 2.5D stages against a CPU character, only progressing when they get to the end of the stage first.  You can choose from five characters: Sonic, Knuckles, Shadow, Silver, and Metal Sonic. There are six zones in the story mode, split into two acts with a boss at the end of the second act. Defeating bosses is not sufficient, players also need to do it before the opponent gets the job done. Next to the story mode, there is also a challenge mode and a cup mode. In the wireless play mode players can challenge other PSP owners. While racing, players can collect power-ups with special attacks. Opponents can also be pushed around during the race.  Players can also collect cards by completing certain tasks in the game and these cards can be traded in the wireless play mode.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sonic Rivals.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sonic Rivals.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sonic Rivals.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20061116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Backbone Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man 2 (USA) (v1.01).cso</path>
		<name>Spider-Man 2</name>
		<desc>Based off the sequel to the popular 2002 movie of the same name, Spider-Man 2 once again places the player in the Web-Swinger's tights as he goes up against Dr. Octopus in this 3D adventure game.    Unlike the first game, however, the sequel is much more open-ended (a la Grand Theft Auto: Vice City), allowing Spider-Man free reign to explore New York City, and doing everyday tasks from stopping muggers, bank robberies and car-jackers, to delivering pizzas and snapping photos for the Daily Bugle.    However, the action becomes even more intense as not only does Spidey have to keep the streets safe in general for the citizens of Manhattan, he also has to face up against such super villains as Rhino, Shocker, Mysterio and Calypso, as well as a few entanglements with the Black Cat along the way to square off against Dr. Octopus and save New York in the process!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Spider-Man 2 (USA) (v1.01).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Spider-Man 2 (USA) (v1.01).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Spider-Man 2 (USA) (v1.01).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20050901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Vicarious Visions</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man - Web of Shadows (USA) (En,Fr) (v1.01).cso</path>
		<name>Spider-Man : Web of Shadows</name>
		<desc>Spider-Man: Web of Shadows is a video game title encompassing three versions: a full-3D action game for Microsoft Windows, PlayStation 3, Wii, and Xbox 360; a 2.5D sidescrolling beat em up action game for the PlayStation Portable and PlayStation 2 (called Amazing Allies Edition), and a 2.5D side-scrolling brawler/platformer[1] for the Nintendo DS.    Spider-Man: Web of Shadows, along with most other games published by Activision that had used the Marvel licence, was de-listed and removed from all digital storefronts on January 1, 2014.[2][3]</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Spider-Man - Web of Shadows (USA) (En,Fr) (v1.01).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Spider-Man - Web of Shadows (USA) (En,Fr) (v1.01).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Spider-Man - Web of Shadows (USA) (En,Fr) (v1.01).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.25</rating>
		<releasedate>20081024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treyarch</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spinout (EU).cso</path>
		<name>Spinout</name>
		<desc>Spinout is a mix of the concepts of Marble Madness and the Monkey Ball series, but set in a futuristic environment. Players need to guide a shiny ball dubbed a xorb through high-tech environments at a high speed. The tracks are narrow and it is easy to drop off at any time, so precise steering is needed.  Games can be played in an arcade mode with forking paths or in a career mode where new tracks are unlocked gradually. Courses are time-limited and set in very different environments. Checkpoint allow the player to respawn at certain sections. While playing, power-ups can be collected to access air brakes and other bonuses. The xorbs can be completely customized in terms of colour. Other game modes are time trial, three multiplayer modes and a bowling mini-game. In certain game modes the xorbs can be armed with weapons such as rockets and missiles, which also deform the xorb when taking damage.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Spinout (EU).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Spinout (EU).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Spinout (EU).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20080515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ghostlight</developer>
		<publisher>Icon Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Split-Second - Velocity (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Ru).cso</path>
		<name>Split-Second : Velocity</name>
		<desc>Split/Second, released in the UK as Split/Second: Velocity, is an arcade racing video game developed by Black Rock Studio and published by Disney Interactive Studios for Microsoft Windows, PlayStation 3, and Xbox 360. Revealed in March 2009, the game was released in May 2010[1] and was later released for OnLive in June 2011.[2] In the game, players take part in a fictional reality television show, consisting of a variety of events, each focusing on destructible environments triggered remotely by driver actions known as "powerplays".[3]    Split/Second was ported to the PlayStation Portable.[4]</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Split-Second - Velocity (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Ru).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Split-Second - Velocity (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Ru).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Split-Second - Velocity (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Ru).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20101118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Black Rock Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pursuit Force.cso</path>
		<name>Pursuit Force</name>
		<desc>Five different gangs are terrorizing the cities, namely Warlords, Capelli Family, Killer66, Vixens, and Convicts. Cities are in chaos as the regular police is helpless. Therefore, a special unit is formed to deal with such a threat, a special unit called the Pursuit Force. You are part of that unit.  Your task is to hunt down the criminals and let none escape. To do so, you will drive your fast car on the streets while being perfectly able to switch the vehicles on the run. Yes, on the run, you can jump from car to car during high speed, usually jumping on the different cars from the criminals and taking them out one by one. But there's more to that than just driving different cars, you can drive motorcycles, trucks, boats, even commandeer a helicopter, though there are occasions you'll have to deal with the criminals on foot.  You can select Time Trial, Race, or Career mode. The latter one plays story-wise which gives you certain variety of cases to choose from. As you get promoted while successfully solving the cases, new cases will become available depending upon your rank, from mere Officer to police Commander. This is a highly fast-paced game with non-stop action, as most missions leave very little room for mistakes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pursuit Force.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pursuit Force.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pursuit Force.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20051123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Bigbig Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="28003" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Dead or Alive - Paradise (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Dead or Alive Paradise</name>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20100402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ninja</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Dead or Alive - Paradise (USA).png</image>
	</game>
	<game id="28329" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Everybody's Tennis (Europe) (PSN).cso</path>
		<name>Everybody's Tennis</name>
		<desc>Everybody's Tennis sur PSP est le portage du titre éponyme sorti sur Playstation 2. Ce jeu de sport vous propose des parties de tennis déjantées, en simple ou en double et jusqu'à 4 joueurs en réseau local. Coups spéciaux et humour sont les lignes directrices de ce titre.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20100101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Clap Hanz</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/Everybody's Tennis (Europe) (PSN).png</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Avatar - The Last Airbender (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Avatar : The Last Airbender</name>
		<desc>Bring to life an adventure of intrigue, deceit and revelation in Avatar: The Last Airbender, based on the popular Nickelodeon show. Play as Aang, Katara, Haru and Sokka as you grow your team into an unstoppable force and make discoveries in this thrilling blend of magic and martial arts. Use your fully customisable bending powers to master the four elements of Earth, Air, Water and Fire and explore the beautifully detailed environments of the Avatar nations.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Avatar - The Last Airbender (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Avatar - The Last Airbender (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Avatar - The Last Airbender (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20061208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Studio Oz</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cho Aniki Zero (USA) (PSN).cso</path>
		<name>Cho Aniki</name>
		<desc>Cho Aniki Zero brings manliness back to the old-school shoot-em-up genre and, warps it to another dimension of sights and sounds. In Cho Aniki Zero, players will be introduced to brand-new characters and newly heightened experiences of rhythmic action, intertwined with the famous BGM of Kouji Hayama. Battle through five man-rageous levels of brotherly love and muscle-on-muscle madness!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Cho Aniki Zero (USA) (PSN).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Cho Aniki Zero (USA) (PSN).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cho Aniki Zero (USA) (PSN).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20111005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya Games</developer>
		<publisher>NCS Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dantes Inferno.cso</path>
		<name>Dante's Inferno</name>
		<desc>Dante's Inferno will take gamers to the western world's most definitive view of the afterlife as created by the 13th century Italian poet Dante Alighieri. Each of the nine circles will showcase its own distinct look, with demons, monsters and geography that are crafted straight from the poem's vivid descriptions. Using Death's Scythe and Beatrice's Holy Cross, and a slate of magic powers with a deep, customizable upgrade system, players will experience a fast and fluid 60 frames-per-second gameplay experience.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dantes Inferno.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dantes Inferno.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dantes Inferno.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20100225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>A2M</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hammerin Hero.cso</path>
		<name>Hammerin' Hero</name>
		<image>./mixart/Hammerin Hero.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Hammerin Hero.mp4</video>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20090303T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DHM Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hot Shots Tennis - Get a Grip (USA) (PSP) (PSN).cso</path>
		<name>Hot Shots Tennis : Get a Grip</name>
		<desc>Hot Shots Tennis is a fun, accessible sports game that's easy to pick up and play but very hard to put down. Taking the popular characters and ethos of the Everybody's Golf series, Hot Shots Tennis crams extra fun into every corner with a variety of gameplay modes for all occasions. Comprehensive training options allow you to get the very best out of your character, but it's possible to head straight onto the court and get some brilliant rallies going if that's what you want. Try the Challenge mode and take your player to the very top, or invite your friends and family to take part in an epic multiplayer match. However you play, Everybody is sure to have some fun.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Hot Shots Tennis - Get a Grip (USA) (PSP) (PSN).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Hot Shots Tennis - Get a Grip (USA) (PSP) (PSN).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hot Shots Tennis - Get a Grip (USA) (PSP) (PSN).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Indiana Jones and the Staff of Kings (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Indiana Jones and the Staff of Kings</name>
		<desc>Indiana Jones and the Staff of Kings is a historical fantasy video game published by LucasArts for the Wii, Nintendo DS, PlayStation 2, and PlayStation Portable. The game is the third in the series of original 3D Indiana Jones games, preceded by Indiana Jones and the Emperor's Tomb, and Indiana Jones and the Infernal Machine. The Wii version also includes Indiana Jones and the Fate of Atlantis video game as an unlockable.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Indiana Jones and the Staff of Kings (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Indiana Jones and the Staff of Kings (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Indiana Jones and the Staff of Kings (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20090619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amaze Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jak and Daxter - The Lost Frontier (USA) (PSN).cso</path>
		<name>Jak and Daxter : The Lost Frontier</name>
		<desc>The dynamic duo Jak and Daxter are back in an all-new adventure on PSP that picks up the action where the previous trilogy left off. Whether battling Sky Pirates in a customizable aircraft or blasting Aeropeans with the punishing Gunstaff weapon, Jak and Daxter's journey will take them beyond the edge of the Brink – and into a war bigger than they ever could have imagined.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Jak and Daxter - The Lost Frontier (USA) (PSN).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Jak and Daxter - The Lost Frontier (USA) (PSN).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jak and Daxter - The Lost Frontier (USA) (PSN).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20091103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>High Impact Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Marvel Ultimate Alliance 2.cso</path>
		<name>Marvel : Ultimate Alliance 2</name>
		<desc>Marvel Ultimate Alliance 2 continues the four-player mayhem of the previous Marvel Ultimate Alliance and, before that, the X-Men Legends series It is based on the Secret War and Civil War storylines from the comics. After Nick Fury leads an unauthorized super-hero assault on Latveria and a fight gone wrong kills hundreds of civilians in Connecticut, the government passes the super-human registration act, which requires all super-powered individuals to reveal their identities to the government. At one point in the story, you have to choose the pro or anti registration side and certain heroes will always be on one side or another, locking them out if you choose the other path. The game after this point changes depending on the storyline you choose.  You start with a handful of characters and can unlock more by completing bonus simulator missions, which will give you a special task like blowing up cars. There are four heroes active at all times during the game, unless they get knocked out. Each character has a health meter and a stamina meter. You can use SHIELD access points, usually at the beginning and middle of each level, to switch out characters. The stamina meter recharges on its own and controls use of powers. Each hero has a jump (which can also be used to double-jump, fly or web-swing, depending on the character), grab, quick strike and powerful strike. These can be used in combination to do things like jumping attacks, pick up an enemy, then punch them, etc. Combining these with a modifier button allows you to use powers. Each hero has a wide variety of powers. Leveling up gives you points to spend on improving the powers. You can re-assign the points and change which powers are active at any time.  Defeating enemies and smashing environment items gives you health refills and points that can be spent upgrading statistics for each hero. There are also items that you can carry that will give stat bonuses like increased HP or a bonus to a specific type of damage.  The big change over the previous game is the addition of fusions, which are two-character team-up attacks. This is controlled by a meter of four stars. You fill this by defeating enemies or finding an item that instantly fills the whole meter. You can spend one star to revive a fallen teammate or all four to perform a fusion attack. Any possible combination of two characters has their own unique fusion. There are three basic types:  There are targeted fusions, like having Things throw Mr. Fantastic at someone. These do high damage to a single target and are good for using on bosses. There are also clearing fusions, like having Storm bounce her lighting off Wolverine. These damage all enemies in a given radius. Clearing fusions are good for clearing out a clump of enemies. Finally, there are guided fusions, like Iceman and Human Torch shooting their powers at each other, then running around mowing down anyone who gets between them. These are good for clearing out scattered enemies.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Marvel Ultimate Alliance 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Marvel Ultimate Alliance 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Marvel Ultimate Alliance 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20091113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SOCOM - U.S. Navy SEALs - Tactical Strike (USA).cso</path>
		<name>SOCOM : U.S. Navy SEALs, Fireteam Bravo</name>
		<desc>SOCOM: U.S. Navy SEALs Fireteam Bravo is the first SOCOM game for the PSP from Zipper Interactive. The game supports up to 16 players at a time, voice chat, and a variety of modes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/SOCOM - U.S. Navy SEALs - Tactical Strike (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/SOCOM - U.S. Navy SEALs - Tactical Strike (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/SOCOM - U.S. Navy SEALs - Tactical Strike (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zipper Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Invaders Evolution.cso</path>
		<name>Space Invaders Evolution</name>
		<desc>Space Invaders makes a return to the gaming scene with both old and new versions of the classic arcade experience. A classic mode includes the original color game and a port of the 1978 match-up mode. While playing the screen can be rotated 90 degrees to have two players compete on a single PSP. It also future a wireless mode with support of up to four players.  In the new Future Mode the game takes place in 13 stages from Pluto to Earth in full 3D. You have to shoot down the mothership, which spawns small invaders over time. This mode supports three viewpoints. In addition to the normal shots there is also Beat Attack accessed by triangle button. If you time your shots with the music using Beat Attack, they will become more powerful. You can also wipe out all aliens on the screen by holding down the triangle button until the fourth beat and then letting go.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Space Invaders Evolution.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Space Invaders Evolution.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Space Invaders Evolution.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20061013T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Battlefront II (USA) (v1.01).cso</path>
		<name>Star Wars : Battlefront II</name>
		<desc>A second helping of Battlefront provides all the same multiplayer action with an added level of spice, and plenty of new content.    Along with an updated assortment of multiplayer maps based upon the Star Wars Saga, including Episode III: Revenge of the Sith, you now have the opportunity to fight as some of the greatest heroes, including the Skywalker family, Darth Vader, Yoda, The Emperor himself and Princess Leia, among others. An expanded single player campaign has you fighting as Vader's 501st Legion of troops, fighting in the Clone Wars as the undercurrent of evil, soon to be known as the Empire, takes its place in the Galaxy.    Now you can also take to the stars in specially developed multiplayer levels where your skill in an X-Wing or TIE-Fighter come to the fore. Defeat enemy ships and destroy the heavy cruisers and capital ships to achieve victory, or land within enemy territory and blow up a Star Destroyer from the inside.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - Battlefront II (USA) (v1.01).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - Battlefront II (USA) (v1.01).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - Battlefront II (USA) (v1.01).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pandemic Studios</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Lethal Alliance (EU).cso</path>
		<name>Star Wars : Lethal Alliance</name>
		<desc>To capture the plans for the Death Star and make it back home safely, players must guide Rianna Saren and her trusty droid Zeeo through a variety of Star Wars environments while avoiding or attacking Imperial soldiers and their allies. Rianna is gifted in combat and Zeeo comes in handy for unlocking security doors, reaching high places, and bypassing dangerous areas. The story of Star Wars: Lethal Alliance unfolds between Episode III and Episode IV, when Princess Leia recruits the duo to steal the plans so the Rebels may learn any weaknesses in the massive weapon. Players will explore such areas as Tatooine, Despayre, Alderaan, and Danuta while interacting with characters including Boba Fett, Darth Vader, and Kyle Katarn. The PSP features various mini-games and multiplayer Twil'lek vs. Twi'lek combat over a wireless network.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - Lethal Alliance (EU).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - Lethal Alliance (EU).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - Lethal Alliance (EU).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20061207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars Battlefront - Renegade Squadron (EU).cso</path>
		<name>Star Wars Battlefront : Renegade Squadron</name>
		<desc>Star Wars Battlefront: Renegade Squadron is an all-new project in the Battlefront saga exclusively for the PlayStation Portable, designed to offer an all-new storyline in the single-player mode and extremely robust PSP multiplayer options.    The story in this game follow the previously secret "Renegade Squadron" that was made up of the galaxy's toughest scoundrels. As the plot unfolds, players will learn how Han Solo recruited and assembled his team and used their many talents for missions in Korriban's Valley of the Sith, the rocky remains of Alderaan, and the fiery ashes of the volcanic planet, Sullust. In addition to single-player story missions, Renegade Squadron allows up to 16 players to compete via Infrastructure mode (eight-person support for ad hoc), with a special 100-point spending system to purchase custom kits with more than a million different combinations that can be used to create unique Star Wars characters.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars Battlefront - Renegade Squadron (EU).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars Battlefront - Renegade Squadron (EU).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars Battlefront - Renegade Squadron (EU).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20071012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<players>1-16</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Syphon Filter - Dark Mirror (EU).cso</path>
		<name>Syphon Filter : Dark Mirror</name>
		<desc>Assume the role of Gabe Logan, a highly-trained Precision Strike Operative, commanding a black box United States Agency that legally doesn't exist. Gabe finds himself dealing with a beautiful woman from his past who harbors a shocking secret while he battles the Red Section, a para-military group in possession of Project Dark Mirror, a next-generation weapon of mass destruction. Using Precision Strike Tactics, advanced vision technology, and the latest in high-tech weaponry, Logan and his team perform surgical strike missions - too sensitive for a military response, too dangerous for civilian intelligence forces. Through the role of Gabe, players will have to be quick to strategize, as he is responsible to infiltrate, recon and execute decisively. Once inserted, Logan is his own authority - he must make life and death decisions, quickly choosing which course of action to take.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Syphon Filter - Dark Mirror (EU).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Syphon Filter - Dark Mirror (EU).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Syphon Filter - Dark Mirror (EU).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Red Star (USA).cso</path>
		<name>The Red Star</name>
		<desc>This game is a mix of different types of games. It has been described as a fighting, action, and shooter game rolled into one. RPG elements are also apparent as players have the option of upgrading certain attributes of a character depending on how well levels are completed.  This story is based on The Red Star graphic novel, set in a futuristic, magic-using Soviet Union, which uses floating Skyfurnaces (gigantic magical ships, reminiscent of all-metal blimps) and Warkasters (sorcerers) to conquer its enemies.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The Red Star (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/The Red Star (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The Red Star (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20110105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>XS Games</developer>
		<publisher>XS Games</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up-Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The_Warriors.cso</path>
		<name>The Warriors</name>
		<desc>Based on the 1979 Paramount Pictures film of the same name and voiced by most of the original cast, The Warriors follows the career of a Coney Island street gang.  Starting months before the events of the film, The Warriors expand and defend their Coney Island turf, while proving that they are heavy enough players to join The Riffs’ network.  With a citywide rep, they can get invited to a major gang meeting where the future of New York street crime will be decided.    The game follows the nine lead members of The Warriors (with flashback missions showing how they came to The Warriors): leader Cleon, Swan, Ajax, Cowboy, Cochise, Snow, Fox, Rembrandt, and Vermin.  During the game, the player will control each member, usually acting as a war chief and leading a squad of Warriors on a mission.  Missions vary from simply wrecking another crew to completing a series of objectives while avoiding arrest or worse.   During missions, players can mug pedestrians, steal car radios, commit smash and grabs, tag walls or bomb other gangs’ burners, and load up on flash.  Between each story based mission, The Warriors return to their Coney Island hangout where they can train to improve their stats, go out on patrol, review their accomplishments, replay levels, or enter into a series of quick-play combat matches.    The game plays like a squad-based brawler.  Each Warrior has his own fighting style and much of the game environment can be weaponized.  Fights are fast and often brutal, but stealth is also an option.  Players can perform stealthy finishing moves and distract police or other gang members with thrown bottles.  The game’s environments are fully 3D allowing Warriors to escape along the rooftops, hop over fences, or dash into shadowy areas.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/The_Warriors.png</image>
		<video>./snap/The_Warriors.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/The_Warriors.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20070223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Games</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TMNT - Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).cso</path>
		<name>TMNT : Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</name>
		<desc>The new Ninja Turtles video game uses the same dark and dangerous environments and adventurous themes featured in the new Ninja Turtles CGI film being developed by Imagi Animation Studios and Mirage Licensing. The Ninja Turtles movie takes place in a New York City plagued by secretive villains and strange, otherworldly creatures. Faced with these perils, the Turtles will experience their most trying time as heroes and as a family, as Raphael, Donatello and Michelangelo lose their focus and struggle to maintain their unity and ninja discipline.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/TMNT - Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
		<video>./snap/TMNT - Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/TMNT - Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.25</rating>
		<releasedate>20070322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tokobot.cso</path>
		<name>Tokobot</name>
		<desc>Tokobot is a puzzle-solving game in which the player takes control of Bolt, a 16-year girl who has been sent to a set of ancient ruins to decipher its clues in order to save the world.  However, Bolt is not alone. She gets help from the Tokobots, a bunch a mechanized men who help Bolt out by forming certain objects such as bridges and ladders to avoid pitfalls and help move objects as well.  The gameplay is similar to Pikmin for the Gamecube, the player controls the Tokobots by highlighting them and sending them to certain areas and complete certain tasks.  The game will start you out with six, but as the levels progress, more Tokobots will be available, the more that can be obtained, the more bigger and powerful machines that can be used.  Likewise, the puzzles get harder as the game progresses as well.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tokobot.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tokobot.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tokobot.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20060407T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game-Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toy Story 3.cso</path>
		<name>Toy Story 3</name>
		<desc>UNLEASH your IMAGINATION    Story Mode: Dive into heroic adventures from the Toy Story 3 movie    Exciting Mini-Adventures: Help Buzz battle Zurg or team up with Sheriff Woody to protect his town!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Toy Story 3.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Toy Story 3.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Toy Story 3.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20100615T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Asobo Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Disney</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Transformers.cso</path>
		<name>Transformers : Le Jeu</name>
		<desc>Transformers: The Game is the name of multiple versions of a video game based on the 2007 live action film Transformers, all of which were released in North America in June 2007. Home console and PC versions were developed by Traveller's Tales for the PlayStation 2, Xbox 360, Wii, PlayStation 3 and PC. A different PlayStation Portable version was developed by Savage Entertainment.    Transformers Autobots and Transformers Decepticons are the Nintendo DS versions of Transfomers: The Game. Vicarious Visions, who was tasked with bringing the adaptation to the Nintendo DS, chose to adapt the DS version into two separate games.[1] Autobots follows the heroes' perspective while Decepticons follows the villains'. Unlike games with multiple SKUs such as PokÃ©mon which feature only minor differences between versions, these are two separate games, sharing some basic similarities, but with unique characters, missions and locations.[2]</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Transformers.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Transformers.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Transformers.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20070619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Savage Entertainment</publisher>
		<players>2-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./UFC Undisputed 2010 (USA).cso</path>
		<name>UFC Undisputed 2010</name>
		<desc>UFC Undisputed 2010 is action-packed fighting game for PlayStation Portable that puts the excitement and intensity of the real-life Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC) in the palm of your hand. The game features all aspects of the UFC experience, including a large roster of UFC fighters, a wide range of fighting styleâ€”including new additions Sambo, Karate and Greco-Roman Wrestlingâ€”authentic environments and commentary, and a variety of play modes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/UFC Undisputed 2010 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/UFC Undisputed 2010 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/UFC Undisputed 2010 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20100910T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yuke's Media Creation</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Untold Legends - The Warrior's Code (USA) (PSN).cso</path>
		<name>Untold Legends : The Warrior's Code</name>
		<desc>While struggling to evade capture and death in the war-ravaged wilderness, some of these shape-shifter refugees stumble upon a carefully guarded and stunning secret that rekindles hope for freedom and peace to the realm. Can these refugees-turned-heroes bring the last surviving heir of the dynasty to the capital city or will they lead him to the warlord's hand, dooming their race into extinction and their human cousins to endless oppression and strife?</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Untold Legends - The Warrior's Code (USA) (PSN).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Untold Legends - The Warrior's Code (USA) (PSN).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Untold Legends - The Warrior's Code (USA) (PSN).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20060328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wipeout Pure.cso</path>
		<name>WipEout Pure</name>
		<desc>WipEout Pure is the first adaptation for the PSP of the long-running Wipeout series. Players take part in a futuristic racing league known as the FX300 Racing League and control a fast hovercrafts on tight, cornering tracks, vying for first place in one of many tournaments. There are ten anti-gravity vehicles available to use (two need to be unlocked), each with their own characteristics in speed, handling and acceleration. Vehicles are further divided into classes that are unlocked gradually. In later classes most of the vehicles become much faster and require more precise steering at fast speeds. In the same vein, players can unlock new tournaments.  There are a total of sixteen tracks to race on: twelve designed from the ground up for the PSP, as well as four classic Wipeout tracks. Each track has its own obstacles, as well as weapon pick-ups (both offensive and defensive) and speed boosters. The different game modes include single races, tournaments of sets of races, time trial and zone races. In the zone races the player goes through a number of increasingly difficult zones on his own without the ability to slow down until the vehicle explodes because of collision damage. New game elements are unlocked through the Tournament mode.  The game features wireless play over ad-hoc mode (PSP-to-PSP). It was also the first PSP game to support downloadable content with extra teams, tracks and PSP skins. Some of these packs are only available for specific regional versions. The European version of the game supports game sharing.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Wipeout Pure.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Wipeout Pure.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Wipeout Pure.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20050316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Studio Liverpool</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World Poker Tour.cso</path>
		<name>World Poker Tour</name>
		<desc>Poker tournament game with six tour-exclusive casinos to choose from. Possibility to create custom poker games with editor or choose from 15 different community poker game types. You can either play against 1000 different AI characters or go on-line and battle other players.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/World Poker Tour.png</image>
		<video>./snap/World Poker Tour.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/World Poker Tour.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20060602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>2K Games</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./X-Men Legends II - Rise of Apocalypse (USA).cso</path>
		<name>X-Men Legends II : Rise of Apocalypse</name>
		<desc>X-Men Legends II: Rise of Apocalypse is an action role-playing game developed primarily by Raven Software and published by Activision. It is the follow up to 2004's X-Men Legends. It was first released in September 2005 for the GameCube, Microsoft Windows, N-Gage, PlayStation 2, PlayStation Portable and Xbox video game platforms. It is set after the events of X-Men Legends and features the mutant supervillain Apocalypse as the primary antagonist.    The developers intended the game to have a greater sense of scale than its predecessor, and writers created a story where the villains known as the Brotherhood of Mutants would need to ally themselves with the heroic X-Men to defeat a greater threat. High quality cinematics were created by Blur Studio. Online multiplayer was also added.    The game was well received by gaming critics on all platforms. Critics felt that the inclusion of online play, additional mutant powers, and a larger cast made the game an improvement over its predecessor. Some reviewers were critical of the game's voice acting and felt that the gameplay was repetitive. It sold enough copies to be added to the budget line known as PlayStation 2's Greatest Hits.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/X-Men Legends II - Rise of Apocalypse (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/X-Men Legends II - Rise of Apocalypse (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/X-Men Legends II - Rise of Apocalypse (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./After Burner - Black Falcon (EUR).cso</path>
		<name>After Burner : Black Falcon</name>
		<desc>The first arcade-style flight combat title exclusively for the PSP system, combining intensive air combat with a multitude of explosions that allow gamers to relive the experience of the classic After Burner arcade game. In addition to the in-depth customization of 19 officially licensed military planes, gamers can compete against friends via ad-hoc in a variety of multiplayer modes, and for the first time ever, fly solo in a story-rich single-player campaign.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/After Burner - Black Falcon (EUR).png</image>
		<video>./snap/After Burner - Black Falcon (EUR).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/After Burner - Black Falcon (EUR).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20070320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Planet Moon</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NPUG80251/</path>
		<name>Pinball Heroes(DLC - DO NOT DELETE)</name>
		<desc>DLC only, needed for Pinball Heroes</desc>
	</game>
	<folder>
		<path>./NPUG80251</path>
		<name>NPUG80251</name>
		<sortname>PINBALL HEROE's DLC ONLY - DO NOT DELETE</sortname>
		<desc>PINBALL HEROE's DLC ONLY - DO NOT DELETE
Needed for Pinball Hero's to play all tables.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<hidden>true</hidden>
	</folder>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - The Force Unleashed.cso</path>
		<name>Star Wars : The Force Unleashed</name>
		<desc>Star Wars: The Force Unleashed is a LucasArts action-adventure video game and part of the The Force Unleashed project. It was initially developed for the PlayStation 2, PlayStation 3, Wii, and Xbox 360 consoles and on the iOS, second-generation N-Gage, Nintendo DS, PlayStation Portable, and Java-equipped mobile phone handhelds.    The game was released in North America on September 16, 2008, in Australia and Southeast Asia on September 17, and in Europe on September 19. LucasArts released downloadable content for the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 consoles. An Ultimate Sith Edition of the game, containing new and all previously released expanded content, was released in November 2009, which also came out on Mac OS and Microsoft Windows.    The project bridges the first two Star Wars trilogies, acting as an origin story for both the united Rebel Alliance and the Galactic Civil War depicted in the Original Trilogy. The game introduces a new protagonist, "Starkiller", as Darth Vader's secret apprentice, who is tasked with hunting down Jedi while killing rebels and Imperials alike in order to hide his existence from the Emperor, but soon starts to slowly redeem himself to the light side of the Force.    Reviews offered fairly positive response, praising The Force Unleashed for its compelling story, robust physics, impressive art and soundtrack, while some more negative reviews cited frustrating gameplay. Despite this, the game was a bestseller in the United States and Australia, with over one million copies sold its debut month. As of February 2010, the game has sold over seven million copies, and it is the fastest-selling Star Wars video game. A sequel, Star Wars: The Force Unleashed II, was released in October 2010.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - The Force Unleashed.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - The Force Unleashed.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - The Force Unleashed.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ratchet and Clank Size Matters.cso</path>
		<name>Ratchet &amp; Clank - Size Matters</name>
		<desc>Ratchet &amp; Clank: Size Matters (known as Ratchet &amp; Clank 5 in Japan) is a 2007 platformer video game developed by High Impact Games and published by Sony Computer Entertainment for the PlayStation Portable and PlayStation 2. The game is the first Ratchet &amp; Clank title on the PSP handheld. Development company High Impact Games was spawned from the original Ratchet &amp; Clank developer, Insomniac Games. The story is about Ratchet and Clank as they are interrupted from their vacation to search for a kidnapped girl and encounter a forgotten race known as the Technomites</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ratchet and Clank Size Matters.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ratchet and Clank Size Matters.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ratchet and Clank Size Matters.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070516T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Impact Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pac-man World 3.cso</path>
		<name>Pac Man World 3</name>
		<desc>Pac-Man is teleported by Orson through 14 different levels to fight Erwin, his army of robots, monsters and Spectral Entities to save the world, Pac-Land and the Spectral Realm. Erwin plans to siphon spectral energy from the Spectral Realm to power his army of robots in order to rule the world. Pac-Man uses punching, Rev Rolls, Butt-Bouncing and various new Power Pellets to defeat Erwin and his minions. Pac-Man also pilots Toc-Man in a battle against Erwin’s robot army.  Joined by Pac-Man’s old enemies, Orson, Clyde and Pinky, and new friends along the way, Pac-Man adventures through different levels from a boneyard of old bots to a burning tower, up mountains, through deserts and the Spectral Realm to destroy all of Erwin’s Spectral Syphons. In this title, Pac-Man has also been given full speech, voiced by Martin T. Sherman.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pac-man World 3.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pac-man World 3.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pac-man World 3.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20060526T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blitz Games</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ridge Racer 2.cso</path>
		<name>Ridge Racer 2</name>
		<desc>Ridge Racer 2 is not so much a sequel to the early PlayStation Portable title Ridge Racer, but rather an update of the existing game that features several enhancements and a lot of new content. Released about a year after its predecessor, the changes and additions in Ridge Racer 2 include:  1. A new opening and ending CGI movie. 2. Many new tracks and songs from previous Ridge Racer games. 3. New SPECIAL class cars to challenge in duels and win.   Survival mode: In a four car race, after each round, the car to be in last place is eliminated from the pack. 4. Duel mode: A race against a single AI car. 5. Single Race mode has been replaced with an Arcade mode in which the player races not only against the pack of 11 cars but also has to reach checkpoints on the track to stay in the game. The options menu features a new setting to adjust the difficulty of Arcade mode.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ridge Racer 2.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ridge Racer 2.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ridge Racer 2.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20061018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twisted Metal Head On.cso</path>
		<name>Twisted Metal : Head On</name>
		<desc>Get ready for the next installment in the Twisted Metal car combat series. Twisted Metal: Head-On puts you behind the wheel of one of 14 destructive vehicles, each equipped with machine guns, turbo boost, and a unique special attack. Once you select a vehicle, you can take out your road rage on opponents in 12 wild arenas. The game also offers multiplayer modes for up to eight players through a wireless connection.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Twisted Metal Head On.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Twisted Metal Head On.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Twisted Metal Head On.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Incognito Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sid Meiers Pirates.cso</path>
		<name>Sid Meier's Pirates!</name>
		<desc>Sid Meier's Pirates! for the PSP is a mix between the PC and Xbox version that were released two and three years earlier, respectively. As a straight port, not much has changed except for three really notable elements.  First, the dancing sequences have been tweaked slightly. Now it is up to your twitch/reaction time to get the job done right, as opposed to being able to simply watch the govenor's daughter's hand motions and body language.  The second tweak is the addition of being able to physically hunt for treasure. In the previous versions, you would find a map, sail to the right spot and land. If you had the location right, you would have your booty. Not so in this version. Now you take four of your crewman ashore and have to find the red "X". All while avoiding booby-traps and vicious jaguars. If you lose your crew, it's back to the ship. If you make it to the "X", then it is time to start raking in the doubloons.  The third change has been made to the sneaking segments. If you want to sneak into a port, it is handled in the exact same way; creeping through the streets, slipping past guards, hiding behind fences and so on. However, your character now moves in a grid, as opposed to being able to move a bit more freely. This does not change the gameplay, but it is possible to accidentally step into a guard's line of sight because you cannot stop moving forward until your character reached the middle of the next tile.  Next to the original game content, the PSP version adds bonus treasure missions, with more plunder and new locations. The game has been tweaked for widescreen display. Multiplayer is supported for up to 4 players, through Wi-Fi, Ad Hoc.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sid Meiers Pirates.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sid Meiers Pirates.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sid Meiers Pirates.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20070309T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Full Fat</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure-Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Angus Hates Aliens (Europe).cso</path>
		<name>Angus Hates Aliens</name>
		<image>./mixart/Angus Hates Aliens (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Angus Hates Aliens (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Angus Hates Aliens (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20150610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Stendec</developer>
		<publisher>Team Stendec</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soul Calibur Broken Destiny (EUR).cso</path>
		<name>Soulcalibur : Broken Destiny</name>
		<image>./mixart/Soul Calibur Broken Destiny (EUR).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Soul Calibur Broken Destiny (EUR).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Soul Calibur Broken Destiny (EUR).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20090702T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania Dracula X Chronicles (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Castlevania : The Dracula X Chronicles</name>
		<desc>Count Dracula has returned and captured the young woman close to the famous vampire hunter, Richter Belmont. Will Richter be able to defeat Dracula and rescue his girlfriend in this new 3D adventure for PSP?</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Castlevania Dracula X Chronicles (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Castlevania Dracula X Chronicles (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Castlevania Dracula X Chronicles (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20071023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resistance Retribution.cso</path>
		<name>Resistance : Retribution</name>
		<desc>Set in the weeks after Resistance: Fall of Man, Resistance: Retribution follows the story of former British Marine James Grayson. After a personal tragedy - he is forced to kill his own brother inside a Chimeran conversion center - Grayson goes on a vendetta to destroy every conversion center he can find. Eventually Grayson learns that his efforts have been futile... in Western Europe the Chimera have evolved a new method of converting humans to aliens. The European resistance - the Maquis - enlist Grayson's help, and he joins Cartwright and Parker in Operation Overstrike. The war to retake the European continent has begun.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Resistance Retribution.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Resistance Retribution.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Resistance Retribution.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20090317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ridge Racer.cso</path>
		<name>Ridge Racer</name>
		<desc>Ridge Racer is about speed and cool power sliding. The game features a nice selection of 24 tracks, 58 cars and music from all previous RR-games and in all aspects is faithful to the series' spirit. There are many game modes in the game, like a world tour-mode where player competes on the courses in order to earn new cars and tracks, Time Attack where one races around the tracks against time and also a multiplayer mode, which supports the ad-hoc, meaning that up to eight players can race against each other with only one game disc, with one player hosting, and others joining.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ridge Racer.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ridge Racer.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ridge Racer.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hot Shots Golf Open Tee.cso</path>
		<name>Hot Shots Golf : Open Tee</name>
		<desc>Go golf crazy and take on a cast of colourful characters in the coolest clubhouse around. No need for airs and graces here - just select a golfer from a range of friendly faces, and customize their abilities, attributes and appearance before teeing off across a series of challenging courses and game modes. Go head-to-head with both friends and foes via WiFi compatible Ad Hoc Mode and become a true golfing legend.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Hot Shots Golf Open Tee.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Hot Shots Golf Open Tee.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Hot Shots Golf Open Tee.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20050503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Clap Hanz</developer>
		<publisher>Clap Hanz</publisher>
		<genre>Sports-Sports / Golf</genre>
		<players>8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Slug XX (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Metal Slug XX</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug XX is an entry in the long-running series of side-scrolling shooters. It is a revised version of Metal Slug 7. The Peregrine Falcons, Marco, Eri, Clark, Tarma, Fio and Ralf, are once again running-and-gunning in colorfully hand-drawn levels, throwing grenades, driving vehicles and slashing enemies.    Metal Slug XX includes various single-player features in the form of a Combat School that lets players return to previously completed missions while executing various objectives; a POW List that shows how many POWs were rescued in each level; and single-player Rankings. Players can also cooperate in Ad-Hoc while gunning down hordes of humorous foes using familiar weapons in seven distinct levels that will see our heroes traverse deserts, mountains, caves and lava pits to finally put an end to their longtime enemy.    This revised version includes additional content including co-op multiplayer and downloadable content, as well as the character Leona Heidern.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Metal Slug XX (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Metal Slug XX (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Metal Slug XX (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20100223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DHM Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up-Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Tennis 3 (EUR).cso</path>
		<name>Virtua Tennis 3</name>
		<desc>Virtua Tennis 3 features 20 international tennis stars like Roger Federer, Lindsay Davenport or Maria Sharapova against which you need to compete in the heart of the game: The World Tour. You create your own character and play to reach the number one rank on the world ranking list.  Virtua Tennis 3 is not a simulation like Top Spin 2 and only needs three buttons to perform all possible shot. Still time needs to be invested in training the character through several mini-games in which need you to hit a circle on the other side of the net or defeat aliens by hitting them with returns.  You can also play as one of the professionals against the CPU or a friend (or two if you play a Double). True to the series of the home version, there are also 12 mini-games available to play against your friends. These include the ones from the World Tour training as well as different ones like Curling or Super-Bingo. The Tournament Mode and Exhibition Mode are also present in the arcade version, but the Challenge Mode has been replaced by the World Tour Mode and Party Mode.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Virtua Tennis 3 (EUR).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Virtua Tennis 3 (EUR).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Virtua Tennis 3 (EUR).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20070323T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghostbusters - The Video Game (EU).cso</path>
		<name>Ghostbusters : The Video Game</name>
		<desc>The game follows the player's character as a new recruit in the Ghostbusters, a team of parapsychologists who pursue and capture ghosts. The game features elements of typical third-person shooters, but instead of using a traditional gun, players are equipped with a "Proton Pack", a laser beam-like weapon, and a ghost trap to fight and capture ghosts.  The game's plot is set two years after Ghostbusters II, around Thanksgiving in 1991, with the Ghostbusters team training the player's character while investigating paranormal activities in New York City.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ghostbusters - The Video Game (EU).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ghostbusters - The Video Game (EU).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ghostbusters - The Video Game (EU).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20091111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Fly Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rocky Balboa.cso</path>
		<name>Rocky Balboa</name>
		<desc>Rocky Balboa is a 2007 video game based on the movie of the same name for the PlayStation Portable, which is similar in style and content to Rocky Legends. The game includes footage from each Rocky film, showing the buildup to the major fights of the film series. There are also some flashback videos of the training footage from the films (this is used in the Mickey's Corner section of the game, which is a tutorial aimed to teach new players how to play).</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rocky Balboa.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rocky Balboa.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rocky Balboa.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Fiction</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Unbound Saga.cso</path>
		<name>Unbound Saga</name>
		<desc>Unbound Saga is a 3D scrolling fighting game. It's story is based on the upcoming comic book series of the same name.  The player tales the role of either Rick Ajax or Lori Machete, fighting through the wasteland known as Toxopolis. The primary aim is to reach the player's nemesis, The Maker. Each of the two characters has its own special abilities that are needed during the quest.  The overall gameplay consists of the player fighting his way through different levels, which are split into comic strips. There are some puzzles, as well, that must be solved in order to progress.   The story of the game is split into chapters, of which the most important feature final bosses. The in-game dialogues are triggered automatically and all of them are considered to be important to the main quest. Each chapter features an outro, except for the first one, which also features the intro of the game. Players will also be able to try out their skills in the Survival Mode which is available from the start and does not need unlocking.  The game is only available through the PlayStation Network by digital download.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Unbound Saga.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Unbound Saga.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Unbound Saga.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20090716T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vogster Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Vogster Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./God of War - Ghost of Sparta.cso</path>
		<name>God of War : Ghost of Sparta</name>
		<desc>Set in the realm of Greek mythology, God of War: Ghost of Sparta is a single-player game that allows players to take on the powerful role of Spartan warrior Kratos. This new adventure picks up after God of War concludes, telling the story of Kratos' ascension to power as the God of War. In his quest to rid himself of the nightmares that haunt him, Kratos must embark on a journey that will reveal the origins of lost worlds, and finally answer long-awaited questions about his dark past. Armed with the deadly chained Blades of Chaos, he will have to overcome armies of mythological monsters, legions of undead soldiers, and amazingly dangerous and brutal landscapes throughout his merciless quest.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/God of War - Ghost of Sparta.png</image>
		<video>./snap/God of War - Ghost of Sparta.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/God of War - Ghost of Sparta.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20101103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ready At Dawn Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SEGA RALLY Revo.cso</path>
		<name>Sega Rally Revo</name>
		<desc>With dynamically deformable terrain, proprietary next-generation graphics, realistic physics, and competitive bumper-to-bumper racing, Sega Rally Revo is a high-tempo driving experience that is every racing fan's driving fantasy. Vehicle selection affects driving strategy in Sega Rally Revo, as race course surfaces dynamically deform upon repeated contact with vehicle tires and changing weather effects. Sega Rally Revo features a variety of fully deformable surfaces, from gravel-littered tracks and smooth tarmac roads, to snow-covered mountain passes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/SEGA RALLY Revo.png</image>
		<video>./snap/SEGA RALLY Revo.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/SEGA RALLY Revo.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20070928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bugbear Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultimate Ghosts 'n Goblins (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Ultimate Ghosts 'n Goblins</name>
		<desc>Once again, the brave knight Arthur is called into action to face the Dark Lord in order to rescue the princess.  The fourth title in the series, Arthur must make numerous ghouls and monsters on his quest to save Princess Prin Prin before her life is taken by the newest Dark Lord's evil plan.  Possessing the familiar moves that Arthur is known for, he must go throughout numerous levels in this latest 2D quest with new 3D rendered elements.  New abilities and upgrades allow Arthur a new set of moves to face this difficult platformer, and Warp Keys allow Arthur to go back and revisit completed worlds in order to find more secrets and weapons.  Ever present are the classic cast of zombies, the shape-changing magicians, and the infamous Red Devil.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Ultimate Ghosts 'n Goblins (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Ultimate Ghosts 'n Goblins (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Ultimate Ghosts 'n Goblins (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./God of War - Chains of Olympis.cso</path>
		<name>God of War : Chains of Olympus</name>
		<desc>Unleash the power of the Gods and embark on a merciless quest as Kratos, an ex-Spartan warrior driven to destroy Ares, the God of War. Armed with lethal double chainblades, Kratos must carve through mythology's darkest creatures including Medusa, Cyclops, the Hydra and more, while solving intricate puzzles in breathtaking environments. Driven by pure revenge, nothing can stop Kratos from achieving absolution.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/God of War - Chains of Olympis.png</image>
		<video>./snap/God of War - Chains of Olympis.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/God of War - Chains of Olympis.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20080304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ready At Dawn Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./300.cso</path>
		<name>300 : March to Glory</name>
		<desc>In the action packed 300: March to Glory, players take on the role of King Leonidas, who leads the brave 300 Spartans against Xerxes and his massive Persian army. The player, as Leonidas, uses his sword, spear and shield and the power of the soldiers in a battle to determine the very fate of western civilization. 300: March to Glory is a visceral experience focused on action and combat, allowing the player to fight both solo and in a phalanx alongside his fellow Spartans</desc>
		<image>./mixart/300.png</image>
		<video>./snap/300.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/300.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20070330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Collision Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Brothers</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Tactics - The War Of The Lions.cso</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Tactics : The War of the Lions</name>
		<desc>Enter a time where the land Ivalice has been divided by the War of the Lions. Play as either Delital Heiral, the hero who stopped the war, or Ramza Beoulve, whose role remains a mystery. These two characters help you to unlock and discover the history of the war and Ivalice.    Witness the origin of the Ivalice Alliance, a series of titles that take place in the same world as Final Fantasy XII and Final Fantasy XII: Revenant Wings. Animated sequences combine hand-drawn style visuals with computer graphics. Enhanced widescreen presentation, new jobs and new characters.  Challenge friends in head-to-head battles with the multiplayer function or team up in the co-operative mode and try to outwit the game's computer opponents. Introduction of the Onion Knight and Dark Knight classes.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Final Fantasy Tactics - The War Of The Lions.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Final Fantasy Tactics - The War Of The Lions.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Final Fantasy Tactics - The War Of The Lions.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20071010T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gretzky NHL 06 (US).cso</path>
		<name>Gretzky NHL 06</name>
		<desc>Gretzky NHL 06 for PSP is a hockey game endorsed by legendary player Wayne Gretzky. Released only six months after the previous PSP game, this version comes with updated rosters and several features taken from the PS2 version, but has its own selection of modes.    Returning modes include single games and a full season. The new chemistry feature makes its way over from the PS2, influencing players' stats depending on how well they interact with each other. Also seen on the PS2 is the "Wayne vs Wayne" mode, in which the two competing teams build up their "99 meter". When full, The Great One himself joins the team as an extra player for a short time. In addition to single games, this mode can also be played in the PSP-exclusive NHL Showdown mode, which is a ladder against all NHL teams, with the finale against a team of five Gretzkys. Another exclusive mode is called "3 on 3 Countdown". It is an arcade mode, with only three players per team on the field, without any of the regular rules, and the winner being the team that reaches a set score first.    Online multiplayer, both ad hoc and via infrastructure, also return, as do the Gretzky Challenges: by earning points through in-game achievements, players can unlock bonuses like alternate and vintage uniforms and new gameplay features and modes. Unlike the previous PSP game, Gretzky 06 features color and play-by-play commentary by Mike Emrick and Darren Pang.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Gretzky NHL 06 (US).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Gretzky NHL 06 (US).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Gretzky NHL 06 (US).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20051004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>989 Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kingdom Hearts - Birth by Sleep (EU).cso</path>
		<name>Kingdom Hearts : Birth by Sleep</name>
		<desc>The Final Mix gives you more challenges and the chance to hear the English voices. The game is based on the upgraded US version, with more boss battles, game modes and even more mini-games. Think you've already become the ultimate Key Blade Master? Think again.    The game contains secret episodes that you can unlock, and in the single player mode, you'll meet the mysterious man, see what secrets he'll reveal about the powerful Kingdom Hearts. Controls and the D-Link are updated, so its easier to use and you can collect stickers on your journey.    There are 9 more missions for you to clear and new challenging bosses in the multi-mode. These bosses aren't just the lord of the world, they could be the world themselves. Now you can battle the whale that swallowed Pinocchio's ship.    Kingdom Hearts is being born again, pick up your key blade and set off on your journey once again.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Kingdom Hearts - Birth by Sleep (EU).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Kingdom Hearts - Birth by Sleep (EU).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kingdom Hearts - Birth by Sleep (EU).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man Maverick Hunter X.cso</path>
		<name>Mega Man : Maverick Hunter X</name>
		<desc>Set a century after the events in the original Mega Man series, Mega Man Maverick Hunter X is a remake of the original SNES game Mega Man X, and details the story of Dr. Light's greatest creation: X, a robot with free will. Dr. Cain's discovery of X led to the creation of reploids, robots modeled after the design of X. When the maverick virus infects a group of reploids, they band together in a revolt against humanity. The call goes to the maverick hunters, X and Zero, to fight the Mavericks.  The game is a side-scrolling action game where the player controls X as he hunts the maverick reploids. Notable features include the ability to find enhancements to augment X's abilities, and the ability to absorb the powers of the maverick reploids X defeats. The original moves, such as dashes, wall jumps and charge shorts are still present.  The original flat backgrounds have been replaced by polygonal models, and the remake features enhanced explosions and generally more detail. Additionally, animated cutscenes and voice acting have been added. All weapon and armour upgrades have been relocated to new hidden areas, and there is a new mode: Vile, in which you can play the entire game as maverick Vile, with abilities Mega Man does not have. As a bonus, there is a demo of Mega Man Powered Up on the UMD - a remake of the very first Mega Man game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mega Man Maverick Hunter X.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mega Man Maverick Hunter X.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mega Man Maverick Hunter X.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ModNation Racers (EU).cso</path>
		<name>ModNation Racers</name>
		<desc>ModNation Racers is a thoroughly fresh take on classic kart racing that empowers the player to personalize their entire game. Players can express themselves by creating their own Mod character, styling their own racing kart and even building -- in just minutes -- an imaginative racing track. Then race other players online or trade your creations with your friends to expand the ModNation across the globe!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/ModNation Racers (EU).png</image>
		<video>./snap/ModNation Racers (EU).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/ModNation Racers (EU).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20100525T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCE Studios San Diego</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Hunter Portable 3rd HD (Japan).cso</path>
		<name>Monster Hunter Portable 3rd HD (Japan)</name>
		<desc>Monster Hunter Portable 3rd is a game in the Monster Hunter franchise for the PlayStation Portable system that was released in Japan on December 1, 2010. The game was released, as a part of the PlayStation Portable Remaster series, on PlayStation 3.The game introduces new regions, monsters, and a revised Felyne combat system. Monster Hunter Portable 3rd is not an update to Monster Hunter Freedom Unite or Monster Hunter Tri. Monster Hunter Portable 3rd is instead separate to the rest of the series, and most of the game has been entirely remade. However, it is also a successor to Monster Hunter Freedom Unite as the third game in the Portable series.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Monster Hunter Portable 3rd (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Monster Hunter Portable 3rd (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Monster Hunter Portable 3rd (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20100624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>RPG</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat Unchained.cso</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat : Unchained</name>
		<desc>It will konsume you!    An ancient evil has returned from beyond death and threatens the very existence of the realms. Will the Champion of the Elder Gods have the power to defeat this threat borne of deception?    -Features six additional fighters including Kitana, Jax, Frost, Blaze, Goro and Shao Kahn,  -Battle your way to the top in the all-new Endurance Mode.  -Multiple fatalities, hara karis and interactive multi-tiered backrounds including brutal death traps.  -Explore the huge free-roaming adventure in Konquest Mode.  -Engage in Chess and Puzzle Kombat...MK style.  -Fight head-to-head against a friend with Wi-Fi wireless support.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mortal Kombat Unchained.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mortal Kombat Unchained.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mortal Kombat Unchained.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20061115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Outrun 2006 (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Outrun 2006 (USA)</name>
		<image>./mixart/Outrun 2006 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Outrun 2006 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Outrun 2006 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20100203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sumo Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pinball Hall of Fame - The Gottlieb Collection (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Pinball Hall of Fame : The Gottlieb Collection</name>
		<desc>Pinball Hall of Fame: The Gottlieb Collection is another entry in the PHOF budget series. Included in the PS2 version are eight authentic pinball tables, some of the best from the 1970s, 1980s and 1990s. The tables are:  Black Hole and much more...</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pinball Hall of Fame - The Gottlieb Collection (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pinball Hall of Fame - The Gottlieb Collection (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pinball Hall of Fame - The Gottlieb Collection (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20080226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KOCH Media</developer>
		<publisher>Encore Software</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pinball Hall Of Fame - The Williams Collection (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Pinball Hall of Fame : The Williams Collection</name>
		<desc>Pinball Hall of Fame: The Williams Collection is another entry in the PHOF budget series. Included in the PS2 version are eight authentic pinball tables, some of the best from the 1970s, 1980s and 1990s. The tables are:  Black Knight (1980)  Firepower (1980)  Funhouse (1990)  Gorgar (1979)  Pinbot (1986)  Space Shuttle (1984)  Taxi (1988)  Whirlwind (1988)</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pinball Hall Of Fame - The Williams Collection (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pinball Hall Of Fame - The Williams Collection (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pinball Hall Of Fame - The Williams Collection (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20080226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KOCH Media</developer>
		<publisher>Encore Software</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pinball Heroes (USA) (PSP) (PSN).cso</path>
		<name>Pinball Heroes</name>
		<desc>Classic arcade pinball action in the palm of your hands. With multiple Pinball Heroes pinball tables to download - each one based off of a different hit PlayStation franchise - you'll always have a new challenge to conquer. So whether you?re a casual gamer or a true pinball wizard, Pinball Heroes for the PSP gives you authentic arcade pinball experience - anytime and anywhere.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pinball Heroes (USA) (PSP) (PSN).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pinball Heroes (USA) (PSP) (PSN).mp4</video>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20091217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Pinball</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Invaders Extreme.cso</path>
		<name>Space Invaders Extreme</name>
		<desc>The pixelated aliens are back to celebrate their 30th anniversary!  Taking a cue from other recent arcade classic updates, Space Invaders Extreme takes the gameplay of the 1978 classic, and reinvents it, giving power-up blasters, boss aliens, and an electronic soundtrack that plays in sync with the onscreen action.  Basic gameplay remains the same: Players guide a ground based cannon either left or right, blasting an oncoming fleet of invaders before they reach the ground.  The main objective is to get as many points as possible before running out of lives.  Space Invaders Extreme introduces new elements, such as invader fleets that break pattern from their left to right descent, boss aliens that require several hits to destroy, power-ups that enhance the cannon, allowing the player to wipe out multiple invaders at once, while racking up combos.  Wi-Fi play is also possible, allowing player to team up cooperatively, or compete against the other.  The Nintendo DS version also has a feature for online ranking.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Space Invaders Extreme.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Space Invaders Extreme.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Space Invaders Extreme.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super StarDust Portable.cso</path>
		<name>Super Stardust Portable</name>
		<desc>Super Stardust Portable is an asteroid arcade shooter viewed from above and is based on the PS3 version of Super Stardust HD. In this classic shooter, the player's mission is to destroy everything that comes against him on the screen. Enemies are mainly asteroids but also other spaceships and mines. Because the game has been reworked for PSP, there is no planet in the background and the wireless multiplayer mode is not available. Controls on the left side moves the ship and right sides four buttons controls firing. Super Stardust Portable also introduces a new game mode called Impact, where the player can only use bombs and boost. Also, the game's end boss has been changed to be more difficult.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super StarDust Portable.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Super StarDust Portable.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super StarDust Portable.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20081125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SWAT_-_Target_Liberty.cso</path>
		<name>SWAT : Target Liberty</name>
		<desc>In New York City, a Koren Triad gang is terrorizing the city, attacking citizens in broad daylight and conducting bold robberies in front of hundreds of witness, as Kurt Wolf you lead an elite group of SWAT officers in order to stop the menace and discover a disturbing secret about the Triads, which could lead to the destruction of New York City.    Each SWAT member is unique and has their own attributes and stats, which in upgradable after every level. The main goal of the game is to rescue hostages, take down terrorists and collect evidence. Players can earn extra points for each unharmed hostage and non-lethal takedowns.     The game also features a randomized AI placement, so each level replayed will have enemies and hostages and different locations than the last, for unlimited playing opportunities and players can create their own maps and play with or against other players using Ad-hoc.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/SWAT_-_Target_Liberty.png</image>
		<video>./snap/SWAT_-_Target_Liberty.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/SWAT_-_Target_Liberty.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20071019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3G Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tekken 6.cso</path>
		<name>Tekken 6</name>
		<desc>A must-have for Tekken aficionados, TEKKEN 6 sees the return of many familiar faces as well as new characters to create the largest line-up the series has ever seen. With a growing roster of fighters, each equipped with their own deadly techniques, moves and attack combinations, TEKKEN 6 will be the best King of Iron Fist Tournaments yet. Adding to the already rich gaming experience, a deeper character customization feature will only further enhance the incredible fighting intensity as players go mano-a-mano. Players can also take the battle online for classic match-ups and to compete for world domination.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tekken 6.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tekken 6.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tekken 6.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tekken - Dark Resurrection (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Tekken : Dark Resurrection</name>
		<image>./mixart/Tekken - Dark Resurrection (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tekken - Dark Resurrection (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tekken - Dark Resurrection (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20060725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thunder Mountain</developer>
		<publisher>Thunder Mountain</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiger Woods PGA Tour 10 (USA).cso</path>
		<name>Tiger Woods PGA Tour 10</name>
		<desc>Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2010 features the U.S. Open, the USGA Championship and the USGA's Rules of Golf for the first time in the franchise's history. The Weather Channel provides dynamic weather data for the game (the forecast channel on the Wii). The new "Tournament Challenge" mode allows players to replicate famous shots and moments from the PGA Tour's history.    There are several new courses available for this version of the game, including Bethpage Black, Pinehurst (Course 2), Torrey Pines, Oakmont, Hazeltine National, Banff Springs, and Turnberry, with all those listed courses having hosted major championships before. There are also many golfers featured in the game that are listed below. There are also fictitious golfers who are present in the game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tiger Woods PGA Tour 10 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tiger Woods PGA Tour 10 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tiger Woods PGA Tour 10 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090616T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WWE All-Stars (USA).cso</path>
		<name>WWE All-Stars</name>
		<desc>WWE All Stars can be seen as a successor to WWF Wrestlemania: The Arcade Game. Unlike the simulation-based WWE SmackDown vs. Raw games, it offers a more arcade-oriented gameplay, featuring elements of fighting games, with over-the-top moves and unrealistic animation.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/WWE All-Stars (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/WWE All-Stars (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/WWE All-Stars (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20110401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Sports</genre>
	</game>
</gameList>
